<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <titleStmt>
            <title>A Catalogue of choice English books consisting of divinity, history, physick, and variety of other subjects, which will be exposed to sale, by way of auction, on Monday the 10th day of January 1686/7 at Jonathan's Coffee-House in Exchange-Alley in Cornhil, London.</title>
         </titleStmt>
         <editionStmt>
            <edition>
               <date>1686</date>
            </edition>
         </editionStmt>
         <extent>Approx. 233 KB of XML-encoded text transcribed from 24 1-bit group-IV TIFF page images.</extent>
         <publicationStmt>
            <publisher>Text Creation Partnership,</publisher>
            <pubPlace>Ann Arbor, MI ; Oxford (UK) :</pubPlace>
            <date when="2013-12">2013-12 (EEBO-TCP Phase 2).</date>
            <idno type="DLPS">A31264</idno>
            <idno type="STC">Wing C1302</idno>
            <idno type="STC">ESTC R25971</idno>
            <idno type="EEBO-CITATION">09304475</idno>
            <idno type="OCLC">ocm 09304475</idno>
            <idno type="VID">42676</idno>
            <availability>
               <p>To the extent possible under law, the Text Creation Partnership has waived all copyright and related or neighboring rights to this keyboarded and encoded edition of the work described above, according to the terms of the CC0 1.0 Public Domain Dedication (http://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/). This waiver does not extend to any page images or other supplementary files associated with this work, which may be protected by copyright or other license restrictions. Please go to https://www.textcreationpartnership.org/ for more information about the project.</p>
            </availability>
         </publicationStmt>
         <seriesStmt>
            <title>Early English books online.</title>
         </seriesStmt>
         <notesStmt>
            <note>(EEBO-TCP ; phase 2, no. A31264)</note>
            <note>Transcribed from: (Early English Books Online ; image set 42676)</note>
            <note>Images scanned from microfilm: (Early English books, 1641-1700 ; 1304:17)</note>
         </notesStmt>
         <sourceDesc>
            <biblFull>
               <titleStmt>
                  <title>A Catalogue of choice English books consisting of divinity, history, physick, and variety of other subjects, which will be exposed to sale, by way of auction, on Monday the 10th day of January 1686/7 at Jonathan's Coffee-House in Exchange-Alley in Cornhil, London.</title>
               </titleStmt>
               <extent>24, 24 [i.e. 20] p.   </extent>
               <publicationStmt>
                  <publisher>s.n.],</publisher>
                  <pubPlace>[London :</pubPlace>
                  <date>1686.</date>
               </publicationStmt>
               <notesStmt>
                  <note>Reproduction of original in the British Library.</note>
               </notesStmt>
            </biblFull>
         </sourceDesc>
      </fileDesc>
      <encodingDesc>
         <projectDesc>
            <p>Created by converting TCP files to TEI P5 using tcp2tei.xsl,
      TEI @ Oxford.
      </p>
         </projectDesc>
         <editorialDecl>
            <p>EEBO-TCP is a partnership between the Universities of Michigan and Oxford and the publisher ProQuest to create accurately transcribed and encoded texts based on the image sets published by ProQuest via their Early English Books Online (EEBO) database (http://eebo.chadwyck.com). The general aim of EEBO-TCP is to encode one copy (usually the first edition) of every monographic English-language title published between 1473 and 1700 available in EEBO.</p>
            <p>EEBO-TCP aimed to produce large quantities of textual data within the usual project restraints of time and funding, and therefore chose to create diplomatic transcriptions (as opposed to critical editions) with light-touch, mainly structural encoding based on the Text Encoding Initiative (http://www.tei-c.org).</p>
            <p>The EEBO-TCP project was divided into two phases. The 25,368 texts created during Phase 1 of the project (2000-2009), initially available only to institutions that contributed to their creation, were released into the public domain on 1 January 2015. The approximately 40,000 texts produced during Phase 2 (2009- ), of which 34,963 had been released as of 2020, originally similarly restricted, were similarly freed from all restrictions on 1 August 2020. As of that date anyone is free to take and use these texts for any purpose (modify them, annotate them, distribute them, etc.). But we do respectfully request that due credit and attribution be given to their original source.</p>
            <p>Users should be aware of the process of creating the TCP texts, and therefore of any assumptions that can be made about the data.</p>
            <p>Text selection was based on the New Cambridge Bibliography of English Literature (NCBEL). If an author (or for an anonymous work, the title) appears in NCBEL, then their works are eligible for inclusion. Selection was intended to range over a wide variety of subject areas, to reflect the true nature of the print record of the period. In general, first editions of a works in English were prioritized, although there are a number of works in other languages, notably Latin and Welsh, included and sometimes a second or later edition of a work was chosen if there was a compelling reason to do so.</p>
            <p>Image sets were sent to external keying companies for transcription and basic encoding. Quality assurance was then carried out by editorial teams in Oxford and Michigan. 5% (or 5 pages, whichever is the greater) of each text was proofread for accuracy and those which did not meet QA standards were returned to the keyers to be redone. After proofreading, the encoding was enhanced and/or corrected and characters marked as illegible were corrected where possible up to a limit of 100 instances per text. Any remaining illegibles were encoded as &lt;gap&gt;s. Understanding these processes should make clear that, while the overall quality of TCP data is very good, some errors will remain and some readable characters will be marked as illegible. Users should bear in mind that in all likelihood such instances will never have been looked at by a TCP editor.</p>
            <p>The texts were encoded and linked to page images in accordance with level 4 of the TEI in Libraries guidelines.</p>
            <p>Copies of the texts have been issued variously as SGML (TCP schema; ASCII text with mnemonic sdata character entities); displayable XML (TCP schema; characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or text strings within braces); or lossless XML (TEI P5, characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or TEI g elements).</p>
            <p>Keying and markup guidelines are available at the <ref target="http://www.textcreationpartnership.org/docs/.">Text Creation Partnership web site</ref>.</p>
         </editorialDecl>
         <listPrefixDef>
            <prefixDef ident="tcp"
                       matchPattern="([0-9\-]+):([0-9IVX]+)"
                       replacementPattern="http://eebo.chadwyck.com/downloadtiff?vid=$1&amp;page=$2"/>
            <prefixDef ident="char"
                       matchPattern="(.+)"
                       replacementPattern="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/textcreationpartnership/Texts/master/tcpchars.xml#$1"/>
         </listPrefixDef>
      </encodingDesc>
      <profileDesc>
         <langUsage>
            <language ident="eng">eng</language>
         </langUsage>
         <textClass>
            <keywords scheme="http://authorities.loc.gov/">
               <term>Catalogs, Booksellers' --  England --  London.</term>
               <term>Booksellers and bookselling --  England --  London.</term>
            </keywords>
         </textClass>
      </profileDesc>
      <revisionDesc>
         <change>
            <date>2012-06</date>
            <label>TCP</label>Assigned for keying and markup</change>
         <change>
            <date>2012-07</date>
            <label>SPi Global</label>Keyed and coded from ProQuest page images</change>
         <change>
            <date>2012-08</date>
            <label>Geremy Carnes</label>Sampled and proofread</change>
         <change>
            <date>2012-11</date>
            <label>SPi Global</label>Rekeyed and resubmitted</change>
         <change>
            <date>2013-01</date>
            <label>Geremy Carnes</label>Sampled and proofread</change>
         <change>
            <date>2013-01</date>
            <label>Geremy Carnes</label>Text and markup reviewed and edited</change>
         <change>
            <date>2013-02</date>
            <label>pfs</label>Batch review (QC) and XML conversion</change>
      </revisionDesc>
   </teiHeader>
   <text xml:lang="eng">
      <front>
         <div type="title_page">
            <pb facs="tcp:42676:1" rendition="simple:additions"/>
            <p>A CATALOGUE OF Choice Engliſh Books, Conſiſting of DIVINITY, HISTORY, PHYSICK, AND Variety of other SUBJECTS.</p>
            <p>Which will be expoſed to Sale, by way of Auction, on <hi>Monday,</hi> the <hi>10th</hi> Day of <hi>January,</hi> 1686/7. at <hi>Jonathan</hi>'s Coffee-Houſe in <hi>Exchange-Alley,</hi> in <hi>Cornhil, London.</hi>
            </p>
            <p>Catalogues are to be Diſtributed <hi>gratis,</hi> at the Coffee-Houſe afore<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſaid, the place of Sale: At Mr. <hi>Sam. Walſal</hi>'s at the <hi>Heart</hi> and <hi>Bible,</hi> at the Weſt End of the <hi>Royal Exchange</hi> in <hi>Cornhil:</hi> At Mr. <hi>John Weld</hi>'s at the <hi>Crown</hi> between the Two <hi>Temple Gates</hi> in <hi>Fleet-ſtreet:</hi> At Mr. <hi>Will. Not</hi>'s at the <hi>Queens Arms</hi> in the <hi>Pellmell,</hi> Bookſellers, 1686.</p>
         </div>
         <div type="notice">
            <pb facs="tcp:42676:2"/>
            <head>Conditions of Sale.</head>
            <p n="1">I. That he who bids moſt is the Buyer; but if any difference ariſe, which the Company cannot decide, then the Book or Books ſhall be expoſed to Sale again.</p>
            <p n="2">II. That all the Books in this Catalogue (for ought we know) are Perfect; but if any of them appear to be otherwiſe, before they be taken away, the Buyer ſhall have his choice of taking or leaving them.</p>
            <p n="3">III. That the Money for the Book or Books ſo bought, is to be payd by the Buyer within a Fortnight after the Auction is ended, at the place where they are ſold; where, upon payment thereof, the Book or Books ſhall be delivered.</p>
            <p>The Books will be expoſed to view from <hi>VVedneſday,</hi> the Fifth of <hi>January,</hi> before the Sale, From Nine in the Morning to Twelve, and from Two to Six in the Afternooon.</p>
         </div>
      </front>
      <body>
         <div type="catalogue">
            <pb facs="tcp:42676:2"/>
            <head>Divinity, Hiſtory, Phyſick, Miſcellanies, in <hi>Folio.</hi>
            </head>
            <list>
               <item>1 ANtiquities of <hi>Great Brittain</hi> and <hi>Ireland,</hi> particularly of <hi>Cheſhire.</hi> — 1673</item>
               <item>2 <hi>Ferd. Pulton</hi>'s Collection of Statutes from <hi>Magna Charta</hi> to 1629. —</item>
               <item>3 <hi>Grimſtone</hi>'s General Inventory of the Hiſtory of <hi>France.</hi>— 1607</item>
               <item>4 <hi>Campian</hi>'s two Books of Ayres, to be ſung to the Lute and Viols, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—</item>
               <item>5 Sir <hi>Phil. Sidney</hi>'s Arcadia: wants the end of the Supplement.—1638</item>
               <item>6 <hi>Deſid. Eraſmus,</hi> his Paraphraſe on the New Teſtament. 2 Vol. —</item>
               <item>7 Dr. <hi>Mart. Luther</hi>'s Divine Diſcourſes at his Table, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1652</item>
               <item>8 <hi>S. Clarks</hi> General Martyrology, a Collection of Perſecutions, with Cuts— 1677</item>
               <item>9 —his Lives of ſundry Eminent Perſons.— 1683</item>
               <item>10 <hi>VVill. Perkins</hi> his Works in Divinity. 3 <hi>Vol.</hi>— 1632</item>
               <item>11 Biſhop <hi>Jewels</hi> Defence of the Apology of the Church of <hi>England.</hi> — 1567</item>
               <item>12 — his Reply unto Mr. <hi>Harding</hi>'s Anſwer.—<hi>London.</hi> 1565</item>
               <item>13 <hi>Geo. Hutcheſon</hi>'s Expoſition of the Goſpel of St. <hi>John</hi> — 1657</item>
               <item>14 Sir <hi>Richard Hawkins</hi> his Voyage into the South Sea, <hi>Anno</hi> 1593. — 1622</item>
               <item>15 Dr. <hi>James Hart</hi>'s Diet of the Diſeaſed: the Nature of Dyet, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1633</item>
               <item>16 Biſhop <hi>Cooper</hi>'s Works Collected into one Volume with his Life — 1623</item>
               <item>17 Biſhop <hi>Babington</hi>'s Works; <hi>viz.</hi> on the Creed, Pentateuch, Commandments, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1622</item>
               <item>18 <hi>VVard</hi>'s Queſtions, Obſervations, and Eſſays upon <hi>Matthew</hi>— 1640</item>
               <item>19 <hi>Steph. Charnock</hi>'s Works compleat. 2 <hi>Vol.</hi>— 1684</item>
               <item>20 St. <hi>Auguſtin</hi> of the City of God, with <hi>Vive</hi>'s Comments — 1610</item>
               <item>21 <hi>Tyndal, Frith,</hi> and <hi>Barne</hi>'s Works—1573</item>
               <item>22 <hi>Dubartas</hi> his Divine Weeks and Works Engliſhed by <hi>Sylveſter.</hi> —</item>
               <item>23 <hi>Leigh</hi>'s Syſtem, or Body of Divinity, in 10 Books—1654</item>
               <item>24 Dr. <hi>Brooks</hi>'s Sacred and Myſterious Hiſtory of Man's Redemption— 1657</item>
               <item>25 <hi>Clelia,</hi> a Romance: <hi>2d.</hi> Part.—<hi>wants Title</hi>
               </item>
               <item>26 Dr. <hi>Jo. Mayer's</hi> Commentary on the New Teſtament. 2 <hi>Vol.</hi> — 1631</item>
               <item>27 Biſhop <hi>VVilliams</hi> his true Church ſhewed unto all men, in 6 Books— 1629</item>
               <item>28 <hi>Gurnal</hi>'s Chriſtian in compleat Armour, the <hi>5th</hi> Edition— 1669</item>
               <item>29 <hi>Clem. Cottons</hi> Compleat Concordance to the Bible— <hi>London.</hi> 1631</item>
               <item>30 Dr. <hi>Heylin</hi>'s Life and Death of Archbiſhop <hi>Land— London.</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>31 <hi>Laud</hi>'s Labyrinth in a Reply to his Conference with <hi>Fiſher</hi> — 1658</item>
               <item>32 <hi>Almahide,</hi> or the Captive Queen, an excellent new Romance— 1678</item>
               <item>33 Dr. <hi>Jo.</hi> and <hi>Fr. VVhites</hi> Works in one Volume— 1624</item>
               <item>34 Dr. <hi>Fr. VVhite</hi>'s Reply to the Jeſuite <hi>Fiſher.</hi> — 1624</item>
               <item>35 <hi>VVill. Auſtin</hi>'s Godly and Learned Meditations on the Holy Days— 1635</item>
               <item>36 <hi>H. Davis</hi>'s three Books, belonging to an Uniformity in Churches. — 1669</item>
               <item>37 <hi>Fr. Maſon</hi> of the Conſecration of Biſhops, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1613</item>
               <item>38 Dr. <hi>Andr. VVillet</hi>'s Sixfold Comment. on <hi>Leviticus, &amp;c.</hi> —</item>
               <item>39 — his Sixfold Comment. on <hi>Daniel</hi> with an Appendix— 1610</item>
               <item>40 — his Sixfold Comment. on the Epiſtle to the <hi>Romans</hi>— 1611</item>
               <item>41 <hi>Tho. VVilſon</hi>'s Chriſtian Dictionary: laſt Edition— 1678</item>
               <item>42 <hi>Ja. Howels</hi> Life of <hi>Lewis</hi> the XIII. of <hi>France,</hi> and Cardinal <hi>Richelieu</hi>— 1646</item>
               <item>43 <hi>VVill Fenners</hi> Works in Divinity— <hi>Lettered</hi> 1657</item>
               <item>44 <hi>Jo. Downame</hi>'s Guide to Godlineſs: a Treatiſe of a Chriſtian Life—1622</item>
               <item>45 — his Chriſtian Warfare againſt the Devil, World, and Fleſh—1634</item>
               <item>46 <hi>Perkins</hi> his Works gathered into one Volume— 1603</item>
               <item>47 Biſhop <hi>Geo. Downame</hi> of Juſtification againſt <hi>Bellarmin</hi>—</item>
               <pb n="2" facs="tcp:42676:3"/>
               <item>48 <hi>Ed Elton</hi>'s Sermons on the <hi>7th. 8th. 9th.</hi> of the <hi>Romans</hi>—1653</item>
               <item>49 —his Expoſition on the Epiſtle to the <hi>Goloſſians</hi>—1637</item>
               <item>50 <hi>VVill. Raſtal</hi>'s Collection of Statutes from <hi>Magna Charta</hi> to 1610. —</item>
               <item>51 <hi>Brathwait's</hi> Engliſh Gentleman and Gentlewoman—1641</item>
               <item>52 <hi>Bayn</hi>'s Commentary on the Epiſtle to the <hi>Epheſians</hi>— 1643</item>
               <item>53 <hi>Ed. Leigh</hi>'s <hi>Critica Sacra</hi> on the Old and New Teſtament—1650</item>
               <item>54 General Practice of Phyſick by <hi>VVirtzung</hi> and <hi>Moſan</hi>—1654</item>
               <item>55 <hi>Renodeus</hi> his Diſpenſatory, Engliſhed by <hi>Tomlinſon</hi> —1657</item>
               <item>56 Works of <hi>Tho. Beacon,</hi> a famous Divine under Q. <hi>Mary</hi> and Q. <hi>Elizabeth.</hi> 2 <hi>Vol.</hi> 1564</item>
               <item>57 <hi>Ge<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>fr. Chaucer</hi>'s Works Lettered. (wants a little at the end) —</item>
               <item>58 Dr. <hi>Cave</hi>'s Lives of the Primitive Fathers. 2 Vol. (Guilt and Let.) — 1682</item>
               <item>59 <hi>H. Boughtons</hi> Learned Works, with Dr. <hi>Lightfoot's</hi> Preface—1662</item>
               <item>60 W. <hi>Pembles</hi> Works: <hi>3d</hi> Edition—1635</item>
               <item>61 Dr. <hi>Rob. Harris</hi> his Works, with an Addition of Sermons not extant before.—</item>
               <item>62 <hi>Burgeſs</hi> his Spiritual Refining, of Grace and Aſſurance —1652</item>
               <item>63 <hi>Tho. VVilſon's</hi> Chriſtian Dictionary: laſt Edition. —1678</item>
               <item>64 <hi>Jo. Baccacio</hi>'s Novels and Tales: <hi>5th</hi> Edition.— 1684</item>
               <item>65 <hi>Oſw. Crollius</hi> his Royal and Practical Chymiſtry— 1670</item>
               <item>66 <hi>Pet. Sterry</hi>'s Diſcourſe of the Freedom of the Will —1675</item>
               <item>67 <hi>Ant. Burges</hi> his Doctrine of Original Sin Aſſerted— 1659</item>
               <item>68 Dr. <hi>Jo. Mayer</hi>'s Commentary on <hi>Joſhua, Judges, Ruth, &amp;c.</hi>— 1657</item>
               <item>69 —his Commentary on the Writings of <hi>Job, David,</hi> and <hi>Solomon</hi>—1653</item>
               <item>70 <hi>Ed. Leigh</hi>'s Annotat. Philological and Theological on the New Teſtament—1650</item>
               <item>71 <hi>Rich. Roger's</hi> Commentary on the whole Book of Judges—1615</item>
               <item>72 <hi>Ja. York</hi> of <hi>Lincoln,</hi> Blackſmith, his Heraldry —1641</item>
               <item>73 Lord <hi>Bacon</hi>'s ſeveral Works brought to publick Light—1657</item>
               <item>74 <hi>Jo. Babington</hi>'s Diſcourſe of Artificial Fireworks with Figures —1635</item>
               <item>75 <hi>Iſaackson</hi>'s Chronology, or ſeries and ſucceſſion of the four Monarchies—1633</item>
               <item>76 <hi>Cawley</hi>'s Laws againſt Recuſants, with the Judges Explanations —1680</item>
               <item>77 <hi>Crook</hi>'s Deſcription of the Body of Man, or Anatomy with Figures, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> —</item>
               <item>78 <hi>Bloom</hi>'s Geographical deſcription of the World, with Maps, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> —</item>
               <item>79 <hi>Jo. Ruſhworth</hi>'s Tryal of the Earl of <hi>Strafford</hi> — 1680</item>
               <item>80 —his Collections: 4 Vol. Compleat —1680</item>
               <item>81 <hi>Seneca</hi>'s Works, Moral and Natural; Engliſhed by Dr. <hi>Lodge</hi>—1618</item>
               <item>82 <hi>Townſend</hi>'s Hiſtorical Collections of Queen <hi>Elizabeth</hi>'s four Parliaments—1680</item>
               <item>83 Sir <hi>Sim. d'Ewe</hi>'s Journal of Queen <hi>Elizabeth</hi>'s Parliaments — 1682</item>
               <item>84 Annals of King <hi>James</hi> and King <hi>Charles</hi> the Firſt —1681</item>
               <item>85 <hi>Richardſon</hi>'s ſtate of <hi>Europe,</hi> a Relation of the Provinces thereof — 1627</item>
               <item>86 Sir <hi>Phil. Sidney</hi>'s Arcadia: the laſt Edition —1674</item>
               <item>87 <hi>Ed. Phillips</hi>'s Dictionary of hard Engliſh Words—1658</item>
               <item>88 <hi>Plutarch</hi>'s Lives of the ancient <hi>Greecians</hi> and <hi>Romans, &amp;c.</hi> —1676</item>
               <item>89 <hi>Fox</hi> his Book of Martyrs: or Acts and Monuments. 3 Vol.—1641</item>
               <item>90 Aſſembly of Divines, Annotations on the Bible. 2 Vol. —1651</item>
               <item>91 Dr. <hi>Fulk</hi>'s Confutation of the <hi>Rhemiſts</hi> Teſtament—1589</item>
               <item>92 <hi>Aug. Marlorate</hi>'s Expoſition of St. <hi>Matthew</hi>'s Goſpel — 1570</item>
               <item>93 <hi>Tho. Wilſon</hi>'s Commentary on the Divine Epiſtle to the <hi>Romans</hi> —1653</item>
               <item>94 <hi>Ferd. Pulton</hi>'s Collection of Statutes from <hi>Magna Charta</hi> to 1632.—</item>
               <item>95 <hi>Manby</hi>'s Continuation of <hi>Pulton</hi>'s Statutes to 1667. —</item>
               <item>96 <hi>Hieron</hi>'s Works: <hi>2d.</hi> Vol. <hi>viz.</hi> Sermons, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—1634</item>
               <item>97 <hi>Geo. Kendal</hi>'s Doctrine of the Saints Perſeverance—1654</item>
               <pb n="3" facs="tcp:42676:3"/>
               <item>98 Dr. <hi>Jo. Lightfoot</hi>'s Works; with his Life: 3 Mapps, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 2 Vol. guilt and Let. 1684</item>
               <item>99 Dr. <hi>Franc. Robert</hi>'s Key of the Bible: <hi>3d</hi> Edition—1665</item>
               <item>100 <hi>Arth. Hilderſam</hi>'s 108 Lectures of the <hi>4th</hi> of <hi>John</hi>—1632</item>
               <item>101 <hi>Jo. Babington</hi>'s Diſcourſe of Artificial Fireworks, with Figures, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1635</item>
               <item>102 <hi>Col. Monro</hi>'s Expedition, &amp; Military Obſervations in the Wars of <hi>Swedeland,</hi> &amp;c. 1637</item>
               <item>103 <hi>Andr. Tackquet</hi>'s Military Architecture, or the Art of Fortifying, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1613</item>
               <item>104 Military Inſtructions for the Cavalry, according to Modern War—1644</item>
               <item>105 <hi>Aelian</hi>'s Tacticks, or the Art of Embattailing Armies, by Capt. <hi>Bingham,</hi> with Fig.</item>
               <item>106 Capt. <hi>Ger. Barry</hi>'s Military Diſcipline with Figures—1634</item>
               <item>107 <hi>Len. Willan</hi>'s Perfect Stateſman, or Miniſter of State—1668</item>
               <item>108 <hi>Ambr. Parey</hi>'s Works in Chyrurgery; with <hi>Spigelius</hi> Figures, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> —1677</item>
               <item>109 <hi>Jo. Parkinſon</hi>'s Theatre of Plants, an Univerſal Herbal, with Figures, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—1640</item>
               <item>110 —his Garden of all ſorts of Pleaſant Flowers: Fig.—1656</item>
               <item>111 Dr. <hi>James Hart</hi>'s Dyet of the Diſeaſed, the Nature of Dyet, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—1633</item>
               <item>112 <hi>Barret</hi>'s Dictionary, Engliſh, Latin, Greek, and French— 1580</item>
               <item>113 <hi>Riverius</hi> his Practice and Obſervations of Phyſick; Engliſhed by <hi>Culpepper</hi>—1672</item>
               <item>114 <hi>Batman</hi> upon <hi>Bartholome</hi>'s Book <hi>de proprietatibus rerum,</hi> Engliſh —1582</item>
               <item>115 <hi>Mich. Dalton</hi>'s Country Juſtices Practice out of Seſſions—1630</item>
               <item>116 <hi>Vignola</hi>'s Architecture, 5 Orders thereof, Engliſhed by <hi>Leek</hi> — 1669</item>
               <item>117 Dr. <hi>Tho. Taylor</hi>'s Works, the firſt Volume— 1659</item>
               <item>118 <hi>Benj. Spencer</hi>'s Golden Meane; for Chriſtians to walk by— 1659</item>
               <item>119 <hi>Curia Potitiae,</hi> or the Apologies of ſeveral Princes, with their Effigies, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—</item>
               <item>120 Diſcourſe of the well Governing a Kingdom, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> againſt <hi>Machiavel</hi>—1608</item>
               <item>121 <hi>Eromena,</hi> a Romance, by <hi>Gio. Fr. Biondi</hi> (wants, Title)—</item>
               <item>122 Lord <hi>Bacon</hi>'s Natural Hiſtory in 10 Centuries; <hi>3d</hi> Edition.— 1631</item>
               <item>123 <hi>Evelyns Sylva,</hi> a Diſcourſe of Forreſt-Trees, <hi>&amp;c. Kalendarium Hortenſe</hi>—1664</item>
               <item>124 <hi>Nich. Gulpepper's Pharmacopoeia Londinenſis:</hi> or the <hi>London</hi> Diſpenſatory—1623</item>
               <item>125 <hi>Oſw. Gabelhorer</hi>'s Book of Phyſick, called the <hi>Dutch</hi> Phyſick —1599</item>
               <item>126 <hi>Al. Tops</hi> Book of Praiſes, called the Pſalms of <hi>David— Amſter.</hi> 1629</item>
               <item>127 <hi>G. Sandy</hi>'s Paraphraſe upon the Divine Poems of <hi>Job, David, Solomon, &amp;c.</hi> —1638</item>
               <item>128 —his <hi>Ovid Metamorphoſis</hi> Engliſhed, with Cuts—1632</item>
               <item>129 <hi>Orlando Furioſo</hi> in Engliſh Heroick Verſe, by Sir <hi>Jo. Harrington,</hi> with Cuts, wants Title</item>
               <item>130 <hi>Geo. Chapman</hi>'s Tranſlation of <hi>Homer</hi>'s Iliads, in Verſe; wants Title.—</item>
               <item>131 E. of <hi>Sterlin</hi>'s Recreation with the Muſes, in Tragedies, Poems, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1637</item>
               <item>132 <hi>Brown</hi>'s <hi>Brittannia</hi>'s Paſtorals, Poems, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1613</item>
               <item>133 <hi>Lawe</hi>'s Treaſury of Muſick: Ayres, Dialogues, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1669</item>
               <item>134 Dr. <hi>Bayly</hi>'s Wall Flower, a Marriage between Reality and Fancy, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—1653</item>
               <item>135 <hi>Plinius Secundus</hi> his Hiſtory of the World, or Natural Hiſtory—1635</item>
               <item>136 <hi>Ogilby</hi>'s <hi>Dutch</hi> Embaſſy to the Emperor of <hi>China;</hi> with Figures—1669</item>
               <item>137 —his Works of <hi>Publ. Virgilius Maro,</hi> with Figures and Annotat. —1669</item>
               <item>138 Capt. <hi>Sam. Sturmy</hi>'s Mariners Magazine, <hi>&amp;c. 3d</hi> Edition — 1684</item>
               <item>139 Lightning Column, or Sea Mirrour, containing the Sea Coaſts, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> with Maps &amp; Fig.</item>
               <item>140 <hi>Rich. Stock</hi>'s Learned and uſeful Comment. on <hi>Malachy</hi> — 1641</item>
               <item>141 The Marrow of the <hi>French</hi> Tongue, with Dialogues, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> by <hi>Woodroeph</hi> — 1622</item>
               <item>142 <hi>Arriana,</hi> a Romance, in two parts, Engliſhed out of <hi>French</hi>—1641</item>
               <item>143 <hi>Reynold</hi>'s Triumphs of Gods Revenge againſt Murther, <hi>Imperfect.</hi> —</item>
               <item>144 <hi>Clelia,</hi> an excellent new Romance, by <hi>de Scudery.</hi> Vol. 3.— 1658</item>
               <item>145 Dutcheſs of Newcaſtle's Philoſophical Letters, <hi>&amp;c</hi>—1664</item>
               <item>146 Lo<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap> 
                  <hi>B<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="4 letters">
                        <desc>••••</desc>
                     </gap>
                  </hi>'s Re<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>uſcitatio, in ſeveral of his Works, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> —1657</item>
               <item>147 <hi>Ni<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>. <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 word">
                        <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                     </gap>
                  </hi> Holy Court, in 3 Tomes, Engliſhed by Sir <hi>T. H.</hi>—1634</item>
               <pb n="4" facs="tcp:42676:4"/>
               <item>148 <hi>Sam Clark</hi>'s Martyrology, with Cuts, (wants Title) —1651</item>
               <item>149 Dr. <hi>Ed. Kellet</hi>'s Miſcellanies of Divinity, of the Eſtate of the Soul, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1635</item>
               <item>150 Apologies of ſeveral Princes, Juſtifying to the World their Actions, with Effigies 1654</item>
               <item>151 <hi>Gadbury</hi>'s Collection of Nativities in 150 Genitures, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1662</item>
               <item>152 <hi>Aar. Rathbourn</hi>'s Surveyor in four Books— <hi>London.</hi> 1616</item>
               <item>153 Treaſury of Ancient Times, <hi>viz.</hi> Collections and Obſervations Divine, Moral, Philoſoph. Poetic. Martial, Political, Hiſtor. Aſtrolog. with Figures, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 2 Vol.</item>
               <item>154 <hi>Sam. Purchas</hi> his Pilgrimage, or Relations of the World and Religions thereof, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>155 Dr. <hi>Will. Gouge's</hi> Comment. on the Epiſtle to the <hi>Hebrews:</hi> 2 Vol. with his Life 1650</item>
               <item>156 <hi>Sam. Crook</hi>'s Divine Character of the Hypocrite, and true Chriſtian, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1658</item>
               <item>157 Dr. <hi>Sibs</hi> his Comment on the <hi>2d Corinthians,</hi> Lettered —1655</item>
               <item>158 Biſhop <hi>Hall</hi>'s Paraphraſe on the hard Texts of Scripture of the Old &amp; N. Teſt. 1633</item>
               <item>159 <hi>Patrick Sympſon</hi>'s Hiſtory of the Church from Chriſt to the preſent year 1634.</item>
               <item>160 Biſhop <hi>Nicholſon</hi>'s <hi>Davids</hi> Harp Tuned, on the Pſalms of <hi>David</hi> —1662</item>
               <item>161 Lord <hi>Mornay</hi>'s 4 Books of the Inſtitution of the Sacrament, againſt the Maſs—1600</item>
               <item>162 <hi>Hooker</hi>'s Laws of Eccleſiaſtical Polity in 5 Books— 1617</item>
               <item>163 <hi>Aelian</hi>'s Tacticks, or the Art of an Army Embattailing —1616</item>
               <item>164 Capt. <hi>Jo. Bingham</hi>'s Art of Embattailing an Army—1631</item>
               <item>165 <hi>Jo. Gadbury</hi>'s Collection of Nativities in 150 Genitures—1662</item>
               <item>166 <hi>Nic. Bifield</hi>'s Expoſition on the Epiſtle to the <hi>Coloſſians</hi> — 1617</item>
               <item>167 <hi>Eln. Parr</hi>'s Works, <hi>viz.</hi> on the <hi>Romans,</hi> Grounds of Divinity, and <hi>Abba</hi> Father. —</item>
               <item>168 <hi>Sam. Newman</hi>'s Large and Compleat Concordance to the Bible in Engliſh.— 1650</item>
               <item>169 <hi>Pet. Martyr</hi>'s Common places of Divinity with his Epiſtles. —</item>
               <item>170 <hi>Rich. Greenham</hi>'s Works in Divinity; <hi>5th</hi> Edition.—1612</item>
               <item>171 <hi>Hooker</hi>'s Laws of Eccleſiaſtical Polity; 5 Books; with his Tracts, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> —</item>
               <item>172 Dr. <hi>Sam. Bolton</hi>'s Dead Saint ſpeaking in ſeveral Treatiſes — 1657</item>
               <item>173 <hi>Jo. Balls</hi> Power of Godlineſs: the Natures, Properties, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> of a Godly Life—1657</item>
               <item>174 Dr. <hi>Nat. Homes</hi> his Works in 16 Tracts, Lettered. —<hi>London.</hi> 1652</item>
               <item>175 <hi>Gataker</hi>'s Sermons gathered into one Volume; Lettered —1637</item>
               <item>176 <hi>Roger</hi>'s Lectures on the Hiſtory of <hi>Naaman</hi> the <hi>Syrian,</hi> his Diſeaſe and Cure 1642</item>
               <item>177 <hi>Rand. Cotgraves</hi> Dictionary, <hi>French</hi> and <hi>Engliſh:</hi> and <hi>Engliſh</hi> and <hi>French;</hi> Let. 1632</item>
               <item>178 <hi>Jo. Minſieu</hi>'s Dictionary, <hi>Spaniſh</hi> and <hi>Engliſh,</hi> and <hi>Engl.</hi> &amp; <hi>Spaniſh,</hi> with a Grammar.</item>
               <item>179 <hi>Jo. Flories</hi> World of Words: a Dictionary, <hi>Ital.</hi> and <hi>Engliſh</hi>— 1598</item>
               <item>180 <hi>Jo. Fox</hi>'s Book of Martyrs, or Acts and Monuments, 3 Vol. large Paper—1684</item>
               <item>181 <hi>Steph. Charnock</hi>'s Works compleat, 2 Vol. Guilt and Lettered—1684</item>
               <item>182 <hi>Mercator</hi>'s <hi>Atlas;</hi> or Deſcription of the World, 2 Vol. with Maps, large Paper</item>
               <item>183 Collection of the <hi>Maps</hi> of the World by <hi>Viſcher, de VVit, &amp;c.</hi> in numb. 58 neatly colourd</item>
               <item>184 Hiſtory of the Reformation of the Church of <hi>England,</hi> by Dr. <hi>Burnet.</hi> 2 Vol.</item>
               <item>185 —of <hi>Italy</hi> in its Original Glory, Ruine, and Revival, by <hi>Warcup</hi>—1660</item>
               <item>186 —of <hi>Venice,</hi> and the Wars of <hi>Cyprus, &amp;c.</hi> —1658</item>
               <item>187 —of the admired City and State of <hi>Venice,</hi> in a Proſpect thereof, by <hi>Howel.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>188 —of <hi>Florence,</hi> or the <hi>Florentine</hi> Hiſtory, by <hi>Macchiavel</hi> —1595</item>
               <item>189 —of <hi>France,</hi> or the general Hiſtory thereof, by <hi>Grimſtone</hi> —1621</item>
               <item>190 —of <hi>France,</hi> by <hi>Gualdo Priorato,</hi> Engliſhed by the E. of <hi>Monmouth</hi> — 1676</item>
               <item>191 —of <hi>Lapland,</hi> with an account of their Religion, Manners, Conjurations, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>192 —of the Troubles and Wars of <hi>Swethland</hi> and <hi>Poland,</hi> by <hi>Fowler</hi>—</item>
               <item>193 —of <hi>Lewis XIth.</hi> King of <hi>France:</hi> Engliſhed by <hi>Grimſtone.</hi> —</item>
               <item>194 —of <hi>Polybius,</hi> with the Order of the <hi>Roman</hi> Encamping — 1634</item>
               <item>195 —of the whole World, in a deſcription thereof, by <hi>Heylin</hi>— 1682</item>
               <item>196 —of <hi>Lewis</hi> the XI. and <hi>Charles</hi> the VIII. of <hi>France,</hi> by <hi>Commines</hi>— 1674</item>
               <pb n="5" facs="tcp:42676:4"/>
               <item>197 —of <hi>Lewis</hi> the XIII. and Cardinal <hi>de Richelieu,</hi> by <hi>Howel</hi>—1646</item>
               <item>198 —of <hi>Great Brittain</hi> and <hi>Ireland,</hi> and particularly of <hi>Cheſhire.</hi> by Sr. <hi>P. Leiceſter</hi>
               </item>
               <item>199 —of the Holy War: by <hi>Tho. Fuller.</hi> —1640</item>
               <item>200 —of the Reign of King <hi>Henry</hi> the VII by Lord <hi>Bacon</hi> —1641</item>
               <item>201 —of State of <hi>Europe,</hi> in 14 Books, by <hi>Richardſon</hi>— 1627</item>
               <item>202 —of the wonderful things of Nature, by <hi>Jo. Jonſtonus</hi>—1657</item>
               <item>203 —of <hi>London,</hi> in an Hiſtorical Account thereof, by <hi>J. Howel</hi>—1657</item>
               <item>204 —of the Life and Death of <hi>Hector,</hi> by <hi>Lidgate,</hi> Dedicated to K. <hi>Hen.</hi> V. 1614</item>
               <item>205 —of Nature, or Nat. Hiſt. New <hi>Atlantis, &amp;c.</hi> by Lord <hi>Bacon</hi>—1651</item>
               <item>206 —or Catalogue of the Kings, Princes, Dukes, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> of <hi>England,</hi> by <hi>R. Brooks</hi> 1619</item>
               <item>207 —of the Recovery of <hi>Jeruſalem</hi> by <hi>Godfr. Bulloign</hi> —1600</item>
               <item>208 —of the Precedency of Kings, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> by <hi>Ja. Howel</hi>—1664</item>
               <item>209 —of the Renowned Kingdom of <hi>Naples, &amp;c.</hi> by <hi>J. Howel</hi> —1647</item>
               <item>210 —of <hi>Virginia, New England,</hi> the Summer Iſles, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> by Capt. <hi>Smith,</hi> — 1632</item>
               <item>211 —of the ſix Voyages of <hi>Bapt. Tavernier</hi> into <hi>Perſia,</hi> &amp;c. —1677</item>
               <item>212 —of the World, and Religions of all Ages and Places, by S. <hi>Purchas</hi>—1617</item>
               <item>213 —of the Life and Reign of King <hi>Charles</hi> the Firſt, by <hi>Sanderſon</hi>—1658</item>
               <item>214 —of <hi>Mary</hi> Queen of <hi>Scots</hi> and King <hi>James,</hi> by the ſame—1656</item>
               <item>215 —of <hi>Scotland,</hi> from 1423. to 1542. and of K. <hi>James</hi> and K. <hi>Charles</hi> I. by <hi>Drummond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>216 —of the Advancement and Proficiency of Learning; by Lord <hi>Bacon</hi> — 1640</item>
               <item>217 —of Sir <hi>Richard Hawkins</hi>'s Voyage to the South Sea—1593—162<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>218 —or the Annals of <hi>Corn. Tacitus,</hi> by Sir <hi>H. Savil</hi> — 1640</item>
               <item>219 —of the Great and Renowned Monarchy of <hi>China,</hi> with a Map—1655</item>
               <item>220 —of the Weſt Indies, in a Survey thereof, by <hi>Gage</hi>—1648</item>
               <item>220 —of <hi>Rome,</hi> by <hi>Titus Livius,</hi> Engliſhed by Dr. <hi>Holland,</hi> with a Map, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1686</item>
               <item>221 <hi>Jo. Boccacio</hi>'s Novels and Tales: the Fifth Edition —1684</item>
               <item>222 <hi>Cawley</hi>'s Laws againſt Recuſants, with the Judges Explanation — 1680</item>
               <item>223 <hi>Wheler</hi>'s Voyage into <hi>Greece</hi> in Company of Dr. <hi>Spon:</hi> with Sculptures — 1683</item>
               <item>224 Dr. <hi>Robert Brady</hi>'s Introduction to the Old Engliſh Hiſtory—1684</item>
               <item>225 Capt. <hi>Sam. Sturmys</hi> Mariners Magazin: <hi>3d</hi> Edition— 1684</item>
               <item>226 Hiſtory of <hi>Guſman,</hi> or the <hi>Spaniſh</hi> Rogue. —</item>
               <item>227 Dr. <hi>Jo. Lightfoot</hi>'s Works, with his Life; 3 Maps, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 2 Vol. — 1684</item>
               <item>228 Lord <hi>Bacon</hi>'s Advancement of Learning; 9 Books—1674</item>
               <item>229 <hi>Sam. Clarke</hi>'s General Martyrology, with Cuts, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1677</item>
               <item>230 <hi>Schefferus</hi> his Hiſtory of <hi>Lapland</hi> with Figures, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—1674</item>
               <item>231 <hi>Corn. Tacitus</hi> his Annals in Engliſh, by Sir <hi>Hen. Savile.</hi>—</item>
               <item>232 Biſhop <hi>Cowper's</hi> Works in one Volume, with his Life, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—1622</item>
               <item>233 Dr. <hi>Andrew Willet</hi>'s ſixfold Comment. on <hi>Geneſis</hi> and <hi>Exodus</hi> —1633</item>
               <item>234 <hi>Speed</hi>'s Proſpect of the moſt Famous Parts of the World, his Maps—1627</item>
               <item>235 Holy Bible, of the Old and N. Teſtament with the Apochrypha, an old Tranſlation.</item>
               <item>236 Aphoriſmes Civil and Military, out of <hi>Guicciardin</hi>— 1629</item>
               <item>237 Aſſembly of Divines Annotations on the Bible, 2 Vol. —1657</item>
               <item>238 <hi>Jo. Fox</hi>'s Book of Martyrs, or the Acts and Monuments of the Chruch, 3 Vol. 1684</item>
            </list>
         </div>
         <div type="catalogue">
            <head>Divinity, Hiſtory, Phyſick, Miſcellanies, in <hi>Quarto.</hi>
            </head>
            <list>
               <item>1 <hi>JO. Diodati</hi> his Learned Annotations on the Bible — 1643</item>
               <item>2 <hi>Th. Gale</hi>'s Court of the Gentiles, of the Origine of Humane Literature— 1672</item>
               <item>3 <hi>Leon. Phioravanti</hi>'s 3 exact pieces in Phyſick and Chrurgery—1652</item>
               <item>4 Morning Exerciſe by ſeveral Miniſters at St. <hi>Giles</hi> in the Fields —1676</item>
               <pb n="6" facs="tcp:42676:5"/>
               <item>5 Morning Exerciſe at <hi>Cripplegate</hi> by ſeveral Miniſters —1671</item>
               <item>6 Supplement to the Morning Exerciſe at <hi>Cripplegate</hi>— 1674</item>
               <item>7 Morning Exerciſe by ſeveral Miniſters in <hi>Southwark</hi> —1675</item>
               <item>8 <hi>Ja. Durham</hi>'s Expoſition of the <hi>Canticles,</hi> with Dr. <hi>Owen</hi>'s Preface—1669</item>
               <item>9—his Practical Expoſition of the Ten Commandments—1669</item>
               <item>10 <hi>Jo. Smith</hi>'s <hi>England</hi>'s Improvement Revived, of Husbandry — 1673</item>
               <item>11 Dr. <hi>Hen More</hi>'s Conſutation of Judiciary Aſtrology—1681</item>
               <item>12 <hi>Nic. Morgan</hi>'s Perfection of Horſmanſhip, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> —1609</item>
               <item>13 <hi>Th. Brugis</hi> his Marrow of Phyſick, and the parts of Man's Body —1640</item>
               <item>14 Sir <hi>Tho. Elyot</hi>'s Caſtle of Health, <hi>Cogan</hi>'s Haven of Health, <hi>Viccary</hi>'s Engliſh Man's Treaſure; <hi>Kelway</hi> againſt the Plague. —</item>
               <item>15 Dr. <hi>Tho. Venner</hi>'s <hi>Via Recta ad Vitam Longam,</hi> for attaining to a long Life— 1650</item>
               <item>16 <hi>Aeneas</hi> his Deſcent into Hell, deſcribed by <hi>Virgil, &amp;c.</hi> —1661</item>
               <item>17 <hi>Sihthorp</hi>'s Advertiſement to the <hi>Iriſh,</hi> and Biſhop <hi>Uſhers</hi> Religion of the Ancient <hi>Iriſh.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>18 Sir <hi>Jo. Temples</hi> Hiſtory of the <hi>Iriſh</hi> Rebellion in 1641.—1646</item>
               <item>19 <hi>Terentius</hi> his Comedy, called <hi>Andria,</hi> Engliſhed by Dr. <hi>Webbe</hi> —1629</item>
               <item>20 <hi>Bruel</hi>'s Phyſician's Practice of all Diſeaſes from Head to Foot—1639</item>
               <item>21 Safeguard for Sailors; or Great Rutter—1671</item>
               <item>22 <hi>Gerv. Markham</hi>'s Cavelarice, or Engliſh Horſeman.—</item>
               <item>23 —his Maſter-piece Revived, in the Cure of all Diſeaſes of Horſes— 1683</item>
               <item>24 <hi>Clem. Cotton</hi>'s Compleat Concordance to the Engliſh Bible —1631</item>
               <item>25 <hi>Moſes Cooke</hi>'s Improving, Raiſing, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> of Forreſt Trees — 1679</item>
               <item>26 <hi>Vigo, Gale,</hi> and <hi>Galens</hi>'s Works in Chyrurgery— <hi>London.</hi> 1586</item>
               <item>27 <hi>Rob. Cawdrays</hi> Treaſury or Store-houſe of Similies— 1609</item>
               <item>28 <hi>Arth. Hopton</hi>'s Topographical Glaſs —1611</item>
               <item>29 Dr. <hi>Jo. Collins</hi> his Lecture Sermons on the <hi>2d Canticles</hi> — 1676</item>
               <item>30 Dr. <hi>Tho. Taylor</hi>'s Chriſts Victory over the Dragon— 1633</item>
               <item>31 —his <hi>Moſes</hi> and <hi>Aaron,</hi> or the Types and Shadows of our Saviour—1653</item>
               <item>32 <hi>R. Verſtegan</hi>'s Antiquities of the Engliſh Nation, with Figures— 1634</item>
               <item>33 <hi>Swediſh</hi> Intelligencer of the Wars of <hi>Guſtavus Adolphus</hi> in <hi>Germany,</hi> with Figures, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>34 Map of the World in four parts, <hi>viz. Aſia, Europe, Africa,</hi> and <hi>America</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>35 Perſons Varieties; or a Survey of excellent matters —1635</item>
               <item>36 The School of <hi>Salerne</hi>'s Regiment of Health — 1634</item>
               <item>37 <hi>Will. Leyhorn's Panorganon;</hi> a deſcription of an Inſtrument —1672</item>
               <item>38 <hi>Tho. Brooks</hi>'s Golden Key to open hidden Treaſures —1675</item>
               <item>39 <hi>R. Montague</hi>'s <hi>Apello Caeſarem,</hi> a Juſt Appeal, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1625</item>
               <item>40 <hi>Fab. Phillips</hi>'s Rights and Priviledges of the Kings Servants— 1671</item>
               <item>41 Biſhop <hi>Hall</hi>'s Peace of <hi>Rome,</hi> in above 300 different Opinions— 1609</item>
               <item>42 <hi>Jo. Goodwin</hi> of being filled with the Spirit, in ſeveral Sermons— 1670</item>
               <item>43 <hi>Jo. Fr. Sena<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>lt</hi>'s Man become guilty. And the Chriſtian Man.— 1650</item>
               <item>44 Dr. <hi>Dan. VVhiteby</hi>'s Romiſh Doctrines not from the beginning —1664</item>
               <item>45 <hi>Sam. Woodford</hi>'s Paraphraſe upon the Pſalms of <hi>David.</hi> — 1667</item>
               <item>46 <hi>Mat. Lawrence</hi>'s Uſe, and Practice of Faith, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1657</item>
               <item>47 Deſtruction of <hi>Troy</hi> in three Books: <hi>10th</hi> Edition. — 1680</item>
               <item>48 <hi>Le Febure</hi> his Compleat Body of Chymiſtry, in 2 Books — 1672</item>
               <item>49 Dr. <hi>Tho. Pierces</hi> Collection of Sermons—1671</item>
               <item>50 <hi>Tho. Brook's</hi> Paradice opened, of Divine Love — 1675</item>
               <item>51 <hi>Will. Greenhil</hi>'s Expoſition of <hi>Ezekiel;</hi> 4 firſt parts— 1658</item>
               <item>52 <hi>Jer. Burroughs</hi> two Treatiſes of earthly mindedneſs, and walking with God —1656</item>
               <item>53 <hi>Epicurus</hi>'s Morals Engliſhed by Dr. <hi>Charleton</hi> — 1656</item>
               <item>54 <hi>Rob. Bolton</hi>'s Inſtructions for comforting Afflicted Conſciences—1631</item>
               <pb n="7" facs="tcp:42676:5"/>
               <item>55 Diſcourſe of Horſemanſhip, and the Art of Riding — 1584</item>
               <item>56 <hi>Gerv. Markham</hi>'s Maſter-piece, curing all Diſeaſes in Horſes — 1683</item>
               <item>57 Dr. <hi>Reynolds</hi> 3 Treatiſes: Vanity of the Creature, Sinfulneſs of Sin, &amp; Life of Chriſt</item>
               <item>58 Morning Exerciſe at St. <hi>Giles</hi> in the Fields — 1660</item>
               <item>59 Biſhop <hi>Taylor</hi>'s Vindication of the Sacred Order of Epiſcopacy — 1660</item>
               <item>60 <hi>R. Vine</hi>'s Treatiſe of the Sacrament of the Lords Supper —1657</item>
               <item>61 <hi>Hen. Philips</hi>'s Seaman's Kalender of Navigation — 1679</item>
               <item>62 <hi>Spaniſh</hi> Pilgrim: an admirable diſcovery of a Roman Catholick — 1625</item>
               <item>63 Biſhop <hi>Reynolds</hi> his Works, <hi>viz.</hi> on the Paſſions, and Faculties of the Soul, on the <hi>14th</hi> of <hi>Hoſea,</hi> of the Sacrament; 3 Treatiſes; and on the <hi>110th</hi> Pſalm, 2 Vol.</item>
               <item>64 Dr. <hi>Heylin</hi>'s deſcription of the World: <hi>7th</hi> Edit. Large Paper — 1636</item>
               <item>65 —his Survey of the State of <hi>France,</hi> and the adjoining Iſles — 1656</item>
               <item>66 —his Hiſtory of St. <hi>George</hi> of <hi>Cappadocia</hi>-Aſſerted — 1631</item>
               <item>67 —his Stumbling-block of Diſobedience, laid by <hi>Calvin.</hi> —</item>
               <item>68 —his Hiſtory of the Sabbath, in 2 Books — 1636</item>
               <item>69 The <hi>Jewiſh</hi> Synagogue, a Narration of the State of the <hi>Jews</hi> — 1656</item>
               <item>70 Lord <hi>Mornay</hi>'s Treatiſe of the Church, and the Queſtions thereabout— 1606</item>
               <item>71 <hi>Got</hi>'s Divine Hiſtory of the <hi>Geneſis</hi> of the World, <hi>&amp;c,</hi> — 1670</item>
               <item>72 Abridgement of the Acts and Monuments; or the Book of Martyrs —</item>
               <item>73 The experienced Farrier, or Farring Compleated — 1678</item>
               <item>74 <hi>Nic. le Febure</hi> his compleat Body of Chymiſtry — 1634</item>
               <item>75 <hi>Jo. Baniſter's</hi> Works in Chyrurgery —1633</item>
               <item>76 <hi>Boterus</hi> his Relation of the moſt Famous Kingdoms, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> of the World — 1630</item>
               <item>77 <hi>Hen. Vertue</hi>'s Chriſt and the Church, or Parallels; 3 Books — 1659</item>
               <item>78 Dr. <hi>Hyde</hi>'s Chriſt and the Church; or Chriſtianity explained, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> —1658</item>
               <item>79 <hi>Jo. Fr. Senault</hi>'s Corruption of Nature by Sin — 1650</item>
               <item>80 <hi>Will. Barrife's</hi> Military Diſcipline, or young Artillery Man — 1639</item>
               <item>81 <hi>Sandivogius</hi> his new Light to Alchimy; and Chymical Dictionary— 1650</item>
               <item>82 Dr. <hi>Jo. Mewton</hi>'s help to Calculation — 1657</item>
               <item>83 <hi>Philips</hi> his Sea-man's Kalendar; and <hi>Norwood</hi>'s Sea-man's Practice — 1678</item>
               <item>84 <hi>Nat. Coleſon</hi>'s Mariners new Kalender — 1675</item>
               <item>85 <hi>Ed. Gunter</hi>'s Mathematical Works —1636</item>
               <item>86 Dr. <hi>Rich. Holdſworth</hi>'s Sermons —1651</item>
               <item>87 Lod. <hi>Loyd</hi>'s Marrow of Hiſtory, or Pilgrimage of Kings and Princes — 1653</item>
               <item>88 <hi>Bapt. Guarini</hi>'s <hi>Paſtor Fido</hi> Engliſhed by <hi>Fanſhaw</hi> — 1647</item>
               <item>89 Capt. <hi>Tho. Bining</hi>'s Light to the Art of Gunnery with Figures — 1677</item>
               <item>90 <hi>Mountague</hi>'s <hi>Miſcellanea Spiritualia:</hi> devout Eſſays — 1654</item>
               <item>91 M. <hi>Blundevil</hi>'s Mathematical Exerciſes, in 8 Treatiſes — 1597</item>
               <item>92 Dr. <hi>Tho. Ridley</hi>'s View of the Civil and Eccleſiaſtical Law — 1634</item>
               <item>93 <hi>Tho. Drant</hi>'s <hi>Horace</hi> in Engliſh Verſe —</item>
               <item>94 <hi>Palmer</hi>'s Catholick Planiſphere, or Mathematical Jewel — 1658</item>
               <item>95 Dr. <hi>Stubb</hi>'s Juſtification of the War with <hi>Holland</hi> — 1673</item>
               <item>96 The Hiſtory of <hi>Trebizond,</hi> in 4 Books — 1616</item>
               <item>97 <hi>Rich. Kilburn</hi>'s Topography or Survey of <hi>Kent</hi> — 1659</item>
               <item>98 Dr. <hi>Webb</hi>'s Comedy of <hi>Terentius,</hi> called <hi>Andria:</hi> Latine and Engliſh— 1629</item>
               <item>99 <hi>Ed. Gunter</hi>'s Mathematical Works Reviſed, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> by <hi>Foſter</hi> and <hi>Bond.</hi> 1653</item>
               <item>100 <hi>Noah Biggs</hi> his Vanity of the Craft of Phyſick, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1651</item>
               <item>101 Names of the Pariſhes, Towns, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> in <hi>England</hi> and <hi>Wales,</hi> with Maps &amp; diſtances</item>
               <item>102 <hi>Lylies Euphues,</hi> the Anatomy of Wit, his <hi>England, &amp;c.</hi> — 1636</item>
               <item>103 <hi>Jer. Burrough</hi>'s <hi>Irenicum</hi> to the Lovers of Truth and Peace —1653</item>
               <pb n="8" facs="tcp:42676:6"/>
               <item>104 Divine Right of Church Government and Goſpel Miniſtry — 1654</item>
               <item>105 <hi>Cogan</hi>'s Haven of Health, (wants Title) —</item>
               <item>106 <hi>Tho. Brightman</hi>'s Revelation of St. <hi>John</hi> illuſtrated, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> —1644</item>
               <item>107 <hi>Gio. Torriano</hi>'s <hi>Italian</hi> Tutor, a compleat <hi>Italian</hi> Grammar — 1640</item>
               <item>108 <hi>Bunting</hi>'s Travel of the Holy Patriarchs, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1629</item>
               <item>109 <hi>Godwin</hi>'s <hi>Roman</hi> and <hi>Jewiſh,</hi> and <hi>Rouſe</hi>'s Attick Antiquities — 1638</item>
               <item>110 <hi>Culverwel</hi>'s Learned and Elegant diſcourſe of the Light of Nature, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1669</item>
               <item>111 <hi>Pet. Heylin</hi>'s Coſmography, or brief deſcription of the World — 1629</item>
               <item>112 Biſhop <hi>Nicholſon</hi>'s Expoſition of the Church Catechiſm —1678</item>
               <item>113 <hi>Leon. Phioravanti</hi>'s 3 exact pieces of Secrets, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1652</item>
               <item>114 Commentary's of the Civil Wars of <hi>France,</hi> with an account of the Maſſacre 1574</item>
               <item>115 Dr. <hi>Preſton</hi> on the New Covenant, and Saints daily Exerciſe, of Prayer—</item>
               <item>116 Sir <hi>Fr. Kinaſton</hi>'s Tranſlation of <hi>Chaucer</hi>'s <hi>Troilus</hi> and <hi>Creſida</hi> — 1635</item>
               <item>117 Glory of <hi>England;</hi> the many Prerogatives thereof, and Pilgrimage of Kings, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>118 Dr. <hi>Ed. Reynold</hi>'s on the <hi>14th</hi> of <hi>Hoſea</hi> —1640</item>
               <item>119 Dr. <hi>Tho. Manton</hi>'s Expoſition upon St. <hi>James</hi> and <hi>Jude</hi> — 1645</item>
               <item>120 <hi>Jo. Clark</hi>'s Holy Oyle for the Lamps of the Sanctu<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>y, Scripture Phraſes, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>121 Dr. <hi>Jo. Mayer</hi>'s Engliſh Catechiſm explain'd; <hi>4th</hi> E<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="4 letters">
                     <desc>••••</desc>
                  </gap>on —1630</item>
               <item>122 <hi>Jer. Burrough</hi>'s Goſpel Remiſſion, that Bleſſed<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap> 
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 span">
                     <desc>〈…〉</desc>
                  </gap> in Pardon—1674</item>
               <item>123 <hi>Bernard</hi>'s Rhemes againſt <hi>Rome</hi> in their E<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 chunk">
                     <desc>…</desc>
                  </gap> 
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 chunk">
                     <desc>…</desc>
                  </gap>ion of the Bi<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ſe—1626</item>
               <item>124 <hi>Markham</hi>'s Maſter-piece Revived in the Cu<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 chunk">
                     <desc>…</desc>
                  </gap> 
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 span">
                     <desc>〈…〉</desc>
                  </gap> Diſ<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>ſes in Ec<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ſes, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—1675</item>
               <item>125 Dr. <hi>Reynold</hi>'s Meditation of the Holy Sacr<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 chunk">
                     <desc>…</desc>
                  </gap> 
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 span">
                     <desc>〈…〉</desc>
                  </gap> Lord's Supper— 1639</item>
               <item>126 <hi>Eph. Pagit</hi>'s Chriſtianographie: with <gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 span">
                     <desc>〈…〉</desc>
                  </gap> — 1635</item>
               <item>127 <hi>Tho. Larkham</hi>'s Attributes of God unfol<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 chunk">
                     <desc>…</desc>
                  </gap> 
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 span">
                     <desc>〈…〉</desc>
                  </gap> — <gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="3 letters">
                     <desc>•••</desc>
                  </gap>6</item>
               <item>128 Dr. <hi>Ed. Reynolds</hi> his Vanity of the C<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 chunk">
                     <desc>…</desc>
                  </gap> 
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 span">
                     <desc>〈…〉</desc>
                  </gap> Sin, and <gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 span">
                     <desc>〈…〉</desc>
                  </gap> 
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 chunk">
                     <desc>…</desc>
                  </gap>ſt</item>
               <item>129 Report of the Kingdom of <hi>Congo,</hi> a Reg<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="3 letters">
                     <desc>•••</desc>
                  </gap> 
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 span">
                     <desc>〈…〉</desc>
                  </gap> Figures, <gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> — 1597</item>
               <item>130 <hi>Chr. Lever</hi>'s Hiſtory of the Defenders of the Catho<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="3 letters">
                     <desc>•••</desc>
                  </gap>k <gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>ith — 1627</item>
               <item>131 <hi>Dud. Digs</hi> unlawfulneſs of Subjects taking up Arms, &amp; <hi>Symon</hi>'s defence of K. <hi>Charles</hi>
               </item>
               <item>132 <hi>R. Cawdray</hi>'s Treaſury or Store-houſe of Similies (wants Title) —</item>
               <item>133 <hi>Ed. Marbury</hi>'s Commentary on the Prophecy of <hi>Habakkuk</hi> — 1650</item>
               <item>134 <hi>Tho. Stirrup</hi>'s compleat Dialiſt of making Dials, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1659</item>
               <item>135 Dr. <hi>Tho. Goodwin</hi>'s Collection of his Works or Pieces, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> —1643</item>
               <item>136 <hi>Chr. Love</hi> of Grace; the Zealous Chriſtian, Heavens Glory, and Hells Terror 1631</item>
               <item>137 <hi>Pet. Charron</hi> of Wiſdom; 3 Books: Engliſhed by <hi>Lennard</hi> —</item>
               <item>138 Hiſtory of the Heroick Life, and deplorable Death of K. <hi>Henry</hi> the <hi>4th</hi> of <hi>France.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>139 <hi>Bapt. Guarini</hi>'s <hi>Paſtor fido,</hi> Engliſhed by <hi>Fanſhaw</hi> —1647</item>
               <item>140 <hi>Fr. Junius</hi> of the painting of the Ancients, 3 Books — 1638</item>
               <item>141 <hi>Phil. Barrough</hi>'s Method of Phyſick for the curing of diſeaſes — 1634</item>
               <item>142 <hi>Ed. Wright's</hi> certain Errors in Navigation corrected — 1657</item>
               <item>143 <hi>Cranmer</hi>'s defence of the Catholick Doctrine of the Sacrament, and <hi>Fox</hi>'s Sermons</item>
               <item>144 <hi>Mat. Sutclif</hi>'s Practice, Proceeding, and Laws of Arms — 1593</item>
               <item>145 <hi>Steph. Gardner</hi>'s Anſwer to <hi>George Joy</hi>'s Confutation —1546</item>
               <item>146 <hi>Camden</hi>'s Remains concerning <hi>Brittain,</hi> eſpecially <hi>England</hi> —1614</item>
               <item>147 <hi>Rog. Aſcham</hi>'s Schoolmaſter for the teaching of the Latine Tongue —1570</item>
               <item>148 <hi>Tho. Godwin</hi>'s <hi>Jewiſh</hi> and <hi>Roman</hi> Antiquities — 1601</item>
               <item>149 Biſhop <hi>Hall</hi>'s Epiſcopacy by divine Right aſſerted —1640</item>
               <item>150 <hi>Jo. Dod</hi> and <hi>Rob. Clever</hi>'s Expoſition of the Commandments —1632</item>
               <item>151 Sir <hi>Hen. Spelman</hi>'s large Treatiſe of Tithes — 1647</item>
               <item>152 <hi>Rich. Bernard</hi>'s <hi>Terence</hi>'s Comedies Engliſh and Latine—1607</item>
               <item>153 <hi>Roman</hi> Conclave in the Lives of the Roman Emperors, and Popes—1609</item>
               <pb n="9" facs="tcp:42676:6"/>
               <item>154 <hi>Card. Contareno</hi>'s Commonwealth of <hi>Venice,</hi> and the Dukes Lives — 1599</item>
               <item>155 <hi>Prideaux</hi> his Compendious Introduction for the reading of Hiſtories — 1648</item>
               <item>156 <hi>Gurnal</hi>'s Chriſtian in compleat Armour: firſt and ſecond parts—1656</item>
               <item>157 Earl of <hi>Clarendon</hi>'s View and Survey of <hi>Hobb</hi>'s Leviathan — 1676</item>
               <item>158 Sir <hi>Ken. Digby</hi> of Bodies, and the Immortality of Man's Soul —1645</item>
               <item>159 <hi>Will. Prin</hi>'s <hi>Hiſtrio-Maſtix,</hi> or the Players Scourge, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1633</item>
               <item>160 D. <hi>Leon. Phioravanti</hi>'s 3 exact pieces of Secrets of Phyſick —</item>
               <item>161 Dr. <hi>Tho. Muffet</hi>'s Healths Improvement: Rules for food, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—1655</item>
               <item>162 <hi>P<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>t. Charron</hi> of Wiſdom, 3 Books; Engliſhed out of <hi>French</hi> —</item>
               <item>263 <hi>Fr. Quarle</hi>'s divine Fancies; and his <hi>Argalus</hi> and <hi>Parthenia</hi> —1638</item>
               <item>264 <hi>R. Vine</hi>'s Gods drawing, and Mans coming to Chriſt, in 32 Sermons — 1662</item>
               <item>265 <hi>Nic. Bifiela</hi>'s Rule of Faith, an expoſition of the Creed — 1626</item>
               <item>166 <hi>Jo. Rud. Glauber</hi>'s deſcription of new Philoſophical Furnaces —1659</item>
               <item>167 <hi>Jeſ. Mede</hi>'s Key of the Revelation, Engliſhed by <hi>R. Moore</hi> —1643</item>
               <item>168 Dr. <hi>Jo. Owen</hi>'s Practical Expoſition on the 130th Pſalm — 1669</item>
               <item>169 <hi>Fr. Walſingham</hi>'s ſearch into matters of Religion— 1609</item>
               <item>170 <hi>Ed. Symon</hi>'s Vindication of King <hi>Charles</hi> the Firſt— 1648</item>
               <item>171 <hi>Fenner</hi>'s Treatiſe of the Affections, and Chriſts Alarm to drowſie Saints— 1650</item>
               <item>172 <hi>Bernard</hi>'s Key of Knowledge for the opening of the Revelation— 1617</item>
               <item>173 —his <hi>Terrence,</hi> his Comedies, Engliſh and Latine; <hi>6th</hi> Edition —1641</item>
               <item>174 Sir <hi>Ken. Digby</hi> of Bodies, and the Soul; with <hi>Roſs</hi> his Philoſophical Touchſtone</item>
               <item>175 <hi>Ant. Burges</hi> his true Doctrine of Juſtification — 1654</item>
               <item>176 <hi>Ja. Howel</hi>'s Familiar Letters Domeſtick and Forrreign —1645</item>
               <item>177 <hi>Geo. Strode</hi>'s Anatomy of Mortality, in 8 Head—1632</item>
               <item>178 Dr. <hi>Jo. Preſton</hi>'s Sin's Overthrow of Mortification — 1641</item>
               <item>179 <hi>Watſon</hi>'s <hi>Decacordon</hi> of 10 Quodlibetical Queſtions betwixt the Prieſts and Jeſuits</item>
               <item>180 <hi>Ed. Leigh</hi>'s Treatiſe of Divinity, in three Books — 1647</item>
               <item>181 Dr. <hi>Jo. Stoughton</hi>'s 15 Sermons upon ſelect Occaſions — 1640</item>
               <item>182 Dr. <hi>Will. Gouge</hi>'s domeſtical Duties, in 8 Treatiſes — 1622</item>
               <item>183 <hi>Gale</hi>'s Court of the Gentiles of the Original of humane Literature, 2 parts. —1669</item>
               <item>184 Lord <hi>Bacon</hi>'s Eſſays or Counſels Civil and Moral— 1639</item>
               <item>185 Dr. <hi>Tho. Venner</hi>'s <hi>Via recta ad vitam longam</hi> —1650</item>
               <item>186 <hi>Will. Langham</hi>'s Garden of Health in the Propertys of all Simples, Plants, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>187 <hi>Jer. Burrough</hi>'s Goſpel Remiſſion: the bleſſedneſs of Pardon, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—1674</item>
               <item>188 Dr. <hi>Jo. Owen</hi>'s death of death in the death of Chriſt — 1648</item>
               <item>189 <hi>Dod</hi> and <hi>Clever</hi>'s plain and familiar Expoſition of the Commandments —</item>
               <item>190 <hi>Dan. Cawdrey</hi> and <hi>H. Palmer</hi>'s Chriſtian Sabbath vindicated, both parts compleat</item>
               <item>191 Dr. <hi>Tho. Jacomb</hi>'s ſeveral Sermons on the <hi>8th</hi> of the <hi>Romans</hi> —1672</item>
               <item>192 Sir. <hi>Jo. Hayward</hi>'s Lives of the three <hi>Norman</hi> Kings of <hi>England</hi>— 1613</item>
               <item>193 <hi>If. Ambroſe</hi>'s <hi>Media,</hi> or the middle things in reference to the firſt and laſt—1650</item>
               <item>194 <hi>Gale</hi>'s Court of the Gentiles; firſt part —1669</item>
               <item>195 Dr. <hi>Tho. Manton</hi>'s Expoſition, with Notes, on St. <hi>James</hi> — 16<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>3</item>
               <item>196 —his practical Commentary on the Epiſtle of <hi>Jude</hi> — 1658</item>
               <item>197 Dr. <hi>Ob. Grew</hi>'s Meditations on our Saviour's Parable of the Prodigal— 1678</item>
               <item>198 <hi>H. Broughton</hi>'s Revelation of the Holy Apocalypſe — 1610</item>
               <item>199 <hi>Cl. Cotton</hi>'s compleat Concordance to the Bible in Engliſh — 1635</item>
               <item>200 <hi>Tho. Caſe</hi>'s Mount <hi>Piſgah,</hi> or Proſpect of Heaven — 1670</item>
               <item>201 M. <hi>Prideaux</hi>'s Introduction for the reading of Hiſtories— 1650</item>
               <item>202 Dr. <hi>Jo. Owen</hi>'s death of death in the death of Chriſt — 1648</item>
               <item>203 Dr. <hi>Hen. Hammond</hi>'s practical Catechiſm; <hi>5th</hi> Edition —1649</item>
               <pb n="10" facs="tcp:42676:7"/>
               <item>204 <hi>Tho. Brooks</hi> his golden Key to open hidden Treaſures — 1675</item>
               <item>205 <hi>Jo. Calvin</hi>'s Sermons on the Epiſtles to <hi>Timothy</hi> and <hi>Titus</hi>— 1579</item>
               <item>206 <hi>Camden</hi>'s Remains concerning <hi>Brittain,</hi> eſpecially <hi>England</hi>— 1629</item>
               <item>207 <hi>Owen Feltham</hi>'s Reſolves, a duple Century; <hi>6th</hi> Edition —1636</item>
               <item>208 <hi>Tho. Wright</hi>'s Paſſions of the mind in general; Six Books— 1630</item>
               <item>209 <hi>Brerewood</hi>'s Enquiry's touching diverſitys of Languages and Religions — 1635</item>
               <item>210 <hi>Prideaux</hi> his compendious Introduction to Hiſtories, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1654</item>
               <item>211 <hi>Atwel</hi>'s faithful Surveyor, and Errors in Land meaſuring — 1658</item>
               <item>212 F. <hi>Paul</hi>'s Apology in defence of <hi>Gerſon</hi> of Excommunication againſt <hi>Bellarmin</hi>—</item>
               <item>213 <hi>Pet. Charron</hi> of Wiſdom, 3 Books, out of <hi>French</hi> —</item>
               <item>214 Hiſtory of the Quarrels of Pope <hi>Paul</hi> the V. with the <hi>Venetians</hi> —1626</item>
               <item>215 <hi>Rich. Norwood</hi>'s Trigonometry, or Doctrine of Triangles— 1631</item>
               <item>216 <hi>Camden</hi>'s Remains concerning <hi>Brittain,</hi> eſpecially <hi>England</hi> —1614</item>
               <item>217 <hi>Glanvil</hi>'s 7 Eſſays on important Subjects in Philoſophy and Religion —1678</item>
               <item>218 <hi>Diggs</hi> his Geomecrical Treatiſe of <hi>Pantometria</hi> and <hi>Longometria</hi> — 1571</item>
               <item>219 <hi>Virgil</hi>'s 13 Books of <hi>Aeneids</hi> Engliſhed by <hi>Th. Phaer,</hi> and <hi>Th. Twyne</hi>— 1584</item>
               <item>220 Hiſtory of <hi>Aſtrea</hi> and <hi>Celadon,</hi> a Romance, in 12 Books — 1620</item>
               <item>221 Dr. <hi>Mart. Luther</hi>'s Commentary on the Pſalms, of degrees— 1577</item>
               <item>222 Dr. <hi>Edw. Reynold</hi>'s Explanation on the 110th Pſalm —1642</item>
               <item>223 <hi>Nic. Culverwel</hi>'s Light of Nature, with other Treatiſes, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1652</item>
               <item>124 <hi>Jo. Eeaton</hi>'s Honey comb of free Juſtification — 1642</item>
               <item>125 Archbiſhop <hi>Bancroft</hi>'s Survey of the pretended Holy Diſcipline—1663</item>
               <item>226 <hi>Pet. Heylin</hi>'s Cofmography, or deſcription of the World —1636</item>
               <item>227 Hiſtory of <hi>Valentine</hi> and <hi>Orſon,</hi> Sons of the Emperor of <hi>Greece</hi>—1679</item>
               <item>228 <hi>Jo. Trapp</hi>'s Comment on the Pentateuch, or 5 Books of <hi>Moſes</hi> —1650</item>
               <item>229 —his Comment. on <hi>Proverbs, Eccleſiaſtes,</hi> and <hi>Canticles</hi> — 1650</item>
               <item>230 —his Commentary on the 4 Evangeliſts and Acts of the Apoſtles— 1647</item>
               <item>231 —his Commentary on all the Epiſtles, Revelation, and common places —1647</item>
               <item>232 Dr. <hi>Ed. Reynolds</hi> his 3 Treatiſes: and on the 110th Pſalm— 1633</item>
               <item>233 <hi>R. Bernard</hi>'s <hi>Terences</hi> Comedies, Engliſh and Latine—1641</item>
               <item>234 <hi>G. Sandy</hi>'s View or ſurvey of the ſtate of Religion in the Weſt, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—1629</item>
               <item>235 <hi>Pet. Heylin</hi>'s little deſcription of the great World: <hi>7th</hi> Edition—1636</item>
               <item>236 Part of a Regiſter, containing ſundry memorable matters by divers Godly Men —</item>
               <item>237 <hi>Ant. Burges</hi> his Vindication of the moral Law, and of Juſtification—1647</item>
               <item>238 <hi>Panoplie</hi> of Epiſtles out of <hi>Cicero,</hi> and others —1576</item>
               <item>239 <hi>Wil. Symmond</hi>'s <hi>Piſgah Evangelica</hi> on the Revelation — 1605</item>
               <item>240 Admirable Hiſtory of a Penitent Woman ſeduced to become a Witch, wants Index</item>
               <item>241 Dr. <hi>Hen. Hammond</hi>'s Practical Catechiſm; and 10 Tracts, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> —1646</item>
               <item>242 <hi>Dan. Cawdrey,</hi> and <hi>Herb. Palmer</hi>'s Chriſtian Sabbath Vindicated; <hi>2d</hi> part —1652</item>
               <item>243 <hi>Barclay</hi> of the Temporal Authority of the Pope over Princes, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> —1611</item>
               <item>244 True Relation of the Affairs of <hi>Cleve</hi> and <hi>Gulick, &amp;c. Harcourts</hi> Voyage to <hi>Guinia,</hi> and the Travels of <hi>Monſieur de Monfart.</hi>— 1614</item>
               <item>245 Biſhop <hi>Hoper</hi>'s Anſwer to St. <hi>Gardner</hi>'s detection of the Devils Sophiſtry —1547</item>
               <item>246 <hi>Tho. Brightman</hi>'s Works, <hi>viz.</hi> on the <hi>Revelation, Daniel, Canticles</hi>— 1644</item>
               <item>247 <hi>Cypr. Lucar</hi>'s Mathematical Treatiſe, called <hi>Lucarſolace;</hi> wants end —</item>
               <item>248 <hi>Will. Pryn</hi>'s ſignal Loyalty, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> of Gods Saints towards their Kings, 2 Vol.—1660</item>
               <item>249 Life and Reign of King <hi>Henry 3d. Hen. 4th.</hi> and <hi>Ed. 6th.</hi> by Sir <hi>Jo. Hayward</hi> 1599</item>
               <item>250 <hi>Ja. Durham</hi>'s Expoſition of the <hi>Canticles,</hi> or Song of <hi>Solomon</hi>— 1669</item>
               <item>251 <hi>Squire</hi>'s Expoſition on the <hi>2d</hi> to the <hi>Theſſalonians</hi> — 1630</item>
               <item>252 Dr. <hi>Jo. Preſton</hi> on the new Covenant, Saints Exerciſe of Prayer, and Court Sermons</item>
               <pb n="11" facs="tcp:42676:7"/>
               <item>253 <hi>Will. Hugh</hi>'s Abridgement of Ordinances of Parliament from 1640 to 1656.</item>
               <item>254 <hi>Phillips</hi> Praeemption and Pourveyance for the King— 1663</item>
               <item>255 Perfect Conveyancer, or ſeveral ſelect and choice Preſidents— 1650</item>
               <item>256 <hi>Sam. Clark</hi>'s marrow of Eccleſiaſtical Hiſtory in the Lives of the Fathers, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 2 Vol.</item>
               <item>257 —his Lives of 10 Eminent Divines, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> not in the Folio Edit. of his Lives 1662</item>
               <item>258 <hi>Jo. Valdeſſo</hi>'s 100 Divine Conſiderations — 1638</item>
               <item>259 Archbiſhop <hi>Cranmer</hi> of the Sacrament of the Body and Blood of Chriſt, wants Title</item>
               <item>260 <hi>R. <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>ſtin</hi>'s Treatiſe of Fruit-Trees, their grafting, ſetting, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> —</item>
               <item>261 Dr. <hi>Jo. Preſton</hi>'s Life Eternal, of the Attributes, and Saints Qualification—1633</item>
               <item>262 —on the new Covenant, Saints daily Exerciſe, of Prayer, and Court Sermons</item>
               <item>263 <hi>Rob. Bolton</hi>'s learned and Pious Works: <hi>viz.</hi> a diſcourſe about the ſtate of true Happineſs: directions for walking with God: Inſtructions for comforting afflicted Conſciences. 4 laſt things; Sermons, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 2 Vol. — 1641</item>
               <item>264 <hi>Gurnal</hi>'s Chriſtian in compleat Armour, a Magazin opened: 3 parts: <hi>4th</hi> Edit. 2 Vol.</item>
               <item>265 <hi>Ant. Burgeſs</hi> his Spiritual Refining, <hi>2d</hi> part: and of Juſtification — 1654</item>
               <item>266 <hi>Tho. Cartwright</hi>'s Reply to Archbiſhop <hi>Whitgyfte;</hi> 2 Vol. — 1575</item>
               <item>267 —his ſecond Reply to Archbiſhop <hi>Whitgyfte:</hi> alone — 1575</item>
               <item>268 <hi>Rob. Bolton</hi>'s Inſtructions for comforting Afflicted Conſciences —1635</item>
               <item>269 <hi>Weemſe</hi>'s Chriſtian Synagogue: Pourtraiture of the Image of God: &amp; Obſervat. <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>270 <hi>Peacham</hi>'s Compleat Gentleman, of drawing, Limning, Antiquities, <hi>&amp;c. wants Title.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>271 <hi>Manſion</hi> of Magnanimity in the Actions of Engliſh Kings, Princes, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1590</item>
               <item>272 <hi>Tho. Cogan's</hi> Haven of Health, upon 5 Words of <hi>Hippocrates</hi>—1636</item>
               <item>273 <hi>Jo. Collin's</hi> Sector on a Quadrant, in the uſe of four ſeveral Quadrants — 1659</item>
               <item>274 <hi>Tho. Brook's</hi> Paradice opened; the Myſteries and Rarities of Divine Love 1673</item>
               <item>275 <hi>Pet. Martyr</hi>'s decades of the Hiſtorys of the <hi>Spaniards</hi> in the Weſt Indies—1612</item>
               <item>276 The Image broken in defence of the Kings Book againſt <hi>Milton</hi>—1651</item>
               <item>277 The Hiſtory of Independency, the <hi>2d</hi> part— 1648</item>
               <item>278 <hi>Glanvil's ſcepſis ſcientifica;</hi> or confeſt Ignorance the way to Science — 1665</item>
               <item>279 <hi>Sam. Clark's</hi> Lives of the Fathers, Reformers, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> with their Effigies—1650</item>
               <item>280 <hi>Hartgil's</hi> Aſtronomical Tables reduced to our Age by <hi>Gadbury</hi>— 1656</item>
               <item>281 The examination of Wits, diſcovering what profeſſion each one is apt for, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>282 Dr. <hi>Mark Ridley's</hi> Treatiſe of magnetical Bodies and motions— 1613</item>
               <item>283 <hi>Geo. Silver's</hi> Paradoxes of defence; and the true grounds of Fight—1599</item>
               <item>284 <hi>Fr. Godwin's</hi> Catalogue of the Biſhops of <hi>England</hi> —1601</item>
               <item>285 <hi>M. Aur. Antoninus</hi> his-Meditations Engliſhed, and Notes by <hi>M. Caſaubon</hi>—1653</item>
               <item>286 <hi>Herd. Cortes</hi> Conqueſt of the Weſt India, now new <hi>Spain,</hi> by the <hi>Spaniards</hi>—1578</item>
               <item>287 <hi>Ro. Aſchams Toxophilus,</hi> or the School of Shooting —1589</item>
               <item>288 <hi>R. Record's</hi> Pathway to Knowledge in the Principles of Geometry— 1557</item>
               <item>289 <hi>Tho. Dig's</hi> Arithmetical and Warlike Treatiſe, named <hi>Stratioticos</hi>—1590</item>
               <item>290 <hi>Leon. Maſcal's</hi> Book of the Government of Cattel — 1610</item>
               <item>291 <hi>Gerardo,</hi> the unfortunate <hi>Spaniard,</hi> a Pattern for Laſcivious Lovers — 1622</item>
               <item>292 <hi>Jo. Speidel's</hi> Geometrical extraction, a Collection of the choiſeſt Problems— 1657</item>
               <item>293 Declaration of the Practiſes and Treaſons attempted, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> by the E. of <hi>Eſſex</hi>—1601</item>
               <item>294 <hi>Albion's England,</hi> the Hiſtory thereof in Verſe; to Queen <hi>Elizabeth</hi> — 1598</item>
               <item>295 Sir <hi>Roger L'Eſtrange's</hi> Apology, with the Tranſactions leading to the Kings Reſtaur.</item>
               <item>296 <hi>Arth. Hopton</hi>'s Topographical Glaſs, and Geodetical Staff; 2 Mathemat. Treatiſes</item>
               <item>297 <hi>E. Meſſelden</hi>'s Circle of Commerce, or balance of Trade —1623</item>
               <item>298 <hi>Pet. du Moulin</hi>'s Anatomy of Arminianiſme, Engliſhed out of Latine— 1620</item>
               <item>299 St. <hi>Auguſtin</hi>'s Religion and Sums: and <hi>Montagu</hi>'s new Gag for an old Gooſe 1624</item>
               <item>300 <hi>Al. Roſs</hi> his Philoſophical Touchſtone againſt <hi>Digby</hi> of Bodies, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—1645</item>
               <pb n="12" facs="tcp:42676:8"/>
               <item>301 Biſhop <hi>Bilſon</hi>'s Sermons of the Redemption of Mankind, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1599</item>
               <item>302 King <hi>Henry</hi> the <hi>8th</hi> his Primer: <hi>2d</hi> Edition; wants Title—</item>
               <item>303 Dr. <hi>Sibs</hi> his Bowels opened on the <hi>4th 5th 6th</hi> of <hi>Canticles</hi> —1639</item>
               <item>304 <hi>Shepheard</hi>'s faithful Councellour; or the marrow of the Law; Engliſh —1651</item>
               <item>305 <hi>Will. Weſt</hi>'s <hi>S<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>mboleography,</hi> of Inſtruments and Preſidents, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 2 parts; with Supplications, Bills, and Anſwers, Pleadings, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—1618</item>
               <item>306 Dr. <hi>Tho. Jacomb</hi>'s Sermons on the <hi>8th</hi> to the <hi>Romans</hi> — <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>672</item>
               <item>307 <hi>Jo. Weemſe</hi>'s Learned Works in 4 parts; 3 Vol. Compleat — 1636</item>
               <item>308 <hi>Greenhil's</hi> Expoſition on <hi>Ezekiel:</hi> Chapt. 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13. — 1649</item>
               <item>309 Dr. <hi>Jo. Preſton's</hi> Breaſt-plate of Faith and Love; <hi>4th</hi> Edition— 1634</item>
               <item>310 <hi>Jo. Caryl's</hi> Expoſition on the 32.33. and 34 Chapt. of <hi>Job,</hi> being the <hi>10th</hi> p<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="3 letters">
                     <desc>•••</desc>
                  </gap> 1661</item>
               <item>311 <hi>Jo. Well's</hi> Soul's Progreſs to the Celeſtial <hi>Canaan</hi> — 1639</item>
               <item>312 Dr. <hi>Sib</hi>'s Returning Back-ſlider, a Commentary on the <hi>14th</hi> of <hi>Hoſea</hi> — 1639</item>
               <item>313 Dr. <hi>Mart. Day's</hi> Sermons on the Reſurrection of the Body, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> —1636</item>
               <item>314 Dr. <hi>Sclater's</hi> Expoſition on the firſt and ſecond of the <hi>Theſſalonians</hi>—1630</item>
               <item>315 Holy Bible containing the Old Teſtament and the New; with Notes, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1583</item>
               <item>316 <hi>Fides Catholica,</hi> or the Doctrine of the Catholick Church— <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>661</item>
               <item>317 <hi>Walt. Bruel</hi>'s Phyſicians Practice, curing all diſeaſes, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1639</item>
               <item>318 <hi>Geo. Swinnock's</hi> Fading of the Fleſh, and Flouriſhing of Faith— 1662</item>
               <item>319 <hi>Jo. Birchenſha</hi>'s Hiſtory of divine Verities, in 4 parts — 1655</item>
               <item>320 <hi>Tho Gataker</hi> of the nature and uſe of Lots — 1619</item>
               <item>321 Dr. <hi>R. Fown's</hi> 3 holy Offices of <hi>Jeſus Chriſt, &amp;c.</hi> — 1619</item>
               <item>322 <hi>Hurault's</hi> Politick, Moral, and Martial Diſcourſes — 1595</item>
               <item>323 <hi>Rich. Brathwait's</hi> Survey of Hiſtory, or a Nurſery for Gentry —1638</item>
               <item>324 P. <hi>du Moulin's</hi> Buckler of Faith, in deſence of the Reformed of <hi>France</hi>—1620</item>
               <item>325 <hi>Tho. Harby's</hi> What is Truth? or the Pattern in the Mount— 1673</item>
               <item>326 Dr. <hi>Will. Gouge's</hi> Saints Sacrifice; on the <hi>16th</hi> Pſalm—1632</item>
               <item>327 Dr. <hi>Jo. Favor's</hi> Antiquity triumphing over Novelty — 1619</item>
               <item>328 <hi>Finch's</hi> Summ of ſacred Divinity publiſhed by <hi>Jo. Downame</hi> —</item>
               <item>329 <hi>Jo. Mureet's</hi> ſeveral Works, with his Life, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> publiſhed by Mr. <hi>Caryl</hi> &amp; Dr. <hi>
                     <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>anton</hi>
               </item>
               <item>330 <hi>Jer. Burrough's</hi> his <hi>Moſes</hi> Choice, with his Eye fixed upon Heaven— 1650</item>
               <item>331 <hi>Jo. Ball's</hi> Treatiſe of Faith, the Nature and Life thereof; <hi>3d</hi> Edition—1657</item>
               <item>332 <hi>Latham's</hi> new and ſecond Book of Falconry, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1633</item>
               <item>333 Dr. <hi>Jo. Stoughton's</hi> 15 Sermons on ſelect occaſions, with his 7 Sermons—</item>
               <item>334 —his 13 Sermons Preached in <hi>Aldermanbury</hi> Church — 1640</item>
               <item>335 Dr. <hi>Mart. Day's</hi> Doomſday; or a Treatiſe of the Reſurection of the Body, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1632</item>
               <item>336 Dr. <hi>Mart. Luther's</hi> Commentary on the Epiſtle to the <hi>Galathians</hi>—1588</item>
               <item>337 Dr. <hi>Jo. Preſt<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>n's</hi> Breaſt-plate of Faith and Love, with his Court Sermons—1630</item>
               <item>338 <hi>Tho. Gataker</hi> of the nature and uſe of Lots, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1619</item>
               <item>339 <hi>Crow's</hi> Catalogue of our <hi>Engliſh</hi> Writers on the Bible, Interleaved — 1668</item>
               <item>340 Biſhop <hi>Reynold's</hi> Work, <hi>viz.</hi> on the Paſſions and Faculties of the Soul: On the Lords laſt Supper: On the <hi>14th</hi> of <hi>Hoſea:</hi> 3 Treatiſes: on the 110th Pſalm: Sermons</item>
               <item>341 <hi>Rich. Turnbul's</hi> Expoſition on the Epiſtles of <hi>James</hi> and <hi>Jude</hi>—1600</item>
               <item>342 <hi>Weemſe's</hi> Expoſititon of the Ceremonial, Moral, and Judicial Laws: &amp; Exercitations</item>
               <item>343 —his Expoſition of the Moral Law or 10 Commandments—1632</item>
               <item>344 The Holy Bible, with the Common Prayer and Pſalms, <hi>&amp;c. — Oxford.</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>345 <hi>Dr. Edw. Stillingſteet's Irenicum,</hi> or Weapon-ſalve for the Churches Wounds 1662</item>
               <item>346 <hi>Herb. Thorndike</hi>'s juſt Weights and Meaſures, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1680</item>
               <item>347 The Famous, delectable, and Pleaſant Hiſtory of <hi>Pariſmus</hi> — 1684</item>
               <item>348 Dr. <hi>Tho. Goodwin</hi>'s Pieces, or Works Collected into one Volume— 1643</item>
               <pb n="13" facs="tcp:42676:8"/>
               <item>349 <hi>Joſ. Caryl</hi>'s Expoſition on the 7 firſt Chapters of <hi>Job,</hi> parts 1 and 2 — 1644</item>
               <item>350 <hi>Tho. Hooker</hi>'s Souls Vocation or effectual calling to Chriſt—1638</item>
               <item>351 Dr. <hi>Hammond</hi>'s Vindication of the diſſertations concerning Epiſcopacy— 1654</item>
               <item>352 <hi>Jo. Clark</hi>'s Holy Oyle for the Lamps of the Sanctuary, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1630</item>
               <item>353 <hi>Jo. Paget</hi>'s Arrow againſt the <hi>Browniſts,</hi> and of <hi>Talmudi<expan>
                        <am>
                           <g ref="char:abque"/>
                        </am>
                        <ex>que</ex>
                     </expan> &amp; Rabbinical Allegations.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>354 <hi>Ja. Buck</hi>'s Treatiſe of the Beatitudes, or <hi>Chriſt</hi>'s happy Men —1637</item>
               <item>355 Sir <hi>H. Plat</hi>'s Jewel-Houſe of Art and Nature, of Husbandry, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—1653</item>
               <item>356 <hi>Hall</hi>'s Mortality's meditation in Verſe: and the Golden Fleece, of Trade, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—</item>
               <item>357 <hi>Nehem. Roger</hi>'s Strange Vineyard in <hi>Palaeſtina,</hi> on <hi>Iſaiah</hi>'s Parable, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1623</item>
               <item>358 Dr. <hi>Dan. Featly</hi>'s Romiſh Fiſher caught in his own Net, againſt the Jeſuite <hi>Fiſher</hi> 1624</item>
               <item>359 <hi>Rob. Cleaver</hi>'s Explanation of the Book of <hi>Proverbs</hi> —1615</item>
               <item>360 Dr. <hi>Reeve</hi>'s <hi>England</hi>'s Reſtitution, the man of men, the Stateſman — 1660</item>
               <item>361 <hi>Jo.</hi> Lord <hi>Napier</hi>'s plain diſcovery of the whole Revelation — 1611</item>
               <item>362 The Office and Duty of Executors, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1641</item>
               <item>363 <hi>Horn</hi>'s Brazen Serpent, or Chriſts Exaltation for mans Salvation—1673</item>
               <item>364 E. <hi>Mollinier</hi>'s Eſſays; or moral and political diſcourſes —1636</item>
               <item>365 St. <hi>Auguſtin</hi>'s Rule for the Brothers &amp; Siſters of that Profeſſion, with St. <hi>Hugh</hi>'s Exp.</item>
               <item>366 <hi>Jo. Harding</hi>'s Chronicle of <hi>England</hi> to King <hi>Edward</hi> the <hi>4th</hi> in Verſe, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1543</item>
               <item>367 Daily Obſervations, Meditations divine and moral, by a Perſon of Honor 1654</item>
               <item>368 Dr. <hi>Will. Gouge</hi>'s Guide to go to God, on the Lords Prayer—1636</item>
               <item>369 Dr. <hi>Burgeſs</hi> his Anſwer to <hi>Ames,</hi> in defence of the 3 Ceremonies, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1631</item>
               <item>370 Dr. <hi>Collins</hi> his Cordial for a fainting Soul, Sermons, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—1649</item>
               <item>371 Dr. <hi>Ed. Reynold</hi>'s <hi>Iſrael</hi>'s Prayer in time of Trouble, on the <hi>14th</hi> of <hi>Hoſeah</hi> 1655</item>
               <item>372 <hi>Nicolſon</hi>'s Apology for the diſcipline of the ancient Church— 1659</item>
               <item>373 Biſhop <hi>Hall</hi>'s Epiſcopacy by divine Right aſſerted — 1640</item>
               <item>374 <hi>Ed. Reeve</hi>'s Chriſtian Divinity contained in the Book of Common Prayer— 1631</item>
               <item>375 <hi>Hilderſam</hi> of Faſting, and Prayer, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> with his Effigies: and <hi>Whately</hi>'s New Birth—</item>
               <item>376 Dr. <hi>Jo. Boys</hi> his Expoſition of the Epiſtles and Goſpels in the Liturgy— 1615</item>
               <item>377 Biſhop <hi>Geo. Downame</hi> of the Covenant of Grace, and of perſeverance—1631</item>
               <item>378 —his Treatiſe of Antichriſt; on the <hi>15th</hi> Pſalm: and 2 Sermons 1603</item>
               <item>379 King <hi>James</hi> his Apology for the Oath of Allegiance, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> Dutiful Conſid. by a <hi>Rom.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>380 Lord <hi>Bacon</hi>'s 2 Books of the Advancement and Proficiency of Learning — 1605</item>
               <item>381 <hi>Liſle</hi>'s <hi>Dukartas</hi> his 4 Books, in French and Engliſh Verſe — 1637</item>
               <item>382 <hi>Dan. Dyke</hi>'s 6 Evangelical Hiſtories: Expoſition of <hi>Philemon:</hi> and of Afflictions</item>
               <item>383 Familiar Epiſtles of Sir <hi>Antony</hi> of <hi>Guevard,</hi> Engliſhed— 1584</item>
               <item>384 <hi>Ed. Elton</hi>'s Gods holy mind, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> on the 10 Commandments and Lords Prayer 1647</item>
               <item>385 Dr. <hi>Fr. White</hi> of the Sabbath day, againſt Sabbatarian Novelty—1635</item>
               <item>386 <hi>Partheniſſa,</hi> a Romance, the laſt part— 1656</item>
               <item>387 Biſhop <hi>Weſtfield's</hi> 11 choice Sermons —1655</item>
               <item>388 Dr. <hi>Tho. Taylor's</hi> Commentary on the Epiſtle of <hi>Paul</hi> to <hi>Titus</hi> —1612</item>
               <item>389 Dr. <hi>Jo. Mayer</hi>'s Engliſh Catechiſm explained, on the Church Catechiſm—1630</item>
               <item>390 Dr. <hi>Cowel</hi>'s Interpreter, or the ſignification of the Words of the Law — 1637</item>
               <item>391 <hi>Heliodorus</hi> his <hi>Aethiopian</hi> Hiſtory, Engliſhed out of Greek— 1587</item>
               <item>392 Dr. <hi>Wil. Gouge</hi>'s whole Armour of God for the Chriſtian Soldier—1615</item>
               <item>393 <hi>Ed. Deering's</hi> Lectures on the Epiſtle to the <hi>Hebrews</hi> — 1578</item>
               <item>394 <hi>Tho. Brightman</hi>'s Revelation of the Apocalipſe, <hi>&amp;c.— Amſterdam</hi> 1611</item>
               <item>395 <hi>Jo. Ball</hi>'s Treatiſe of the Covenant of Grace, publiſhed by S. <hi>Aſh</hi> —1645</item>
               <item>396 <hi>R. Bernard</hi>'s Evidences, that the Church of <hi>England</hi> is Apoſtolical, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—</item>
               <item>397 <hi>Wil. Perkin</hi>'s Expoſition of the Symbole, or Creed of the Apoſtles —1595</item>
               <item>398 <hi>Ant. Gade</hi>'s Juſtification of the Church of <hi>England</hi> againſt the Church of <hi>Rome</hi> 1631</item>
               <pb n="14" facs="tcp:42676:9"/>
               <item>399 <hi>Will. Cowper</hi>'s Heaven opened, on the <hi>8th</hi> of the <hi>Romans; 6th</hi> Edition — 1632</item>
               <item>400 <hi>Wil. Pryn</hi>'s Church of <hi>England</hi>'s old Antitheſis to new Arminianiſm— 1620</item>
               <item>401 Dr. <hi>Sclater</hi>'s Expoſition on the 3 firſt Chapters to the <hi>Romans</hi> — 1611</item>
               <item>402 Biſhop <hi>Lucy</hi>'s Treatiſe of the Nature of a Miniſter in all its Offices— 1670</item>
               <item>403 <hi>Joſ. Caryl</hi>'s Expoſition on the <hi>18th. 19th.</hi> and <hi>20th.</hi> Chapters of <hi>Job;</hi> part 6—1658</item>
               <item>404 <hi>Jef, Wat</hi>'s Vindication of the Church and Univerſitys of <hi>England</hi>— 1657</item>
               <item>405 <hi>Wil. Perkin's</hi> Expoſition of the Symbole, or Creed of the Apoſtles—1611</item>
               <item>406 <hi>Tho. Wilſon</hi>'s Commentary on the Divine Epiſtle to the <hi>Romans</hi> — 1614</item>
               <item>407 <hi>Moulin</hi>'s Buckler of Faith, in defence of the Confeſſion of the Reformed of <hi>France</hi>
               </item>
               <item>408 <hi>Ed. Holyoke</hi> (of <hi>New England</hi>) his Doctrine of Life, or of Mans Redemption 1658</item>
               <item>409 Biſhop <hi>King</hi>'s Lectures upon <hi>Jonas,</hi> delivered at <hi>York, Anno</hi> 1594. — 1618</item>
               <item>410 <hi>Tho. Wilſon</hi>'s Chriſtian Dictionary, of the ſignification of the chiefeſt words in Script.</item>
               <item>411 <hi>Tho. Adam</hi>'s Happineſs of the Church, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> in ſundry Sermons— 1619</item>
               <item>412 <hi>Jo. White's</hi> way <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> the true Church, and defence of the ſame, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—1616</item>
               <item>413 <hi>Wil. Pryn</hi>'s perpe<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>uity of a regenerate Man's Eſtate — 1626</item>
               <item>414 <hi>Joſ. Caryl</hi>'s Expoſition of the <hi>15th. 16th. 17th</hi> Chapters of <hi>Job:</hi> being the <hi>5th</hi> part.</item>
               <item>415 <hi>Ed. Elton</hi>'s Expoſition on the Epiſtle of St. <hi>Paul</hi> to the <hi>Coloſſians</hi>—1615</item>
               <item>416 <hi>Rich. Turnbul</hi>'s Expoſition on the Epiſtles of St. <hi>James,</hi> and <hi>Jude</hi> —1606</item>
               <item>417 <hi>Elton</hi>'s Triumph of a true Chriſtian, on the <hi>8th</hi> to the <hi>Romans</hi>—1623</item>
               <item>418 <hi>Jo. Clarks</hi> holy Oyl for the Lamps of the Sanctuary, or Scripture Phraſes, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1630</item>
               <item>419 Biſhop <hi>Abernethy</hi>'s Heavenly Treatiſe, of Phyſick for the Soul, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1622</item>
               <item>420 Dr. <hi>Tho. Taylor</hi>'s <hi>David</hi>'s Learning, the high way to happineſs, on the 32 Pſalm 1617</item>
               <item>421 <hi>Go. Goodman</hi>'s fall of Man, or the Corruption of Nature proved, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1616</item>
               <item>422 <hi>R. Bernard</hi>'s <hi>Terence</hi>'s Comedies, in Engliſh and Latine; <hi>6th</hi> Edition — 1647</item>
               <item>423 Bp <hi>Cowper</hi>'s Heaven opened, on the <hi>8th</hi> of <hi>Romans: Dykes</hi> deceitfulneſs of the Heart</item>
               <item>424 Dr. <hi>Tho. Taylor</hi> on the Parable of the Sower, and the Seed— 1621</item>
               <item>425 <hi>Dan. Dyke</hi>'s 2 Treatiſes, of Repentance, and Chriſts Temptations —1635</item>
               <item>426 <hi>Nic. Lockyer</hi>'s Sermons on the 1 <hi>Coloſſians, &amp;c.</hi> — wants Title</item>
               <item>427 <hi>Ed. Elton</hi>'s Gods holy Mind, <hi>&amp;c. viz.</hi> on the Commandments, and Lords Prayer</item>
               <item>428 <hi>Ed. Leigh</hi>'s <hi>Critica Sacra</hi> on all the Greek Words in the New Teſtament—1635</item>
               <item>429 <hi>Tho. Stoughton</hi>'s 2 Treatiſes, of <hi>David</hi>'s Love to, and Meditation in, the Word, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>430 <hi>Pet. Barker</hi>'s Learned and Familiar Expoſition on the 10 Commandments —1633</item>
               <item>431 <hi>Jo. Hull</hi>'s St. <hi>Peter</hi>'s Propheſie of theſe laſt days, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1611</item>
               <item>432 Dr. <hi>Jo. Burges</hi> his Vindication of Biſhop <hi>Morton</hi>'s defence of the 3 Ceremonies</item>
               <item>433 <hi>Benj. Woodbridge</hi>'s Method of Grace in Juſtification of Sinners—1656</item>
               <item>434 Lord <hi>Bacon</hi>'s 2 Books of the Advancement and Proficience of Learning — 1605</item>
               <item>435 <hi>Joſ. Caryl</hi>'s Expoſition of the 22, 23, 24, 25, and 26 Chapters of <hi>Job,</hi> being the <hi>7th</hi> par<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>436 <hi>Jo. Goodwin</hi>'s Treatiſe of Juſtification by the Imputation of Faith—164<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>437 <hi>Jo. Boterus</hi> his Relation of the moſt Famous Kingdoms, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> of the World—163<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>438 <hi>Tho. Wilſon</hi>'s Chriſtian Dictionary; <hi>3d</hi> Edition— 162<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>439 <hi>Jo. Downame</hi>'s Lectures on the 4 firſt Chapters of <hi>Hoſea</hi>— 160<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>440 Dr. <hi>Tho. Taylor</hi>'s Commentary on the Epiſtle to <hi>Titus</hi> — 161<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>441 Biſhop <hi>King</hi>'s Lectures upon <hi>Jonas,</hi> at <hi>York, Anno</hi> 1594.— 161<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>442 <hi>Pemble</hi>'s <hi>Vindiciae Fidei, &amp; Vindiciae Gratiae;</hi> of Juſtification, and Plea for Grace 162<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>443 <hi>Ant. Burgeſs</hi> his Vindication of the Moral Law, and Covenants— 164<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>444 <hi>Dan. Dyke</hi>'s Expoſition on <hi>Philemon:</hi> School of Afflictions: &amp; 6 Evangelic. Hiſtorie<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>445 Dr. <hi>Sanderſon</hi>'s 10 Sermons, <hi>ad Clerum, ad Magiſtratum, ad Populum.</hi> —162<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>446 Dr. <hi>Jo. Rainold</hi>'s Conference with <hi>Hart,</hi> of the Popes Supremacy — 162<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>447 <hi>Ed. Elton</hi>'s Triumph of a true Chriſtian, on the <hi>8th</hi> of the <hi>Romans</hi> — 162<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>448 R. <hi>Stocks</hi> Stock of divine Knowledge on the Attributes —16<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <pb n="15" facs="tcp:42676:9"/>
               <item>449 <hi>Jo. Baſtwick</hi>'s utter routing of the Independent Army—wants Title —</item>
               <item>450 Sir <hi>R. L'Eſtrange</hi>'s Relapſed Apoſtate, againſt the Petition for Peace, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—1661</item>
               <item>451 —his Truth and Loyalty Vindicated, againſt <hi>Bagſhaw</hi> — 1662</item>
               <item>452 <hi>Godwin</hi>'s Engliſh Expoſition of the Roman Antiquitys —1671</item>
               <item>453 <hi>Colſon</hi>'s General Repertory of Accounts of Chriſtendom— 1612</item>
               <item>454 Dr. <hi>Ed. Reynold</hi>'s Meditations on the Sacrament of the Lords laſt Supper— 1639</item>
               <item>455 D. <hi>Roger</hi>'s Treatiſe of the two Sacraments, Baptiſm, and the Lords Supper—1635</item>
               <item>456 <hi>Tho. Hooker</hi>'s Chriſtians chief Leſſons, <hi>viz.</hi> of ſelf-denyal and ſelf-Tryal—1640</item>
               <item>457 <hi>Dan. Dyke</hi>'s diſcourſe and diſcovery of the deceitfulneſs of Mans Heart— 1642</item>
               <item>458 Dr. <hi>Ed. Reynold</hi>'s Explication of the 110th Pſalm—1632</item>
               <item>459 <hi>Ed. Elton</hi>'s Gods Holy Mind, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> on the Commandments, and Lords Prayer 1625</item>
               <item>460 <hi>Tho. Hooker</hi>'s Souls Exaltation and ingrafting into Chriſt, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1638</item>
               <item>461 Dr. <hi>Sanderſon</hi>'s 12 Sermons: with an Addition of 2 Sermons; <hi>3d</hi> Edition —1637</item>
               <item>462 <hi>Ed. Elton</hi>'s Expoſition on the Epiſtle to the <hi>Coloſſians,</hi> in ſundry Sermons—1615</item>
               <item>463 <hi>Jo. Gore</hi>'s 10 Godly and Fruitful Sermons upon ſeveral Occaſions— 1646</item>
               <item>464 R. <hi>Maden</hi>'s Chriſts Love and Affection towards Jeruſalem, in ſeveral Sermons 1637</item>
               <item>465 Dr. <hi>du Moulin</hi>'s ſincerity of the Proteſtant Religion, againſt <hi>Philanax Anglicus</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>466 <hi>Jo. Bal.</hi>'s Friendly Tryal of the Grounds tending to ſeparation— 1640</item>
               <item>467 Dr. <hi>Bridges</hi> of the Princes Supremacy in Eccleſiaſtical Cauſes, wants Title—</item>
               <item>468 Dr. <hi>Wil. Covel</hi> of the Eccleſiaſtical State of this Kingdom —1604</item>
               <item>469 D. <hi>Roger's</hi> Practical Catechiſm, a View of Principal Truths, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1633</item>
               <item>470 <hi>Jo. Yate</hi>'s <hi>Ibis ad Caeſarem,</hi> againſt <hi>Mountague</hi>'s Appeal— 1626</item>
               <item>471 The Collegiate Suffrage of the Divines of <hi>Great Brittain</hi>— 1629</item>
               <item>472 <hi>Joſ. Shute</hi>'s Judgement and Mercy, or the Plague of Frogs; 9 Sermons— 1645</item>
               <item>473 Divine Dictionary, or the Bible abbreviated, the Contents thereof, with Sermons</item>
               <item>474 Biſhop <hi>Weſtfieid</hi>'s 11 choice Sermons on ſundry Occaſions—1656</item>
               <item>475 Dr. <hi>Tho. Taylor</hi>'s Progreſs of Saints to full Holineſs—1630</item>
               <item>476 Dr. <hi>Wil. Sclater</hi>'s Expoſition on the firſt and ſecond Epiſtle to the <hi>Theſſalonians</hi> 1630</item>
               <item>477 <hi>Rich. Bernard</hi>'s Key of Knowledge for the opening of St. <hi>John</hi>'s Revelation—1617</item>
               <item>478 <hi>Culverwel's</hi> learned and elegant diſcourſe of the Light of Nature, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1669</item>
               <item>479 <hi>Tho. Brooks</hi> his Golden Key to open hidden Treaſures—1675</item>
               <item>480 Biſhop <hi>Nicolſon</hi>'s Expoſition on the Catechiſm of the Church of <hi>England</hi>—1678</item>
               <item>481 Truth will out, a diſcovery of ſome Untruths in Biſhop <hi>Taylor</hi>'s diſſuaſive—1665</item>
               <item>482 Biſhop <hi>King</hi>'s Lectures upon <hi>Jonas,</hi> delivered at <hi>York, Anno</hi> 1594.— 1600</item>
               <item>483 Biſhop <hi>Hall</hi>'s Epiſcopacy by divine Right aſſerted — 1640</item>
               <item>484 <hi>Sam. Rutherfurd</hi>'s Survey of the Spiritual Antichriſt, againſt the <hi>Antinomians</hi>—1648</item>
               <item>485 —his Divine Right of Church Government, and Excommunication —1646</item>
               <item>486 Dr. <hi>Dan. Featly</hi>'s dippers dipt, in a diſputation in <hi>Southwark,</hi> &amp;c. —1647</item>
               <item>487 <hi>Joſ. Caryl</hi>'s expoſition of the <hi>8th 9th</hi> and <hi>10th</hi> Chapters of <hi>Job,</hi> being the <hi>3d</hi> part</item>
               <item>488 <hi>De la Noves</hi> Politick and Military diſcourſes — 1597</item>
               <item>489 <hi>Markham</hi>'s Maſter-piece revived, touching the Cure of all diſeaſes in Horſes 1681</item>
               <item>490 Chriſtian Policy; or the Chriſtian Commonwealth, out of <hi>Spaniſh</hi> — 1632</item>
               <item>491 Every Woman her own Midwife, a compleat Cabbinet for Child-bearing Women</item>
               <item>492 <hi>Ed. Marbury</hi>'s Commentary on the Propheſie of <hi>Habakkuk</hi> — 1650</item>
               <item>493 <hi>Jo. Downame's</hi> Lectures on the 4 firſt Chapters of <hi>Hoſea</hi>— 1650</item>
               <item>494 The Counſellor of Eſtate; or the moſt remarkable conſiderations for publick good</item>
               <item>495 Dr. <hi>Hoyle</hi>'s Juſtification of Biſhop <hi>Uſher</hi>'s Book of the Real Preſence againſt <hi>Malone</hi>
               </item>
               <item>496 P. <hi>du Moulin's</hi> defence of the Catholick Faith againſt <hi>Coffiteau</hi>— 1610</item>
               <item>497 <hi>Jer. Burrough</hi>'s <hi>Irenicum</hi> to the Lovers of Peace and Truth — 1653</item>
               <item>498 Sir <hi>Mart. Cognet</hi>'s Politick diſcourſes upon Truth and Lying—1586</item>
               <pb n="16" facs="tcp:42676:10"/>
               <item>499 <hi>Mat. Sutcliff</hi>'s Practice, Proceedings, and Laws of Arms—1593</item>
               <item>500 <hi>Shepheard</hi>'s Calender, <hi>Colin</hi> Clouts come home again, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> by <hi>Spencer</hi>—1597</item>
               <item>501 <hi>Joſ. Caryl</hi>'s Expoſition with Notes on the 11, 12, 13, and 14 <hi>Job,</hi> part 4. — 1652</item>
               <item>502 Dr. <hi>Burges</hi> his Anſwer to <hi>Ames,</hi> in defence of Biſhop <hi>Morton</hi> of the 3 Ceremonies</item>
               <item>503 Sir <hi>Chriſt, Sibtho<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>p</hi>'s Advertiſement to the pretended Catholicks of <hi>Ireland, &amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>504 Dr. <hi>Pet. Heylin</hi>'s Stumbling-block of Diſobedience laid by <hi>Calvin,</hi> Removed 1658</item>
               <item>505 <hi>Tho. Blake</hi>'s Treatiſe of the Covenant of God entered with Mankind — 1658</item>
               <item>506 The experienced Farrier, or Farring compleated — 1617</item>
               <item>507 <hi>Ed. Symon</hi>'s Vindication of King <hi>Charles,</hi> or a Loyal Subject's dury— 1648</item>
               <item>508 Mr. <hi>de Bellay</hi>'s Military Inſtructions for the Wars — 1589</item>
               <item>509 Dr. <hi>Don</hi>'s five Sermons <hi>Rogers</hi> on the 29 Articles: and <hi>Sandy</hi>'s <hi>Europae ſpeculum</hi>
               </item>
               <item>510 Dr. <hi>Reynold</hi>'s 3 Treatiſes, the Vanity of the Creature, Sinfulneſs of Sin, &amp; Life of Chriſt</item>
               <item>511 Dr. <hi>Jo. Preſton</hi>'s new Covenant, or the Saints Portion; <hi>8th</hi> Edition — 1634</item>
               <item>512 <hi>Jo. Mayer</hi>'s Engliſh Catechiſm explained, on the Church Catechiſm— 1623</item>
               <item>513 Letters of Mr. <hi>de Balzack</hi> Engliſhed by W. <hi>Thirwyt, &amp;c.</hi>— 1634</item>
               <item>514 <hi>Dan. Cawdrey</hi> and <hi>Herb. Palmer</hi>'s Chriſtian Sabbath Vindicated; <hi>2d</hi> part— 1652</item>
               <item>515 W. <hi>Creed</hi>'s Refuter Refuted, in Vindication of Dr. <hi>Hammond</hi> againſt <hi>Jeanes</hi>—1659</item>
               <item>516 <hi>Tho. Styrrup</hi>'s deſcription and uſe of the univerſal Quadrat — 1655</item>
               <item>517 The whole Works of <hi>Sam. Daniel,</hi> Eſq; in Poetry — 1623</item>
               <item>518 Dr. <hi>Jo. Stoughton</hi>'s 15 choice Sermons, preached upon ſelect Occaſions — 1640</item>
               <item>516 <hi>Ed. Leigh</hi>'s Treatiſe of Divinity, in 3 Books— 1646</item>
               <item>520 <hi>Rob. Bolton</hi>'s ſome general directions for walking with God, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1638</item>
               <item>521 Dr. <hi>Jo. Mayer</hi>'s Engliſh Catechiſm explained, on the Church Catechiſm—1635</item>
               <item>522 R. <hi>Stock</hi>'s ſtock of divine Knowledge on the Attributes — 1641</item>
               <item>523 <hi>Tho. Blake</hi>'s Covenant ſealed, a treatiſe of the Sacraments of both Covenants—1655</item>
               <item>524 <hi>Tho. Hooker</hi>'s Souls Humiliation: Unbelievers preparing for <hi>Chriſt:</hi> Souls preparat. <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>525 Biſhop <hi>King</hi>'s Lectures upon <hi>Jonas,</hi> and Funeral Sermon on the Archbiſh. of <hi>York</hi>
               </item>
               <item>526 <hi>Wil. Gerrard,</hi> and Capt. <hi>Hichcock</hi>'s Art of War; with Figures, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1591</item>
               <item>527 Lord <hi>Bacon's</hi> Eſſays, or Councils Civil and Moral—<hi>London</hi> 1629</item>
               <item>528 <hi>Rich. Braithwait</hi>'s Survey of Hiſtory: or a Nurſery for Gentry — 1638</item>
               <item>529 <hi>Hurault</hi>'s Politick, Moral, and Martial diſcourſes, out of <hi>French</hi>— 1595</item>
               <item>530 <hi>Wil. Bucanus</hi> his Inſtitution of <hi>Chriſtian</hi> Religion out of Gods Word—1606</item>
               <item>531 Dr. <hi>Wil. Sclater</hi>'s expoſition on the firſt and and ſecond of the <hi>Theſſalonians</hi> — 1638</item>
               <item>532 An Abſtract of certain Acts, Canons, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> for the Government of the Church—</item>
               <item>533 <hi>Hen. C<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>rn. Agrippa</hi>'s 3 Books of Occult Philoſophy, Engliſhed by J. F. — 1651</item>
               <item>534 <hi>Tho. Harby</hi>'s what is Truth? Recommended by Biſhop <hi>Sanderſon</hi> and others—1671</item>
               <item>535 Dr. <hi>Wil. T<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>iſs</hi> his Morality of the <hi>4th</hi> Commandment to bind <hi>Chriſtians</hi>—1641</item>
               <item>536 <hi>Jo. Cruſo</hi>'s Caſtramet<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>tion, or the meaſuring out of Quarters for encamping an Army</item>
               <item>537 <hi>R. Shelden</hi>'s motives of his Converſion from Papiſtry, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—wants Title —</item>
               <item>538 Dr. <hi>Jo. Preſton</hi>'s Works, <hi>viz.</hi> on the new Covenant: of the divine Attributes: of Prayer: Breaſt-plate of Faith, and Love: The Saints Qualifications: The Golden Scepter: Court Sermons: a Liveleſs Life: a Sermon: of Mortification: 4 Godly and Learned Treatiſes: and his Remains: 4 Vol. —</item>
               <item>539 Dr. Tho. <hi>Manton</hi>'s Commentary with expoſition on <hi>Jude</hi>— 1658</item>
               <item>540 <hi>Jo. Acoſta</hi>'s natural and moral Hiſtory of the <hi>Indies</hi> — wants Title —</item>
               <item>541 <hi>Th. Godwin</hi>'s Romiſh and Jewiſh, and <hi>Rouſe</hi>'s Attick Antiquities; compleat—1655</item>
               <item>542 The Paſſenger of <hi>Benvenuto Italiano,</hi> Italian and Engliſh — 1612</item>
               <item>543 <hi>Jer. Burrough</hi>'s Evil of Evils, or the exceeding Sinfulneſs of Sin —1654</item>
               <item>544 <hi>Langham</hi>'s Garden of Health in the hidden Virtues of all Simples, Plants, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>545 <hi>Jef. Wats</hi> his Vindication of the Church and Univerſities of England —</item>
            </list>
         </div>
         <div type="catalogue">
            <pb n="17" facs="tcp:42676:10"/>
            <head>Divinity, Hiſtory, Phyſick, Miſcellanies, in <hi>Octavo.</hi>
            </head>
            <list>
               <item>1 BIſhop <hi>Jer. Taylor</hi>'s Collection of Offices, or Forms of Prayer: Guilt and Let. 1658</item>
               <item>2 Dr. <hi>Ed. Stillingfleet's</hi> diſcourſe concerning Idolatry — 1672</item>
               <item>3 —his Conference between a Romiſh Prieſt, Fanat. Chapl. <hi>&amp;c.</hi> of Idolatry 1679</item>
               <item>4 Dr. <hi>Dan. Featly</hi>'s Handmaid to devotion: <hi>9th</hi> Edition — 1675</item>
               <item>5 Lord <hi>Hales</hi> his Contemplations Divine and Moral; both parts compleat — 1685</item>
               <item>6 Dr. <hi>Bate</hi>'s Hiſtorical Account of the late Troubles of <hi>England, &amp;c.</hi> — 1685</item>
               <item>7 Lively Oracles given unto us by the Author of the whole Duty of Man—1678</item>
               <item>8 New Teſtament in Engliſh, in a large Octavo, with Cuts —1679</item>
               <item>9 <hi>Nic. Culpepper's London Diſpenſatory,</hi> Adorned, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> —1680</item>
               <item>10 New Light to Alchymy, with a Chymical Dictionary, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1674</item>
               <item>11 Book of Pſalms collected into Engliſh Metre, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1684</item>
               <item>12 <hi>Tho. Brook's</hi> Remedies againſt <hi>Satan</hi>'s devices— 1676</item>
               <item>13 Biſhop <hi>Davenant</hi> againſt <hi>Hoard's</hi> Gods Love to Mankind — 1641</item>
               <item>14 <hi>Plutarch</hi>'s Lives of the Noble <hi>Greeks</hi> and <hi>Romans</hi> abridg'd: with other Lives. 1665</item>
               <item>15 Divine Dialogues concerning the Attributes and Providence of God, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> —1668</item>
               <item>16 <hi>Tho. Watſon</hi>'s Beatitudes, on Chriſts Sermon in the Mount —1671</item>
               <item>17 <hi>Jo. How</hi>'s Bleſſedneſs of the Righteous, on Pſalm 17.15 — 1668</item>
               <item>18 Hiſtory of <hi>Peter d'Aubuſſon,</hi> and the <hi>Turkiſh</hi> War, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1683</item>
               <item>19 <hi>Polhil</hi>'s Anſwer to a diſcourſe of Mr. <hi>Sherlock</hi>'s, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1675</item>
               <item>20 —his precious Faith conſidered, in its Nature, working, and Growth—1657</item>
               <item>21 <hi>Tho. Ellis</hi> his Kingdom of God opened and improved — 1678</item>
               <item>22 Lord <hi>Hale</hi>'s Obſervations on the Principles of Natural Motion—1677</item>
               <item>23 Life and Death of Mr. <hi>Joſ. Al<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>eine:</hi> with his Letters, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1672</item>
               <item>24 <hi>Jo. Faldo's</hi> Quakeriſm no Chriſtianity; recommended by many Divines —1675</item>
               <item>25 Dr. <hi>Patrick</hi>'s <hi>Menſa myſtica:</hi> on the Sacrament of the Lords Supper —1667</item>
               <item>26 <hi>R. Wicken</hi>'s compleat and perfect Concordance of the Engliſh Bible— 1655</item>
               <item>27 <hi>Fr. Robert's</hi> Key of the Bible, unlocking the Richeſt Treaſury of Scriptures, 2 Vol.</item>
               <item>28 Lord <hi>Hale</hi>'s <hi>Difficiles nugae:</hi> Obſervations touching the <hi>Torricellian</hi> Experiment 1675</item>
               <item>29 Dr. <hi>Tho. Jacomb</hi>'s Treatiſe of Holy Dedication, Perſonal and Domeſtick —1668</item>
               <item>30 <hi>Pet. Gaſſendus</hi> his Life of <hi>Nic. Cl. Piereskius;</hi> Engliſhed by Dr. <hi>Rand</hi>— 1657</item>
               <item>31 Dr. <hi>Stillingfleet's</hi> Conferences betwixt a Romiſh Prieſt, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> about Idolatry 1679</item>
               <item>32 Dr. <hi>Mart. Luther's</hi> 34 choſen Sermons, Engliſhed by <hi>Will Gace</hi>—1649</item>
               <item>33 <hi>Ja. Nalton</hi>'s 20 Sermons upon ſeveral Texts — 1649</item>
               <item>34 <hi>Will. Greenhil's</hi> Treatiſe of ſoundneſs of heart, with other Sermons — 1670</item>
               <item>35 <hi>Will. Barton</hi>'s Book of Pſalms in Metre — 1682</item>
               <item>36 <hi>Andr. Moor</hi>'s Compendious Hiſtory of the <hi>Turks</hi> — 1663</item>
               <item>37 <hi>Ed. Leigh's</hi> ſelect obſervations on the Twelve <hi>Caeſars</hi> —1670</item>
               <item>38 <hi>Jo. Smith</hi>'s Myſtery of Rhetorick unvail'd — 1657</item>
               <item>39 Young Clerks Guide in 4 parts; a Collection of Engliſh Preſidents— 1673</item>
               <item>40 <hi>Hugh</hi>'s Abridgement of Sir <hi>Fr. More</hi>'s Reports. Engliſh — 1665</item>
               <item>41 <hi>Fidel's</hi> Guide for a ſtudious young Lawyer, in Preſidents for Conveyances — 1658</item>
               <item>42 <hi>Will. Shepheard's</hi> ſure Guide for his Majeſties Juſtices of Peace—1669</item>
               <item>43 —his Actions upon the Caſe for ſlander; <hi>2d</hi> Edition — 1674</item>
               <item>44 —his Actions upon the Caſe for Deeds, out of many great Volumes of the Law</item>
               <item>45 Principles and Practices of moderate Divines abuſively called <hi>Latitudinarians</hi>—1671</item>
               <item>46 Dr. <hi>Will. Harvy</hi>'s Anatomical Exerciſes of the Heart and Blood — 1673</item>
               <item>47 <hi>Machiavel's</hi> Diſcourſes upon T. <hi>Livius,</hi> with his Prince, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1674</item>
               <pb n="18" facs="tcp:42676:11"/>
               <item>48 Renunciation of ſeveral Doctrines contrary to the Church of <hi>England</hi> — 1680</item>
               <item>49 Examination of <hi>Tilenus</hi> in <hi>Eutopia</hi> before the <hi>Triers</hi> —1658</item>
               <item>50 <hi>Geo. Herbert's</hi> Prieſt to the Temple, or the Country Parſon—1675</item>
               <item>51 <hi>Hoard</hi>'s God Love to Mankind, and Souls Miſery and Recovery—1658</item>
               <item>52 <hi>Baſil. Valentine's</hi> Triumphant Chariot of Antimony with Figures — 1678</item>
               <item>53 <hi>Jer. Dyke's</hi> worthy Communicant, a Treatiſe of the Lords Supper — 1636</item>
               <item>54 <hi>Joſ. Symona's</hi> Caſe and Cure of a deſerted Soul —1639</item>
               <item>55 <hi>Nicremberge</hi>'s Treatiſe of the difference betwixt Temporal and Eternal—1672</item>
               <item>56 <hi>J.</hi> F. <hi>Senault</hi>'s uſe of the Paſſions, Engliſhed out of <hi>French</hi> —1671</item>
               <item>57 Book of the Common Prayer, New Teſtament, and Pſalms, large letter—1680</item>
               <item>58 <hi>Baſ. Valentine</hi>'s laſt Will and Teſtament, with his 2 Treatiſes — 1670</item>
               <item>59 S. <hi>Partridges</hi> Deſcription of an Inſtrument called the double Scale of Proportion 1661</item>
               <item>60 <hi>Cl. Mauger's</hi> French Grammar, French and Engliſh: 5th Edition— 1667</item>
               <item>61 Dr. <hi>South</hi>'s Sermons upon ſeveral Occaſion — <hi>Oxford</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>62 <hi>Benj. Baxter</hi> concerning the making a Judgement of Temporal Conditions —1669</item>
               <item>63 <hi>Cl. A<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>lianus</hi> his various Hiſtory tranſlated out of <hi>Greek</hi>—1665</item>
               <item>64 <hi>Rich. Garpenter</hi>'s Experience, Hiſtory, and Divinity, in 5 Books — 1642</item>
               <item>65 <hi>Evelyn</hi>'s Navigation and Commerce, their Original and Progreſs—167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>66 <hi>P. Barbette's</hi> Chyrurgical and Anatomical Works, with Figures—1676</item>
               <item>67 Sir <hi>Geo. <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>harton</hi>'s Works collected into one Volume by <hi>Jo. Gadbury</hi>—168<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>68 <hi>Al. Brome</hi>'s Poems and other Songs: <hi>3d</hi> Edition —1668</item>
               <item>69 <hi>Jo. Smith</hi>'s Inſtructions for the French, Italian, Spaniſh and Engliſh Tongues—167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>70 <hi>Sam. Rolle</hi>'s burning of <hi>London</hi> Commemorated in a hundred diſcourſes, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—166<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>71 —his <hi>London</hi>'s Reſurrection, or Rebuilding encouraged, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1668</item>
               <item>72 <hi>Zack C<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ke's</hi> Art of Logick, the entire Body thereof, in Engliſh— 165<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>73 Dr. <hi>du Viel</hi>'s Literal Explanation of the Acts of the Apoſtles— 168<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>74 Dr. <hi>Patrick</hi>'s divine Arithmetick; or the right Art of numbring our days — 167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>75 <hi>May's</hi> Hiſtory of the Reign of King <hi>Edward</hi> the <hi>3d</hi> in Engliſh Verſe, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 163<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>76 Dr. <hi>Reg. de Graaſ's</hi> Treatiſe of Pancreatick Juice, with Figures—167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>77 Fellow Traveller, furniſhed with ſhort Stories, choice Speeches, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 165<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>78 <hi>Ed. Leigh</hi>'s Treatiſe of the divine Promiſes, in 5 Books; <hi>3d</hi> Edition — 165<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>79 <hi>Mat. Pool</hi>'s Dialogue between a Popiſh Prieſt and an EngliſhProteſtant — 166<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>80 <hi>N<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>m<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ſi<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>
                  </hi> the Philoſopher of the Nature of Man, Engliſh out of Greek —163<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>81 Dr. <hi>Tho. Bruge's <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>a<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>e <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>cum;</hi> or a Companion for a Chyrurgion —165<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>82 <hi>Parker</hi>'s diſcourſe of Eccleſiaſtical Polity, and of Toleration —167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>83 Mock <hi>Cl<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>lia,</hi> a Comical Hiſtory in Imitation of <hi>Don Quixot</hi>— 167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>84 <hi>Aeſ<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>p</hi> Improved, <hi>viz.</hi> his Fables, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> in Engliſh Verſe —167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>85 <hi>Planter</hi>'s Manual; Inſtructions for Raiſing, Planting, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> of Fruit-Trees — 167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>86 <hi>Al. Roſs</hi> his View of the <hi>Jewiſh</hi> Religion, their manner of Life, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> —165<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>87 <hi>P. Thibaul</hi>'s Art of Chymiſtry; as it is now practiſed — 167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>88 Archibiſhop <hi>Uſher</hi>'s Judgement, of the extent of <hi>Chriſt</hi>'s Death <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—165<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>89 Hiſtory of <hi>Juſtin,</hi> Engliſhed by <hi>Rob. Codrington; 4th</hi> Edition— 168<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>90 Dr. <hi>Goore</hi>'s Expoſition of the difficult Texts of the Bible—168<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>91 <hi>Blome</hi>'s deſcription of <hi>Jamaica, Barbados, &amp;c.</hi> with Maps—167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>92 Dr. <hi>Simpſon</hi>'s Philoſophical diſcourſe of Fermentation — 16<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>93 <hi>Tho. Gobbet</hi>'s practical diſcourſe of Prayer —165<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>94 Dr. <hi>Tho. Sherley</hi>'s Curioſities of Scurvy-graſs, with Figures, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> —167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>95 Dr. <hi>Tho. Manton</hi>'s practical expoſition of the Lords Prayer — 168<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>96 <hi>Bulter</hi>'s account of the Year, Month, day, and Minute of the Birth of Chriſt— 167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>97 The Right of Tythes Re-aſſerted and Vindicated, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 168<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <pb n="19" facs="tcp:42676:11"/>
               <item>98 <hi>Secker</hi>'s Nonſuch Profeſſor in his Meridian Splendour — 1660</item>
               <item>99 View of the Empires, Kingdoms, Principalities, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> of <hi>Europe</hi>—1669</item>
               <item>100 <hi>Evelin</hi>'s Navigation and Commerce, their Original and Progreſs — 1674</item>
               <item>101 <hi>Will. L<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>yl<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>urn</hi>'s Arithmetick, Vulgar, Decimal, Inſtrumental, Algebraical —</item>
               <item>102 <hi>Dela Maine</hi>'s deſcription, and uſe of the Horizontal Quadrant— 1631</item>
               <item>103 <hi>Guidot</hi>'s diſcourſe of <hi>Bathe,</hi> and the hot Waters, with a Map, &amp; Fig. of <hi>Rom.</hi> Antiq.</item>
               <item>104 W. <hi>Si<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>pſ<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>
                  </hi>'s Anatomy of <hi>Scarbrough</hi> Spaws in <hi>Yorkſhire,</hi> with Figures—1669</item>
               <item>105 The Compleat Sollicitor performing his duty, <hi>&amp;c. 4th</hi> Edition — 1672</item>
               <item>106 Compleat Attorney, or the Practick part of the Law — 1666</item>
               <item>107 <hi>H<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>h</hi>'s Parſon's Law, or a view of Advowſons; <hi>3d</hi> Edition — 1673</item>
               <item>108 <hi>Cl. Mauger</hi>'s French Grammar; and new Dialogues; <hi>6th</hi> Edition—1670</item>
               <item>109 <hi>P. de Lai<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>
                  </hi>'s French Grammar, for the uſe of the Princeſſes of <hi>Orange</hi> &amp; <hi>Denmark</hi>
               </item>
               <item>110 Buckler of State and Juſtice, againſt the French Deſign of Univerſal Monarchy 1673</item>
               <item>111 Practick part of the Law, or the compleat Attorney— 1666</item>
               <item>112 Vindication of the Primitive Church, and of Epiſcopacy, in anſwer to Mr. <hi>Baxter</hi>
               </item>
               <item>113 The Mirror of Fortune, or the true Characters of Fate and Deſtiny — 1676</item>
               <item>114 Choice Pieces of that renowned Antiquary Sir <hi>Rob. Cotton, &amp;c.</hi>— 1679</item>
               <item>115 <hi>Geo. Meriton</hi>'s <hi>Anglorum geſta,</hi> or an Hiſtory of <hi>England</hi>—1678</item>
               <item>116 <hi>Jo. Clieveland</hi>'s Poems, Orations, Epiſtles, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—1677</item>
               <item>117 <hi>Mynſicht</hi>'s Treaſury of Phyſick, Engliſhed by <hi>Jo. Partridge</hi>— 1682</item>
               <item>118 <hi>Rabiſha</hi>'s whole Body of Cookery diſſected; <hi>2d</hi> Edition — 1675</item>
               <item>119 Reduction of <hi>Ireland</hi> to the Crown of <hi>England,</hi> and of the Maſſacre in 1641—</item>
               <item>120 Dr. <hi>Wettenhal</hi>'s Giſt of Prayer, Singing, Preaching, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— <hi>Dublin</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>121 <hi>Pet. Morellus</hi> Expert Doctors Diſpenſatory; Engliſhed by <hi>Gulpepper</hi> — 1657</item>
               <item>122 <hi>Glaſer's</hi> compleat Chymiſt, a new Treatiſe of Chymiſtry, with Copper Plates 1677</item>
               <item>123 Dr. <hi>Ever. Maynwaring</hi>'s Treatiſe of the Scurvy, <hi>4th</hi> Edition—1672</item>
               <item>124 Sir <hi>Jon. Moor</hi> of Artillery, or great Ordinance, with Figures—1683</item>
               <item>125 <hi>Bohun</hi>'s diſcourſe of the origine and properties of Wind—1671</item>
               <item>126 New Politick Lights, or modern <hi>Rome's</hi> Government — 1678</item>
               <item>127 <hi>R. Mayhews</hi> death of death in the death of Chriſt —1679</item>
               <item>128 <hi>Will. Rabiſha</hi>'s whole Body of Cookery diſſected —1682</item>
               <item>129 <hi>R. Steel</hi>'s Husbandmans Calling, in 12 Sermons; <hi>2d</hi> Edition— 1672</item>
               <item>130 <hi>Tho. Vincent</hi>'s Chriſts certain and ſudden Appearance to Judgement— 1683</item>
               <item>131 <hi>Bauthumley</hi>'s Relation of the moſt material Paſſages and Perſecutions of the Church</item>
               <item>132 <hi>Jo. Partridge's</hi> Treaſury of Phyſick, and Remedies againſt all Diſeaſes — 1682</item>
               <item>133 <hi>White</hi>'s perpatetical Inſtitutions, and Appendix of the Beginning of the World</item>
               <item>134 New Teſtament, tranſlated out of Greek, with <hi>Beza</hi>'s Notes, and an Appendix, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>135 Hiſtory of the Grand Viſiers, of the 3 laſt Grand Seigniors, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1677</item>
               <item>136 Captain <hi>Sharp</hi>'s Voyages in the South Sea, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 16<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>4</item>
               <item>137 <hi>Jo. Smith</hi>'s Myſtery of Rhetorick unveil'd— 1663</item>
               <item>138 <hi>Dr. Jo. Owen</hi>'s diſcourſe of the Work of the Holy Spirit in Prayer — 1682</item>
               <item>139 <hi>Phil. Goodwin</hi>'s Family Religion revived—wants Title —</item>
               <item>140 <hi>Squire</hi>'s unreaſonableneſs of the Romaniſts requiring our Communion— 1670</item>
               <item>141 <hi>Fr. Craven</hi>'s <hi>Eternalia:</hi> upon <hi>John</hi> 6.27.— 1677</item>
               <item>142 <hi>Tho. Brook's</hi> precious Remedies againſt <hi>Satan</hi>'s Devices—1661</item>
               <item>143 <hi>Nic. Machiav<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>l</hi>'s diſcourſes upon the firſt decade of <hi>Titus Livius</hi>—1636</item>
               <item>144 M. <hi>Needham's medela medicinae,</hi> a Plea for the free profeſſion of Phyſick — 1665</item>
               <item>145 Dr. <hi>Whitlo<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>k</hi>'s Obſervations on the preſent mannners of the Engliſh— 1654</item>
               <item>146 <hi>Bayfield</hi>'s Treatiſe, <hi>de <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 word">
                        <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                     </gap> his Capitis,</hi> of the Diſeaſes of the Head—1663</item>
               <item>147 <hi>Zayde,</hi> a Spaniſh Hiſtory, a pleaſant and witty Novel—1678</item>
               <pb n="20" facs="tcp:42676:12"/>
               <item>148 <hi>Fragmenta Prophetica,</hi> or the Remains of <hi>George Wither,</hi> Eſquire— 1669</item>
               <item>149 <hi>Jo. Bunyan's</hi> Holy War, made by <hi>Shaddai</hi> upon <hi>Diabolus, &amp;c.</hi>— 1682</item>
               <item>150 New Survey of the <hi>Turkiſh</hi> Empire, Hiſtory, and Government, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> —1664</item>
               <item>151 <hi>Brown</hi>'s Apothecary's Proſody — <hi>London</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>152 <hi>Zach. Bogan</hi>'s help to Prayer and Meditation —1660</item>
               <item>153 <hi>Cl. Elianus</hi> his various Hiſtory, Engliſhed from the Greek by <hi>Tho. Stanly</hi> —1665</item>
               <item>154 Dr. <hi>du Moulin</hi>'s Treatiſe of Peace and Contentment of Mind; <hi>3d</hi> Edition — 1679</item>
               <item>155 <hi>R. Broughton</hi>'s memorial of the Ancient, and moſt Holy State of <hi>Great Brittain</hi> 1650</item>
               <item>156 Sir <hi>Tho. Killigrew</hi>'s 3 Plays. <hi>viz. Selindra, Pandora, Ormaſdes</hi> — 1665</item>
               <item>157 <hi>Leybourn</hi>'s Arithmetick, Vulgar, Decimal, Inſtrumental, Algebraical— 1678</item>
               <item>158 <hi>Villier</hi>'s Engliſhman ſpeaking <hi>French,</hi> and the Frenchman ſpeaking <hi>Engliſh</hi>—1680</item>
               <item>159 <hi>Joſ. Symond</hi>'s Caſe and Cure of a deſerted Soul — 1629</item>
               <item>160 <hi>Pettit</hi>'s Viſions of Government, confuting Antimonarchical Principles, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> —1684</item>
               <item>161 <hi>Th. Heywood</hi>'s general Hiſtory of Women, of the moſt Holy and moſt Profane 1657</item>
               <item>162 <hi>Lithgow</hi>'s 19 years Travels through the moſt eminent places of the World—1682</item>
               <item>163 <hi>Ed. Calamy</hi>'s Evidence for Heaven; infallible Signs of Salvation—1657</item>
               <item>164 <hi>Loyd</hi>'s Pourtraicture of King <hi>Charles</hi> the II. — 1660</item>
               <item>165 <hi>Blome</hi>'s deſcription of <hi>Jamaica,</hi> and the Engliſh Territorys in <hi>America,</hi> with Maps, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>166 P. <hi>Thibaut</hi>'s Art of Chymiſtry, as it is now practiſed— 1668</item>
               <item>167 Whole Duty of Man, <hi>2d</hi> part — 1683</item>
               <item>168 <hi>Eutrophius</hi>'s Breviary of the Roman Hiſtory, Engliſhed by divers hands— 1684</item>
               <item>169 <hi>Lawrence</hi>'s Intereſt of <hi>Ireland</hi> in its Trade and Wealth ſtated— 1682</item>
               <item>170 <hi>Hen. Gellibrand</hi>'s Epitomy of Navigation—1680</item>
               <item>171 Dr. <hi>Fowler</hi>'s deſign of Chriſtianity, and our Saviours coming into the World 1671</item>
               <item>172 Biſhop <hi>Hall</hi>'s Inviſible World diſcovered to the Spiritual Eye — 1659</item>
               <item>173 <hi>Robinſon</hi>'s Chriſt all in all, of the Similitudes whereby Chriſt is deſcribed in Script.</item>
               <item>174 <hi>Al. Ross</hi> his <hi>Arcana Microcoſmi;</hi> the hid Secrets of Mans Body—1652</item>
               <item>175 <hi>Jo. Howe</hi>'s Redeemers Tears over loſt Sinners: and of the Sin againſt the H. Ghoſt</item>
               <item>176 Secretary in Faſhion; a compendious way of Writing Letters —1658</item>
               <item>177 <hi>Jer. Dyke</hi>'s worthy Communicant: a Treatiſe of the Sacrament —1657</item>
               <item>178 <hi>Cleopatra,</hi> the Eighth part, a new Romance —1658</item>
               <item>179 <hi>Leigh</hi>'s ſelect Obſervations on all the <hi>Roman</hi> Emperors—1664</item>
               <item>180 <hi>Parſon</hi> the Jeſuite his <hi>3d</hi> and <hi>4th</hi> part of his Treatiſe of the 3 Converſions of <hi>England</hi> in an examination of <hi>Fox</hi>'s Calendar Saints —</item>
               <item>181 Dr. <hi>Parker</hi>'s Reproof of <hi>Marvel</hi>'s Rehearſal tranſproſed — 1673</item>
               <item>182 <hi>Rome</hi>'s Conviction, or a Vindication of the Original Inſtitution of Chriſtianity 1683</item>
               <item>183 <hi>Steph. Charnock</hi>'s diſcourſe of Divine Providence —1684</item>
               <item>184 Dr. <hi>Bate</hi>'s Sermons upon death, and Eternal Judgement —1683</item>
               <item>185 Dr. <hi>du Moulins</hi> Treatiſe of Peace and Contentment of the Mind —1657</item>
               <item>186 <hi>Meriton</hi>'s <hi>Anglorum geſta,</hi> or the hiſtory of <hi>England</hi>—1670</item>
               <item>187 Annals of Love in the Amours of divers Princes Courts—1672</item>
               <item>188 <hi>Rich. Saunder</hi>'s Aſtrological Judgement and Practiſe of Phyſick — 1677</item>
               <item>189 <hi>Record</hi>'s Arithmetick, or the grounds of Art, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> wants Title—</item>
               <item>190 <hi>Val. Maximus</hi> his View of the Religion, Laws, Cuſtoms, Manners, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> of the <hi>Romans</hi>
               </item>
               <item>191 Diſcourſe of Auxiliary Beauty, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> in point of Conſcience between two Ladys 1656</item>
               <item>192 <hi>Hue's</hi> Learned Treatiſe of the Globes, Engliſhed by <hi>chilmead</hi> — 1639</item>
               <item>193 Biſhop <hi>Hall's</hi> Honor of the marryed Clergy maintain'd— 1620</item>
               <item>194 <hi>Blount's Goſſographia,</hi> or a Dictionary Interpreting hard Engliſh words—1656</item>
               <item>195 Dr. <hi>Gid. Harvey</hi>'s Great <hi>Venus</hi> unmaskt, of the Pox — 1672</item>
               <item>196 Dr. <hi>E. Maynwaring</hi>'s preſervation of Health and prolongation of Life —1669</item>
               <pb n="21" facs="tcp:42676:12"/>
               <item>197 <hi>Nieremberge</hi>'s difference betwixt Temporal and Eternal— 1672</item>
               <item>198 Diſcourſe of Church Unity in defence of Dr. <hi>Stillingfleet</hi> —1681</item>
               <item>199 Dr. <hi>Bury</hi>'s conſtant Communicant, of Conſtancy in receiving the Sacrament 1681</item>
               <item>200 <hi>Janeway's</hi> Heaven upon Earth, the beſt Friend in the worſt of Times — 1671</item>
               <item>201 <hi>Lovel's Indiculus Univerſalis;</hi> the Univerſe in Epitomy— 1679</item>
               <item>202 <hi>Quarle's</hi> Triumphant Chaſtity in a diſpute betwixt <hi>Joſeph</hi> and his Miſtreſs—</item>
               <item>203 <hi>J. Evelyn</hi>'s Navigation and Commerce, their Original and Progreſs—1674</item>
               <item>204 <hi>Baſ. Valentine's</hi> Triumphant Chariot of Antimony, with Figues, <hi>&amp;.</hi> — 1678</item>
               <item>205 Hiſtory of Feavers, with a deſcription of the Spleen and Pancreas— 1674</item>
               <item>206 The unfortunate Heroes, or the Adventures of 10 fam'd Men—1679</item>
               <item>207 A Boulſter Lecture: Art aſleep Husband: Witty Jeſts, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—1640</item>
               <item>208 <hi>W<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>lgrave</hi>'s whole Art of decimal Arithmetick: and Eſſay of Gunnery, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> Fig.</item>
               <item>209 <hi>
                     <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>a<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>ſha</hi>'s whole body of Cookery diſſected, taught, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1682</item>
               <item>210 Dr. <hi>Mor<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>
                  </hi>'s conjectural Eſſay of a threefold <hi>Cabbala</hi> — 1653</item>
               <item>211 Dr. <hi>Stillingſteet</hi>'s conferences betwixt a <hi>Romiſh</hi> Prieſt and a Divine touching Idolatry</item>
               <item>212 <hi>Tho. Collier</hi>'s Body of Divinity, or Confeſſion of Faith — 1674</item>
               <item>213 Dr. <hi>Tim. Puller</hi>'s moderation of the Church of <hi>England</hi> — 1679</item>
               <item>214 <hi>Tho. Ravenſcroft</hi>'s whole Book of Pſalms, with ſeveral Tunes— 1672</item>
               <item>215 Dr. <hi>Patrick</hi>'s Friendly debate betwixt a Conformiſt and a Nonconformiſt—1669</item>
               <item>216 <hi>E<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>. Reyner</hi>'s Precept for Chriſtian Practice; or the Rule of the N. Creature 1662</item>
               <item>217 Dr. <hi>Mart. Luther's</hi> 34 ſpecial and choſen Sermons—1649</item>
               <item>218 <hi>Tho. Brightman</hi>'s Revelation of St. <hi>John</hi> Illuſtrated—<hi>Leyden</hi> 1616</item>
               <item>219 <hi>Dies Dominica,</hi> or the Lords day; a ſucinct Narration thereof—1672</item>
               <item>220 <hi>Rob. Sharrocks</hi> Hiſtory of the Propagation and Improvement of Vegetables 1672</item>
               <item>221 <hi>Cl. Mauger</hi>'s Letters in <hi>French a<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap> Engliſh</hi> on divers Subjects— 1671</item>
               <item>222 Sport upon Sport in ſelected pieces of drollery—1672</item>
               <item>223 <hi>Sherburn's Medea,</hi> a Tragedy, Engliſhed out of <hi>Seneca,</hi> with Annotations — 1648</item>
               <item>224 <hi>H. C. de Luzanci</hi>'s Reflexions on the Council of <hi>Trent</hi> —1672</item>
               <item>225 <hi>Kirkman</hi>'s unlucky Citizen with Figures — 1673</item>
               <item>226 <hi>Leigh</hi>'s <hi>England</hi> deſcribed in the ſeveral Countys and Shires thereof — 1659</item>
               <item>227 <hi>Moſ. Amyraldus</hi> his diſcourſe concerning the divine Dreams in Scripture —1676</item>
               <item>228 Dr. <hi>Tho. Simpſon</hi>'s true way of preſerving the Blood, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> —1670</item>
               <item>229 <hi>Ed. Calamy</hi>'s Art of divine Meditation — 1670</item>
               <item>230 <hi>Nat. Ranews</hi> ſolitude improved by divine meditation — 1670</item>
               <item>231 <hi>Tillinghaſt</hi>'s knowledge of the Times, how long it ſhall be to the end of Wonder,</item>
               <item>232 <hi>Blount</hi>'s <hi>Gloſſographia;</hi> a Dictionary interpreting of hard Engliſh Words— 1656</item>
               <item>233 <hi>Ed. Waterhouſe</hi>'s humble Apology for Learning and Learned Men — 1653</item>
               <item>234 <hi>Dud. Digg's</hi> unlawfulneſs of Subjects taking up Arms — 1664</item>
               <item>235 <hi>Commelyn's</hi> management, ordering and uſe of the Lemmon and Orange-Trees 1683</item>
               <item>236 <hi>Silvius de le Boe's</hi> Jdea of the Practice of Phyſick; with Dr. <hi>Needham's</hi> Preface 1675</item>
               <item>237 Compleat Midwives Practice enlarged, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> with Figures —1663</item>
               <item>238 <hi>Jo. Beguinus</hi> his Chymical Eſſays from the Fountain of Nature— 1669</item>
               <item>239 Dr. <hi>Will. Marſhal's</hi> Reſolutions of divers knotty Queſtions in Philoſophy—1678</item>
               <item>240 <hi>Jo. Gadbury</hi>'s Aſtrological Treaſury relating to Phyſick — 1674</item>
               <item>241 Hiſtory of Cardinal <hi>de Richelieus,</hi> French Academy erected at <hi>Paris</hi>— 1657</item>
               <item>242 <hi>Mat. Mead</hi>'s Good of early Obedience, and bearing Chriſts Yoke betimes—1683</item>
               <item>243 <hi>Chr. Sympſon</hi>'s Compendium of practical Muſick, in 5 parts —1667</item>
               <item>244 <hi>R. Hawkin</hi>'s diſcourſe of the National Excellencies of <hi>England</hi>— 1658</item>
               <item>245 <hi>Ovid</hi>'s Heroical Epiſtles in Engliſh, with Figures — 1677</item>
               <item>246 Dr: <hi>Nehem Grew</hi>'s Anatomy of Vegetables, with Figures—1672</item>
               <pb facs="tcp:42676:13"/>
               <item>247 <hi>Bohun</hi> concerning the Origine and Properties of Wind — 1671</item>
               <item>248 The Wits, or ſport upon ſport; curious Drolls, Faces, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—</item>
               <item>249 Deſcription of the Iſland of <hi>Jamaica,</hi> with the Engliſh Territorys in <hi>America,</hi> Maps</item>
               <item>250 <hi>Aleyn</hi>'s Hiſtory of King <hi>Henry</hi> the <hi>7th</hi> of <hi>England</hi> in Verſe — 1638</item>
               <item>251 <hi>Ed. Wingate</hi>'s exact Abridgement of all the Statutes in force—1655</item>
               <item>252 Biſhop Saint <hi>David</hi>'s Apology for the Church of <hi>England</hi> in point of ſeparation 1658</item>
               <item>253 Hiſtorical Memoirs on the Reigns of Q. <hi>Elizabeth</hi> and King <hi>James</hi> — 1658</item>
               <item>254 Dr. <hi>Jo. Newton's</hi> Scale of Intereſt; or the uſe of Decimal Fractions—1668</item>
               <item>255 <hi>Dan. Bartolus</hi> his Learned Man, defended and Reformed —</item>
               <item>256 <hi>Webb</hi>'s Antiquity of <hi>China,</hi> in an Eſſay of its Language, being the Primitive 1678</item>
               <item>257 <hi>Evelyn's</hi> Navigation and Commerce, their Original and Progreſs— 1674</item>
               <item>258 <hi>R. Rapin</hi>'s Reflexions on <hi>Ariſtotles</hi> Treatiſe of Poeſie— 1674</item>
               <item>259 Dr. <hi>Grew</hi>'s Idea of a Phytological Hiſtory of Roots, with Figures —1673</item>
               <item>260 <hi>Newton</hi>'s <hi>Coſmographia,</hi> a View of the Globes Terreſtrial, and Celeſtial— 1679</item>
               <item>261 <hi>May</hi>'s Victorious Reign of King <hi>Edward</hi> the <hi>3d.</hi> in Engliſh Verſe —1655</item>
               <item>162 <hi>Ja. Howel</hi>'s <hi>Dodona</hi>'s Grove, or the Vocal Forreſt, <hi>2d</hi> part — 1650</item>
               <item>263 <hi>R. Rapinus</hi> of <hi>Garden's</hi> 4 Books, Engliſhed into Verſe by <hi>Evelyn</hi> —1673</item>
               <item>164 <hi>Procopius</hi> his ſecret Hiſtory of the Court of the Emperor <hi>Juſtinian</hi> — 1674</item>
               <item>265 Practick part of the Law; or the compleat Attorney — 1654</item>
               <item>266 <hi>Al. Roſs</hi> his <hi>Myſtagogus Poeticus,</hi> or the Muſes Interpreter —1648</item>
               <item>267 <hi>Zach. Coke</hi>'s Art of Logick; an intire Body thereof in <hi>Engliſh</hi> —1654</item>
               <item>268 <hi>Rich. Laſſel</hi>'s Voyage of <hi>Italy</hi> in 2 parts — 1670</item>
               <item>269 Sir <hi>Jo. Suckling</hi>'s Poems and incomparable Pieces — 1648</item>
               <item>270 <hi>Rob. Baron</hi>'s <hi>Cyprian Academy</hi>—1648</item>
               <item>271 <hi>Rob. Bo<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>le</hi>'s Eſſay about the Origine and Vertues of Gems — 1672</item>
               <item>272 Memoirs of the Duke of <hi>Roa,</hi> and Occurre<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>es of <hi>France</hi> — 1660</item>
               <item>273 <hi>Doolittle</hi>'s Young Man's Inſtructer, and the Old Man's Remembrancer—1673</item>
               <item>274 <hi>Sandy</hi>'s <hi>Ovid Metamorphoſis</hi> in Engliſh Verſe— wants Title —</item>
               <item>275 Modern Curioſities of Art and Nature. by <hi>Lemery:</hi> Engliſhed out of French 1685</item>
               <item>376 <hi>Stockton</hi>'s Counſel to the Afflicted, who ſuffered by Fire— 1666</item>
               <item>277 Academy of Complements, with new Additions of Songs— 1680</item>
               <item>278 Sir <hi>Tho. Ireland</hi>'s exact Abridgement of <hi>Cook</hi>'s Reorts—1650</item>
               <item>279 Dr. <hi>Hinckley's</hi> Letters on ſeveral Occaſions betwixt him and Mr. <hi>Baxter</hi> —1680</item>
               <item>280 <hi>Seargeant</hi>'s Faith Vindicated from the Poſſibility of Falſhood—1667</item>
               <item>281 Dr. <hi>Mart. Luther</hi>'s 34 ſpecial and choſen Sermons —1649</item>
               <item>282 <hi>Bun<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>an</hi>'s Holy War, made by <hi>Shaddai</hi> upon <hi>Diabolus, &amp;c.</hi> — 1682</item>
               <item>283 <hi>Chilm<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ad</hi>'s Treatiſe of the Globes Terreſtrial and Celeſtial— 1639</item>
               <item>284 <hi>England</hi>'s <hi>Parnaſſus,</hi> or the choiceſt Flowers of our Modern Poets—1600</item>
               <item>285 Dr. <hi>Tho. B<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ugis Vade mecum;</hi> or a Companion of a Chyrurgion — 1679</item>
               <item>286 Epitomy of the whole Art of Husbandry, with new Additions—1670</item>
               <item>287 <hi>Chr. Neſs</hi> his Compleat and Compendious Church Hiſtory; <hi>3d</hi> Edition— 1681</item>
               <item>288 <hi>America,</hi> or an exact deſcription of the Weſt Indies, with a Map — 1655</item>
               <item>289 <hi>Blount</hi>'s <hi>Horae ſubſecivae,</hi> Obſervations and Diſcourſes, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1620</item>
               <item>290 Diſcourſe concerning the Beauty of Holineſs, by the Author of the Duty of Man</item>
               <item>291 <hi>Rich. Saunder</hi>'s Aſtrological Judgement and Practice of Phyſick—1677</item>
               <item>292 Dr. <hi>Jo. Newton</hi>'s <hi>Coſmographia,</hi> a view of the Globes Terreſtrial and Celeſtial 1679</item>
               <item>293 <hi>Hudibraſs,</hi> the Third and laſt part — <hi>London</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>294 <hi>Geo. Wyther</hi>'s Abuſes ſtript and whipt, or Satyrical Eſſays—1613</item>
               <item>295 <hi>Jo. Evelyn</hi>'s Navigation and Commerce, their Original and Progreſs — 1674</item>
               <item>296 <hi>Crow</hi>'s Exact Catalogue of our Engliſh Writers on the Bible—1673</item>
               <pb n="23" facs="tcp:42676:13"/>
               <item>297 Dr. <hi>Martin Luther</hi>'s 34 ſpecial and choſen Sermons, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1649</item>
               <item>298 <hi>Dryden</hi>'s <hi>Annus mirabilis;</hi> the year of Wonders 1666. an Hiſtorical Poem—1667</item>
               <item>299 Dr. <hi>Rich. Sibbs</hi> his Souls Conflict, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—wants Title —</item>
               <item>300 <hi>Sam. Ward</hi>'s Collection of Sermons and Treatiſes, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1636</item>
               <item>301 A Journey into <hi>Spain —London</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>302 Dr. <hi>Jo. Twyſden</hi>'s Anſwer to <hi>Needham's Medela Medicinae</hi>—1666</item>
               <item>303 Dr. <hi>Staunton</hi>'s Life and Death; and of Chriſtian Conference, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—1673</item>
               <item>304 Practice of Piety —1675</item>
               <item>305 Dr. <hi>Tho. Piercy</hi>'s Sinner Impleaded in his own Court — 1660</item>
               <item>306 <hi>Tho. Mannyngham</hi>'s Two Diſcourſes— 1681</item>
               <item>307 Sir <hi>Hen. Wotton</hi>'s Remains, <hi>viz.</hi> Lives, Letters, Poems, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—1651</item>
               <item>308 <hi>Li<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>tleton</hi>'s Tenures in Engliſh, lately peruſed and amended—1627</item>
               <item>309 <hi>Nic. Culpeper</hi>'s Treatiſe of the Rickets; or Childrens Diſeaſe —1668</item>
               <item>310 <hi>Sennertus</hi> his Practical Phyſick; of the Scurvy, Dropſie, Fevers, Pox and Gout 1676</item>
               <item>311 Dr. <hi>Reg. de Graaf's</hi> Treatiſe of Pancreatick Juice, with Figures—1676</item>
               <item>312 <hi>Ro<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>. Vilvain</hi>'s Epitomy of Eſſays, in Engliſh Verſe — 1654</item>
               <item>313 <hi>Geo. Sandy</hi>'s <hi>Ovid Metamorphoſis</hi> Engliſhed, in Verſe, <hi>3d</hi> Edition—1638</item>
               <item>314 Archbiſhop <hi>Abbot</hi>'s brief deſcription of the whole World—1656</item>
               <item>315 Sir <hi>Will. Temple's</hi> Obſervations upon the United Provinces of the Netherlands 1673</item>
               <item>316 Dr. <hi>Will. Johnſon's</hi> Narrative of a great deliverance at Sea —1672</item>
               <item>317 Dr. <hi>Patrick</hi>'s Appendix to the third part of the Friendly Debate—1670</item>
               <item>318 —his divine Arithmetick; or the right Art of numbring our Days— 1672</item>
               <item>319 <hi>Bulwer</hi>'s <hi>Chirologia,</hi> or the natural Language of the hand, with Figues —1644</item>
               <item>320 Cauſes and Remedy of the diſtempers of the Times, in diſcourſes of Obed. &amp; diſobed</item>
               <item>321 Choice Pieces of that Renowned Antiquary, Sir <hi>Rob. Cotton</hi> — 1651</item>
               <item>322 <hi>All. Roſs</hi> his <hi>Myſtagogus Po<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ticus,</hi> or the Muſes Interpreter— 1648</item>
               <item>323 —his View of the <hi>Jewiſh</hi> Religion, with the Articles of their Faith — 1656</item>
               <item>324 Memoirs of Mr. <hi>des. Ecotais,</hi> or the Motives of his Converſion—1677</item>
               <item>325 Monarchy aſſerted in a Conference before <hi>Owler Cromwel</hi> — 1660</item>
               <item>326 <hi>Wilkinſon</hi>'s Office and Authority of Coroners and Sherifs — 1641</item>
               <item>327 Biſhop <hi>Hall</hi>'s Reſolutions of divers Practical Caſes of Conſcience —1649</item>
               <item>328 <hi>Gildas</hi> (the Wiſe) his Epiſtle touching the deſtruction of <hi>Brittain</hi> by the <hi>Saxons</hi>
               </item>
               <item>329 Hiſtory of <hi>Eraſtus,</hi> and the 7 Wiſe Maſters of <hi>Rome,</hi> Illuſtrated with Pictures 1674</item>
               <item>330 Reflexions upojn Ancient and Modern Philoſophy, Moral and Natural—1678</item>
               <item>331 <hi>Herne</hi>'s Modern Aſſurancer, or the Clerks Directory, Preſidents, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—1658</item>
               <item>332 Touchſtone of Precedents Relating to Judicial Proceedings at Common Law 1682</item>
               <item>333 <hi>Clark's</hi> Guide, a Collection of Engliſh Preſidents, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> —1651</item>
               <item>334 <hi>Wil. Greenwood</hi>'s practical demonſtration of County-Judicatures —1668</item>
               <item>335 Judgement upon Law Caſes in the upper Bench and Common Pleas— 1655</item>
               <item>336 <hi>Jo. Cotgrave</hi>'s Engliſh Treaſury of Wit and Language— 1655</item>
               <item>337 <hi>Al. Roſs</hi> his marrow of Hiſtory in an Epitomy of Sir W. <hi>Rawleigh</hi> —1650</item>
               <item>338 <hi>America,</hi> an exact deſcription of the Weſt Indies, with a Map: by <hi>N. N.</hi>—1655</item>
               <item>339 Fort Royal of Holy Scriptures, a new Concordance, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> —1652</item>
               <item>340 <hi>Geo. Herbert</hi>'s Prieſt to the Temple, or the Country Parſon — 1677</item>
               <item>341 <hi>Jo. How</hi>'s Reconciliableneſs of Gods Preſcience of the Sins of Men—1677</item>
               <item>342 <hi>Ja. Janeway</hi>'s Heaven upon Earth, the beſt Friend in the worſt of Times, <hi>6th</hi> Edit.</item>
               <item>343 Thirty four ſpecial and choſen Sermons of Dr. <hi>Martin Luthers</hi> —1649</item>
               <item>3444 Mr. <hi>du Balzack</hi>'s new Epiſtles, Engliſhed by Sr. <hi>Rich. Baker</hi>—1639</item>
               <item>345 <hi>Al. Brome</hi>'s Songs and other Poems— 1661</item>
               <item>346 <hi>Certamen Epiſtolare,</hi> or a Letter-Combat between Dr. <hi>Heylin,</hi> Mr. <hi>Baxter,</hi> Dr. <hi>Bernard</hi>
               </item>
               <pb n="24" facs="tcp:42676:14"/>
               <item>347 Holy Life and happy Death of <hi>J. Bruen</hi> of <hi>Cheſhire,</hi> Eſq. — 1649</item>
               <item>348 Some Inſtructions concerning the Art of Oratory— 1658</item>
               <item>349 <hi>Jo. Wilkinſon</hi>'s Treatiſe of the Offices of Sherifs, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1641</item>
               <item>350 Sir <hi>Tho. Ireland</hi>'s exact abridgement of the Lord <hi>Cook</hi>'s Reports—1657</item>
               <item>351 <hi>Geo. Meriton</hi>'s Parſons Monitor, of Caſes concerning the Clergy— 1681</item>
               <item>352 Practick part of the Law in the Office of a compleat Attorney— 1656</item>
               <item>353 Compleat Sollicitor, performing his Duty, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 1666</item>
               <item>354 <hi>Tho. Wenthworths</hi> Office and Duty of Executors: <hi>4th</hi> Edition — 1656</item>
               <item>355 <hi>Wil. Shepheards</hi> Office of a Juſtice of Peace, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—1662</item>
               <item>356 <hi>Oſborne</hi>'s Political Obſervations on the Government of the <hi>Turks</hi>—1656</item>
               <item>357 <hi>Meriton</hi>'s Touchſtone of Wills, Teſtaments, and Adminiſtrations —1668</item>
               <item>358 Young Clerks Tutor in a Collecion of Engliſh Preſidents, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1668</item>
               <item>359 <hi>Littleton</hi>'s Tenures in Engliſh, peruſed and amended— 1661</item>
               <item>360 <hi>Jo. Sleiden</hi>'s Key of Hiſtory in an Abridgement of the 4 Monarchies — 1661</item>
               <item>361 Dr. <hi>Chamberlain</hi>'s Preſent State of <hi>England,</hi> with Reflexions on the Ancient, 2 Vol<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>362 French Gardner, <hi>3d</hi> Edition; Illuſtrated with Sculptures, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> —1675</item>
               <item>363 Anatomy of the Elder-Tree, in approved Remedys, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1670</item>
               <item>364 <hi>Tho. Vicary</hi>'s Surgeons directory for young Practitioners— 1651</item>
               <item>365 The Life of <hi>Donna Olimpia Maldachini</hi>— 1666</item>
               <item>366 <hi>Pet. Levin</hi>'s Pathway to Health, in excellent Medicines, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 166<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>367 Dr. <hi>Bayly</hi>'s <hi>Certamen Religioſum,</hi> in a conference between K. <hi>Charles</hi> &amp; M. of <hi>Worceſt<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>
                  </hi>
               </item>
               <item>368 The School of the Heart, in 47 Emblems —167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>369 <hi>Gildas</hi> (the Wiſe) his Epiſtle of the deſtruction of <hi>Brittain</hi> by the <hi>Saxons</hi> — 1638</item>
               <item>370 Sir <hi>Jo. Hayward</hi>'s Life and Reign of K. <hi>Edward</hi> the <hi>6th.</hi> and beginning of Q. <hi>Eli<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>
                  </hi>
               </item>
               <item>371 Mr. <hi>du Balzack</hi>'s Prince, Engliſhed out of <hi>French</hi> —1648</item>
               <item>372 Biſhop <hi>Hall</hi>'s Reſolutions of divers Caſes of Conſcience — 1641</item>
               <item>373 The Practice of Piety, directing a Chriſtian how to walk, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—</item>
               <item>374 Preſent State of the united Provinces of the Low Countrys —166<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>375 Biſhop <hi>Downame</hi> of the Covenant of Grace, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>—1647</item>
               <item>376 <hi>Evelyn</hi>'s <hi>K<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>len<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>arium Hortenſe,</hi> or the Gardners Almanack —167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>377 <hi>Sennertus</hi> his Practical Phyſick, of the Scurvy, Dropſie, Feavers, Pox and Gout 167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>378 Netherland-Hiſtorian, of the Wars between the <hi>Engliſh, French</hi> and <hi>Dutch,</hi> 60 Sculp<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>379 <hi>Geo. Joy's</hi> Refutation of Biſhop <hi>Wincheſter</hi> St. <hi>Gardner</hi>'s Book — 154<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>380 <hi>Jo. Wyckclif</hi>'s true Copy of a Prologue on the Engliſh Bible— 155<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>381 <hi>Fr. Rouſe</hi>'s Catholick Charity, and <hi>Rome</hi>'s Uncharitableneſs—164<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>382 <hi>R. Capel</hi> of Tentations, their Nature, Danger, Cure, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>— 165<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>383 <hi>Allen</hi>'s Riches of God's Covenant of Grace —166<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>384 <hi>Hughe</hi>'s exact Abridgement of Sir <hi>Fr. Moor</hi>'s Reports — 166<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>385 <hi>Hue</hi>'s Learned Treatiſe of the Globes, Engliſhed by <hi>Chilmead</hi>— 163<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>386 Sir <hi>Rob. Cotton</hi>'s choice Pieces, publiſhed by <hi>Howel</hi> — 167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>387 <hi>Fidel</hi>'s Guide for a ſtudious young Lawyer in Preſidents of Conveyances—1658</item>
               <item>388 <hi>Herne</hi>'s Modern Aſſurancer, or the Clerks Directory in Preſidents, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> —1658</item>
               <item>389 <hi>Phillip's</hi> Grandeur of the Law, and Catalogue of the Nobility and Gentry advanc'd</item>
               <item>390 <hi>Will. Tower</hi>'s Treatiſe againſt Atheiſm, confuting the ſame—1679</item>
               <item>391 Reply to the Anſwer of the Catholick Apology — 1668</item>
               <item>392 Capt. <hi>Bo<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>eler</hi>'s War practically performed, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> —1663</item>
               <item>393 <hi>Jeruſalem</hi> and <hi>Babel,</hi> whether Catholicks or Proteſtants be better Subjects—1653</item>
               <item>394 Sir <hi>Tho. Smith</hi>'s Commonwealth of <hi>England</hi> —1633</item>
               <item>395 <hi>Eugen. Philalethes</hi> his <hi>Magia Adamica,</hi> or Antiquity of Magick — 165<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>396 <hi>Oſborne</hi>'s Miſcellany of Eſſays, Paradoxes, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1659</item>
            </list>
         </div>
         <div type="catalogue">
            <pb n="1" facs="tcp:42676:14"/>
            <head>Divinity, Hiſtory, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> in Folio.</head>
            <list>
               <item>1 BIſhop <hi>Andrews</hi> ninety ſix Sermons, with a Sermon preached before two Kings 1641</item>
               <item>2 A View of the Soul, in ſeveral Tracts, by a Perſon of Quality, Gilt Back 1682</item>
               <item>3 <hi>Sibbs</hi> Commentary on the firſt Chapter of the Second Epiſtle to the <hi>Corinthians</hi> 1655</item>
               <item>4 <hi>Jermins</hi> Commentary upon the whole Book of the Proverbs of <hi>Solomon</hi> 1638</item>
               <item>5 <hi>Democritus Junior,</hi> alias <hi>Burtons</hi> Anatomy of Melancholy — <hi>Oxon.</hi> 1624</item>
               <item>6 <hi>Grews</hi> Deſcription of the Natural and Artificial Rarities belonging to the R. Society 1681</item>
               <item>7 <hi>Pembles</hi> Works; containing ſundry Treatiſes and Expoſitions — 1659</item>
               <item>8 <hi>Calvins</hi> Sermons upon the fifth Book of <hi>Moſes,</hi> called <hi>Deutronomy</hi> — 1583</item>
               <item>9 Dr. <hi>Cudworths</hi> Intel. Syſtem of the Univerſe, confut. the Reaſon and Phil. of Atheiſm 1673</item>
               <item>10 <hi>Auſtins</hi> Devout, Godly and Learned Meditations — 1633</item>
               <item>11 <hi>Cartwrights</hi> Confutation of the <hi>Rhemiſts</hi> Tranſlation of the New Teſtament 1618</item>
               <item>12 <hi>Willets</hi> Sixfold Commentary upon the Epiſtle of Saint <hi>Paul</hi> to the <hi>Romans</hi> 1611</item>
               <item>13 <hi>Guevaras</hi> Dial of Princes, declaring the Excel. of a Prince that is a good Chriſtian 1619</item>
               <item>14 Dr. <hi>Hortons</hi> choice Expoſitions on four ſelect <hi>Pſalms</hi> — 1675</item>
               <item>15 <hi>Luſhingtons</hi> Commentary on the Epiſtle to the <hi>Galathians</hi> — 1650</item>
               <item>16 <hi>Brathwaits Engliſh</hi> Gentleman, and <hi>Engliſh</hi> Gentlewoman, third Edition 1641</item>
               <item>17 <hi>Sterrys</hi> Diſcourſe of the Freedom of the Will — 1675</item>
               <item>18 <hi>Roberts</hi> Key of the Bible, unlocking the Richeſt Treaſures of the Holy Scriptures 1675</item>
               <item>19 The Houſe of Mourning, or a collection of 47 Funeral Serm. by ſeveral emin. Div. 1640</item>
               <item>20 <hi>Hooker</hi> of the Laws of Eccleſiaſtical Polity — 1611</item>
               <item>21 <hi>Davis</hi> Rights belonging to an Uniformity in Churches — 1669</item>
               <item>22 <hi>Monſieur de Silhons</hi> Miniſter of State, ſhewing the true uſe of Modern Policy 1658</item>
               <item>23 Dr. <hi>Mores</hi> Modeſt Enquiry into the Myſtery of Iniquity — 1664</item>
               <item>24 <hi>Cottons</hi> Compleat Concordance to the Bible of the laſt Tranſlation — 1631</item>
               <item>25 <hi>Muſculus</hi> Com. places of C. Rel. for the uſe of thoſe who deſire the knowl. of Godly truth 1563</item>
               <item>26 Relation of a Conference between Arch-Biſhop <hi>Laud,</hi> and Mr. <hi>Fiſher</hi> the Jeſuit 1673</item>
               <item>27 <hi>Cradocks</hi> Harmony of the 4 Evangeliſts — 1668</item>
               <item>28 Dr. <hi>Charletons Phiſiologia Epicuro-Caſſendo-Charletoniana,</hi> or a Fabrick of Science Nat. 1654</item>
               <item>29 <hi>Malynes, Lex Mercatoria,</hi> or the ancient Law Merchant — 1622</item>
               <item>30 <hi>Edmunds</hi> on <hi>Caeſars</hi> Com. ſhewing the practice of the Art Mil. in the time of the <hi>Rom.</hi> 1604</item>
               <item>31 <hi>Dickſons</hi> Expoſit. of St. <hi>Pauls</hi> Epiſtles, and thoſe other Epiſt. of the Apoſt. Gilt back 1659</item>
               <item>32 <hi>Skenes</hi> Collection of the Laws, and Acts of Parliament of <hi>Scotland</hi>
               </item>
               <item>33 L. <hi>Bacons</hi> Nat. Hiſt. with his Hiſt. of Life and Death, New <hi>Atlantis,</hi> and <hi>Novum Organum</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>34 —Advancement and Proficiency of Learning 1640</item>
               <item>35 <hi>Seldens</hi> Titles of Honour, the third and laſt Edition, with Addit. and Amendments 1672</item>
               <item>36 <hi>Symſons Lexicon,</hi> or Alphab. Concordance of all the Words in the N. Teſt. <hi>Eng. Gr.</hi> &amp; <hi>Lat.</hi> 1658</item>
               <item>37 <hi>Gells</hi> Eſſay toward the amendment of the laſt Engliſh Tranſlation of the bible 1659</item>
               <item>38 The Muſes Welcome to the High and Mighty King <hi>James Edinburgh</hi> 1618</item>
               <item>39 <hi>Wards</hi> Animadverſions, or a Magazine of the trueſt Inſtruct. for the managery of War 1639</item>
               <item>40 <hi>Froſts</hi> Select Sermons, preached on ſpecial occaſions — 1658</item>
               <item>41 <hi>Willets</hi> Sixfold Commentary on the moſt Divine Propheſie of <hi>Daniel</hi> 1610</item>
               <item>42 — Sixfold Commentary upon the Third Book of <hi>Moſes,</hi> called <hi>Leviticus</hi> 1631</item>
               <item>43 — An Harmony upon the Firſt Book of <hi>Samuel</hi> 1614</item>
               <item>44 Dr. <hi>Featlys Clavis Myſtica,</hi> a Key opening difficult Texts, handled in 70 Sermons 1636</item>
               <item>45 Biſhop <hi>Williams</hi> Truth Vindicated, againſt Atheiſm, Sacriledge and Profaneneſs 1666</item>
               <item>46 Dr. <hi>Whi<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>es</hi> Way to the true Ch. and his Reply to Jeſuit <hi>Fiſher,</hi> 2 Books bound in 1 vol. 1624</item>
               <item>47 Biſhop <hi>Downames</hi> Treatiſe of Juſtification — 1639</item>
               <pb n="2" facs="tcp:42676:15"/>
               <item>48 Dr. <hi>Hakwills</hi> Apology for the Providence of God in the Government of the World 1630</item>
               <item>49 Biſhop of <hi>Exeters</hi> Poor Mans Library — 1652</item>
               <item>50 Biſhop <hi>Halls</hi> Works, the firſt Vol. with a Table newly added to the whole work 1625</item>
               <item>51 B. of <hi>Coventry</hi> and <hi>Lichfield</hi> of the Inſtitut. of the Sacr. of the Body and Blood of Chr. 1631</item>
               <item>52 <hi>Lucius Annaeus Seneca</hi>'s Works, both Moral and natural, Tranſlated by <hi>T. Lodge.</hi> 161<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>53 Hiſt. of the Church for the firſt ſix hundred Years after Chriſt, by <hi>Euſeb. Pamphilius.</hi> 1607</item>
               <item>54 —Of the Ch. from the Prim. Age, with an acc. of the Perſ. of true Martyrs, by <hi>fox.</hi> Vol. 1. 1641</item>
               <item>55 —Of the World, from the beg. to the Monarchy of <hi>Conſtantine</hi> the Great, by <hi>W. Howel.</hi> 1661</item>
               <item>56 —Of the World, or <hi>Mercators</hi> Atlas, containing his deſcription thereof, full of Mapps. 1635</item>
               <item>57 —Of 4 footed Beaſts, by <hi>Geſner;</hi> to which is added the Theatre of Inſects by <hi>T. Muflet</hi> 1658</item>
               <item>58 —Of the noble and renowned Kingdom of <hi>Naples,</hi> with a ſupplement, by <hi>J. Howel.</hi> 1654</item>
               <item>59 —Of the 22. years reign of K. <hi>Lewis</hi> the 11. by <hi>P. Mattheu,</hi> Engliſhed by <hi>E. Grinſton.</hi> 1614</item>
               <item>60 —Of the <hi>Presbyterians,</hi> cont. the beg. progreſs and ſucceſs of that active Sect. by <hi>P. Heylin.</hi> 1672</item>
               <item>61 —Of the whole World, and all the Kingdoms, Prov. Seas, and Iſles thereof by <hi>P Heylin</hi> 1666</item>
               <item>62 —Of the County Palentine of <hi>Cheſter,</hi> illuſt. with divers Fig. cut in Copper, by <hi>D. King.</hi> 1656</item>
               <item>63 —Of the Lives of all the Ks. of this Iſle from 2855 unto the year 1660. by Sir <hi>W. Churchil</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>64 —Of the <hi>Turks,</hi> from the firſt beg. of that Nat. with the Lives of the <hi>Ott.</hi> Emp. by <hi>R. Knolls</hi> 1610</item>
               <item>65 —Of <hi>France,</hi> from the beg. of that Monar. Writ. in <hi>Fr.</hi> by <hi>I. Deſerres,</hi> Eng. by <hi>E. Grinſtone</hi> 1607</item>
               <item>66 —Of the 4 laſt Parliaments of Q. <hi>Elizabeth</hi> of famous memory, coll. by <hi>H. Townſhend.</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>67 —Of the Wars of <hi>Flanders</hi> writ. in <hi>Italian</hi> by Card. <hi>Bentivoglio,</hi> eng. by the E. of <hi>Monmouth</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>68 —Of the Civil Wars of <hi>Spain</hi> ih the beginning of the reign of <hi>Charles</hi> the Fifth. 1652</item>
               <item>69 —Of <hi>England</hi> to the reign of <hi>Edward</hi> III. by <hi>S. Daniel;</hi> cont. to <hi>Richard</hi> III. by <hi>J. Truſſel.</hi> 2 Vol.</item>
               <item>70 —Of the World, or an account of Time, compiled by the learned <hi>Dioniſius Petavius.</hi> 1659</item>
               <item>71 —Of the Antiquities of Antient <hi>Brittaine,</hi> by <hi>Aylet Sammes.</hi> Lettered.— 1676</item>
               <item>72 —Of thoſe Philoſophers on whom the Attribute of Wiſe was conferred, by <hi>T. Stanley.</hi> 1655</item>
               <item>73 —Of S. <hi>Pauls</hi> Cathedral, by <hi>W. Dugdale:</hi> beaut. with Proſ. of the Church, Tombs, &amp; Monuments</item>
               <item>74 —Of the Civil Wars of <hi>France</hi> by <hi>H. C. D' Avila.</hi> Gilt and Lettered on the Back. 1678</item>
               <item>75 —Of the aff. of State in <hi>Scotland</hi> to the murther of K. <hi>Charles</hi> I. by <hi>P. Nalſon</hi> Vol. 2. 1683</item>
               <item>76 —Of the Council of <hi>Trent</hi> in eight Books. — 1620</item>
               <item>77 —Of the lives of the noble <hi>Grecians</hi> and <hi>Romans</hi> by <hi>Plutarch.</hi> — 1612</item>
               <item>78 —Of the Signiory of <hi>Venice,</hi> of her policy, and method of Government, by <hi>J. Howel.</hi> 1651</item>
               <item>79 —Of <hi>Great Britain,</hi> from the firſt peopling of this Land, to K. <hi>James,</hi> by <hi>W. Slatyr</hi>
               </item>
               <item>80 —Of the Holy War, by <hi>Thomas Fuller.</hi> — 1647</item>
               <item>81 —Of the Church of <hi>Great Britaine,</hi> from the birth of Chriſt to 1648. by <hi>T. Fuller.</hi> 1655</item>
               <item>82 —Of the Reign of K. <hi>Henry</hi> VII. by my Lord <hi>Bacon.</hi> — 1641</item>
               <item>83 —Of the mem. acc. of <hi>France</hi> under <hi>Henry</hi> II. <hi>Francis</hi> II. <hi>Charles</hi> IX. <hi>Henry</hi> III. <hi>Henry</hi> IV. 1598</item>
               <item>84 —Of <hi>Great Brittain,</hi> by <hi>J. Speed.</hi> — 1632</item>
               <item>85 —Of <hi>Polybius</hi> the <hi>Megapolitan</hi> — 1634</item>
               <item>86 —Of the Noble, High and Puiſſant Prince, <hi>W. Cavendiſh,</hi> Duke of <hi>Newcaſtle</hi> 1667</item>
               <item>87 —Of the <hi>Jews,</hi> &amp;c by <hi>Joſephus</hi> — 1670</item>
               <item>88 —Of the Valarous and Witty Knight Errant <hi>Don Quixot</hi> of the <hi>Mancha.</hi> — 1675</item>
               <item>89 —Of the great and renowned Monarchy of <hi>China.</hi> — 1655</item>
               <item>90 —Of <hi>Edward</hi> IV. King of <hi>England,</hi> by <hi>W. Habington.</hi> — 1640</item>
               <item>91 —Of the Reign of King <hi>Henry</hi> VII. by my Lord <hi>Bacon.</hi> — 1641</item>
               <item>92 —Of the Iron Age, illuſtrated with the lively Effigies of renowned Perſons. 1650</item>
               <item>93 <hi>Speed (John)</hi> Proſpect of the moſt famous parts of the World. — 1662</item>
               <item>94 <hi>Caſſandra</hi> the ſamed Romance, the whole Work, gilt Back and lettered — 1676</item>
               <item>95 Dutcheſs of <hi>Newcaſtles</hi> Playes, never before printed — 1668</item>
               <item>96 — Philo<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ophycal and Phyſical Opinions. — 1655</item>
               <item>97 — Philo<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ophical <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>e<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>ers and Reflect. upon ſome Opinions in Natural Philoſophy. 1664</item>
               <pb n="3" facs="tcp:42676:15"/>
               <item>98 Letters and Poems in honour of the incomparable <hi>Margaret</hi> Dutcheſs of <hi>Newcaſtle.</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>99 <hi>Ovids</hi> Metamorphoſis, engliſhed, methodized, and repreſented in Figures by <hi>G. Sandys.</hi> 1632.</item>
               <item>100 <hi>Guillims</hi> diſplay of Heraldry, ſecond Edition enlarged. — 1632</item>
               <item>101 <hi>Philips</hi> new World of <hi>Engliſh</hi> Words, or gen. Dict. interp. the hard Words in our Lan. 1663</item>
               <item>102 The Princeſs <hi>Cloria,</hi> or the Royal Romance, by a perſon of Honour. — 1665</item>
               <item>103 <hi>Tarſis</hi> and <hi>Zelie,</hi> the famous new Romance — 1685</item>
               <item>104 The Novels and Tales of the Renown. <hi>John Boccaſio,</hi> fifth Edit. corrected and am. 1684</item>
               <item>105 <hi>Howells Morphandra,</hi> or parley of Beaſts — 1660</item>
               <item>106 <hi>Plutarchs</hi> Philoſophy, commonly called the Morals — 1603</item>
               <item>107 The Works of the famous and worthy Miniſter of Chriſt, Mr. <hi>W. Perkins,</hi> in 3 Vol.</item>
               <item>108 <hi>Hilderſams</hi> Lectures on the fourth Chapter of <hi>John</hi> — 1629</item>
               <item>109 <hi>Leighs</hi> Body of Div. in 10 Books, wherein the Fundam. and grounds of Rel. are open'd 1654</item>
               <item>110 —Annotations on the five Poetieal Books of the Old Teſtament — 1657</item>
               <item>111 —Annotations upon all the New Teſtament, Philological and Theological 1650</item>
               <item>112 Four Tracts, written by the Learned <hi>John Selden,</hi> of the <hi>Inner Temple,</hi> Eſquire 1683</item>
               <item>113 <hi>Towerſons</hi> Works, being an Explic. of the Creed, the Decal. of the L. Prayer, in 3 vol. 1685</item>
               <item>114 <hi>Urſinus</hi> ſumm of Chriſt. Relig. to which is added <hi>Parens</hi> Theological Miſcellanies 1645</item>
               <item>115 <hi>Rea</hi>'s <hi>Flora, Ceres</hi> and <hi>Pomona,</hi> adorn'd with Sculptures cut in Copper — 1665</item>
               <item>116 <hi>Calvins</hi> Commentary upon the Propheſie of <hi>Iſaiah</hi> — 1609</item>
               <item>117 Dr. <hi>Littletons</hi> ſixty one Sermons, preached moſtly upon publick occaſions — 1680</item>
               <item>118 Biſhop <hi>Brownrigs</hi> ſixty five Sermons, in 2 Volumes</item>
               <item>119 <hi>Wrights</hi> Commentary on the five Books of <hi>Moſes</hi> — 1668</item>
               <item>120 A Collection of the Works of Dr. <hi>Jackſon,</hi> ſuch as were not publiſhed before 1654</item>
               <item>121 <hi>Faringdons</hi> 30 Sermons, to which is added a Sermon at the Funeral of Sir <hi>Geo. Whitmore</hi> 1647</item>
               <item>122 <hi>Bochas</hi> Fall of Princes and other Nobles, Engliſhed by <hi>John Lydgate,</hi> Monk of <hi>Bury</hi> 1527</item>
               <item>123 Four Books of the Hiſtory of <hi>Cornelius Tacitus,</hi> with Annototions by <hi>Henry Savil</hi> 1591</item>
               <item>24 The Wall-Flower, a Hiſt. partly true, partly Romantick, morally Divine, by <hi>T. Baily</hi> 1650</item>
               <item>125 Pleaſant Notes on <hi>Don Quixot,</hi> by <hi>Edmund Gayton</hi> — 1654</item>
               <item>126 Sir <hi>William Davenants</hi> Works compleat, conſiſting of Poems and Plays — 1673</item>
               <item>127 <hi>Hymens Preludia,</hi> or Loves Maſter-piece, being that ſo much admired Rom. <hi>Cleopatra</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>128 <hi>Roberts</hi> Merchants Map of Commerce — 1677</item>
               <item>129 <hi>Bentivoglio</hi> and <hi>Urania,</hi> in ſix Books, by <hi>Nathanael Ingelo</hi> — 1682</item>
               <item>130 <hi>Chillingworths</hi> Relig. of the Prot. a ſafe way to Salv. with 9 Serm. and other things 1684</item>
               <item>131 <hi>Kendalls</hi> Perſeverance of Saints, vind from the Attempts made againſt it, by <hi>J. Goodwin</hi> 1654</item>
               <item>132 Biſhop <hi>Jewells</hi> Works, wants part of the Epiſt. Dedicatory, and part of 2 Leaves at the end</item>
               <item>133 <hi>Perkins</hi> Works, the ſecond Volume — 1631</item>
               <item>134 <hi>Muſculus</hi> Common Places of Chriſtian Religion — 1563</item>
               <item>135 <hi>Parrs</hi> Expoſition on the Epiſtle of St. <hi>Paul</hi> to the <hi>Romans,</hi> wants a Title</item>
               <item>136 <hi>Du Bartus</hi> his Divine Works and Weeks, Tranſlated, with Additions, by <hi>J. Sylveſter</hi> 1633</item>
               <item>137 A learned ſummary upon the famous Poem of <hi>William</hi> of <hi>Saluſt,</hi> Lord of <hi>Bartas</hi> 1621</item>
               <item>138 The Rogue, or the Life of <hi>Guſman de Alferache</hi> — 1634</item>
               <item>139 The Triumphs of <hi>Naſſau,</hi> or a Deſcript of the Victories obtained by Pr. <hi>Maurice</hi> of <hi>Naſſau</hi>
               </item>
               <item>140 <hi>Ramſeys</hi> Aſtrology reſtored, being an introduction to the language of the Stars 1653</item>
               <item>141 <hi>Guillims</hi> Diſplay of Heraldry, the laſt edition, illuſtrated with variety of Sculptures 1679</item>
               <item>142 Dr. <hi>Kellets</hi> Miſcellanies of Divinity — 1635</item>
               <item>143 <hi>Sleidans</hi> Commentaries, concern. Relig. during the Reign of the Emp. <hi>Charles</hi> V. wants a Title</item>
               <item>144 Sir <hi>Thomas Mores</hi> Works — 1530</item>
               <item>145 Counteſs of <hi>Pembrokes Arcadia,</hi> written by Sir <hi>Phil. Sidney,</hi> laſt edition, with his Life 1674</item>
               <item>146 <hi>Mayers</hi> Commentary on the New Teſtament as far as the <hi>Acts</hi> — 1631</item>
               <item>147 <hi>Geodwin (John)</hi> Redemption Redeemed — 1651</item>
               <pb n="4" facs="tcp:42676:16"/>
               <item>148 Biſhop <hi>Uſhers</hi> Body of Divinity, or ſum and ſubſtance of Chriſtian Religion 164<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>149 B. <hi>Taylors</hi> great Exemplar deſ. in the Life and Death of the ever bleſſed Jeſus Chriſt 1653</item>
               <item>150 — Courſe of Sermons for all the Sundays of the Year — 1668</item>
               <item>151 A Bible of an ancient print, undivided, with A. B. <hi>Cranmers</hi> Preface. imperf. toward the end</item>
               <item>152 <hi>Cauſins</hi> Holy Court — 1650</item>
               <item>153 <hi>Beards</hi> Theatre of God's Judgments on notorious ſinners, continued by D. <hi>Tho. Taylor</hi> 1648</item>
               <item>154 <hi>Stephens</hi> World of Wonders — 1607</item>
               <item>155 <hi>Bonets</hi> Guide to the Practical Phyſician, ſhewing the ſafeſt way to cure all Diſeaſes 1684</item>
               <item>156 <hi>Yorkes</hi> Union of Honour — 1640</item>
               <item>157 <hi>Bodins</hi> ſix Books of a Commonwealth — 1606</item>
               <item>158 King <hi>Charles</hi> Declaration concerning the Tumults in <hi>Scotland,</hi> from their firſt originals 1639</item>
               <item>159 Sir <hi>Kenelm Dighys</hi> two Treatiſes of the Nature of Bodies, and of Mans Soul 1644</item>
               <item>160 <hi>Steph. Charnocks</hi> Works, 2 Vol. Compleat — 1684</item>
               <item>161 <hi>Jo. Ruſhworths</hi> Collections, 4 Vol. Compleat — 1680</item>
               <item>162 Lord <hi>Howards</hi> defenſative againſt the poyſon of ſuppoſed Propheſies — 1620</item>
               <item>163 <hi>De Grays</hi> compleat Horſeman and exper Farrier — 1639</item>
               <item>164 Notable Revol. that happen'd in the <hi>Netherlands</hi> in 1650 and 1651 by <hi>Lion Aitzema</hi> 1653</item>
               <item>165 <hi>Camdens</hi> Brittania, or Maps of all the Count. of <hi>Eng.</hi> &amp; <hi>Wales,</hi> with a Map of <hi>Scotl.</hi> &amp; <hi>Jrel.</hi>
               </item>
            </list>
         </div>
         <div type="catalogue">
            <head>Divinity, Hiſtory, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> in Quarto.</head>
            <list>
               <item>1 <hi>ARrowſmiths</hi> Chain of Principles, wherein the Heads of Rel. are aſſerted &amp; improv. 1659</item>
               <item>2 <hi>Airays</hi> Lectures upon the whole Epiſtle of St. <hi>Paul</hi> to the <hi>Philippians</hi> 1618</item>
               <item>3 An Account of Ancient Ch. Gov. with Reflex. on the modern Writ. of the <hi>Presbyt.</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>4 Atturneys Academy, or the man. to proceed practic. upon any Suit, Plaint, or Action whatſoev.</item>
               <item>5 <hi>Antoninus</hi> the <hi>Roman</hi> Emperour, his Meditations concerning a natural mans happineſs 1634</item>
               <item>6 <hi>Burroughs</hi> of earthly-mindedneſs, and of Heavenly converſation, and walking with God 1649</item>
               <item>7 <hi>Balzacs</hi> Letters — 1638</item>
               <item>8 Lord <hi>Bacons</hi> Eſſays, and Counſels Civil and Moral — 1625</item>
               <item>9 Biſhop <hi>Bilſons</hi> difference between Chriſtian Subjection and Unchriſtian Rebellion 1595</item>
               <item>10 <hi>Boltons (Robert)</hi> Works, in 2 Vol. containing his diſcourſe about Happineſs, his Inſtructions for comforting afflicted Conſciences, his 4 laſt things, his Direct. for walking with God</item>
               <item>11 <hi>Breerewoods</hi> Enquiries, touching the diverſity of Religions and Languages in the World 1622</item>
               <item>12 <hi>Brinſleys</hi> third part of the true watch, or call of the Lord, to meet him ſpeedily 1623</item>
               <item>13 <hi>Burroughs</hi> Goſpel Converſation — 1650</item>
               <item>14 <hi>Burges</hi> Anſwer to a Pamphlet againſt Dr. <hi>Mortons</hi> defence of the 3 nocent Ceremonies 1631</item>
               <item>15 <hi>Barclayes</hi> Diſcourſe of the Felicity of Man, or his <hi>Summum Bonum</hi> — 1598</item>
               <item>16 <hi>Barriffes</hi> Military Diſcipline, or the young Artillery-man — 1643</item>
               <item>17 <hi>Beards</hi> Theatre of Gods Judgments upon notorious Sinners, both Great and Small 1612</item>
               <item>18 <hi>Boords</hi> Breviary of Health, wherein doth follow Rem. for all Diſ. hap. to the Body of Man 1598</item>
               <item>19 <hi>Collings</hi> on the whole Second Chapter of the <hi>Canticles</hi> — 1676</item>
               <item>20 Biſhop <hi>Bilſons</hi> Sermons concerning the Redemption of Mankind by Chriſt Jeſus 1599</item>
               <item>21 <hi>Birckbeks</hi> Proteſtants Evidence taken out of good Records — 1635</item>
               <item>22 Mr. <hi>Blandeviles</hi> Exerciſes in the Mathematicks, containing 8 Treatiſes — 1622</item>
               <item>23 <hi>Barclays Argenis,</hi> or the Loves of <hi>Polyarchus</hi> and <hi>Argenis,</hi> adorned with curious Cuts 1636</item>
               <item>24 Lord <hi>Clarendons</hi> Survey of the pernicious errors in Mr. <hi>Hobbes Leviathan</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>25 <hi>Colvills</hi> twelve Sermons — 1655</item>
               <item>26 Dr. <hi>Donnes</hi> Letters to ſeveral Perſons of Honour — 1651</item>
               <item>27 — His Poems, with Elegies on the Authors Death; the laſt Leaf torn 1633</item>
               <item>28 The Country Farm, with a Diſcourſe concerning Hunting — 1606</item>
               <pb n="5" facs="tcp:42676:16"/>
               <item>28 <hi>Calvins</hi> Commentary on the Epiſtle St. <hi>Paul</hi> to the <hi>Galathians</hi> — 1581</item>
               <item>29 <hi>Cartwrights</hi> Expoſit. on the whole 15 <hi>Pſalm,</hi> to which is added the Life of the Author 1658</item>
               <item>30 Dr. <hi>Charletons</hi> Darkneſs of Atheiſm diſpelled by the Light of Nature — 1652</item>
               <item>31 <hi>Crellius</hi> his 2 Books, touching one God the Father — 1665</item>
               <item>32 <hi>Des-Chartes</hi> Compendium of Muſick, with Animadv. thereon by a Perſon of Honour 1653</item>
               <item>33 <hi>Culverwells</hi> elegant Diſcourſe of the Light of Nature, with ſeveral other Treatiſes 1669</item>
               <item>34 Dr. <hi>Charletons</hi> Ternary of Par. of the magnet. Cure of Wounds, Nativ. of Tartar in Wine, <hi>&amp;c</hi>
               </item>
               <item>35 <hi>Dods</hi> Expoſition of the Commandments — 1632</item>
               <item>36 Sir <hi>Kenelm Digby</hi> of the Nature of Bodies, and of the Nature of Mans Soul 1665</item>
               <item>37 Sir <hi>William Davenants Gondibert,</hi> an Heroick Poem — 1651</item>
               <item>38 <hi>Downames</hi> ſumm of Sacred Divinity</item>
               <item>39 <hi>Dearings</hi> Readings upon the Epiſtle to the <hi>Hebrews</hi> — 1583</item>
               <item>40 <hi>Eltons</hi> Explanation of the Epiſtle of St. <hi>Paul</hi> to the <hi>Romans</hi> — 1623</item>
               <item>41 — On the Commandments and Lords Prayer — 1625</item>
               <item>42 Dr. <hi>Featlys</hi> Caſe for the Spectacles, or a defence of <hi>Via Tuta,</hi> by Sir <hi>Humph. Lynde</hi> 1638</item>
               <item>43 — <hi>Romiſh Fiſher</hi> caught and held in his own Net — 1624</item>
               <item>44 <hi>Dykes</hi> two Treatiſes of Repentance and of Chriſts Temptations — 1631</item>
               <item>45 Biſhop <hi>Charletons</hi> Thankful Remembrance of Gods Mercies — 1624</item>
               <item>46 Biſhop <hi>Gauders</hi> Defence by way of Apol. of the Miniſters of the Church of <hi>Engl.</hi> 1653</item>
               <item>47 <hi>Harbys</hi> Pattern in the Mount, wherein many places of Scripture are explained 1674</item>
               <item>48 <hi>Howards</hi> Defenſative againſt the poyſon of ſuppoſed Propheſies</item>
               <item>49 <hi>Goodmans</hi> Penit. pardon'd, or effic. of Rep. ſet forth under the Par. of the Pr. Son, with Fig. 1679</item>
               <item>50 <hi>Goodwin (John)</hi> Divine Authority of the Scriptures aſſerted — 1648</item>
               <item>51 <hi>Hammond</hi> Obl. to Peace and Charity, deliv. in a Serm. at <hi>Carisbrook</hi> Caſtle, with 9 Serm. 1649</item>
               <item>52 — <hi>Diſarmers</hi> Dexterity. Reply to the Cath. Gent. anſ. to his Bookab. Schiſm, bound up tog. 1656</item>
               <item>53 — Diſpatcher diſpatched, being a third defence of the Treatiſe of Schiſm. — 1659</item>
               <item>54 — Practical Catechiſm, with eleven other Tracts of his bound up together — 1646</item>
               <item>55 — Power of the Keys, or, of Binding and Looſing — 1647</item>
               <item>56 <hi>Hanſteds</hi> Sermons, Preached on ſeveal Sundays and Saints days — 1636</item>
               <item>57 <hi>Markhams</hi> way to get wealth, con. 6 Prin. Vocat. in which good Husbands may imp. themſ. 1676</item>
               <item>58 <hi>Dariots</hi> Judgment of the Stars, wherein we whole Art of Aſtrology is plainly delivered 1653</item>
               <item>59 <hi>Markhams</hi> Maſter-piece, touching the Cure of all Diſeaſes in Horſes — 1675</item>
               <item>60 Dr. <hi>Heylinss</hi> little diſcription of the great World. — 1631</item>
               <item>61 The Sum of a conference between <hi>J. Reynolds,</hi> and <hi>J. Hart,</hi> about the head of the Church 1609</item>
               <item>62 Dr. <hi>Mantons</hi> Seventeen Sermons on ſeveral Texts of Scripture. — 1678</item>
               <item>63 <hi>Stonehams</hi> Parable of the ten Virgins opened — 1676</item>
               <item>64 <hi>Swans Speculum Mundi,</hi> or a Glaſs repreſenting the Face of the World. — 1670</item>
               <item>65 <hi>Swinnocks</hi> Heaven and Hell Epit. Fading of the fleſh, and flour. of faith, bound toget. 1663</item>
               <item>66 <hi>Taylor (Tho.)</hi> parable of the Sower and of the Seed — 1623</item>
               <item>67 <hi>Forbes</hi> Commentary on the <hi>Revelation</hi> of St. <hi>John</hi> — 1613</item>
               <item>68 <hi>Calvins</hi> Commentary on the whole Book of Pſalms — 1571</item>
               <item>69 Dr. <hi>Heylins</hi> Hiſtory of the Sabbath, ſecond edition — 1636</item>
               <item>70 <hi>Medes (Joſeph)</hi> Apoſtacy of the latter times — 1655</item>
               <item>71 <hi>Clelands</hi> Inſtitution of a young Noble-man — 1607</item>
               <item>72 <hi>Mayers</hi> Treaſury of Eccleſiaſtical expoſitions on the difficult places of Scripture 1623</item>
               <item>73 <hi>Hardys</hi> Sermons, preached on ſolemn occaſions — 1653</item>
               <item>74 <hi>Goads</hi> Refreſhing Drops and Scorching Vialls — 1653</item>
               <item>75 Mr <hi>John Hales</hi> of <hi>Eaton Colledge,</hi> his Golden Remains — 1659</item>
               <item>76 <hi>Coghams</hi> Haven of Health, gathered for the comfort of thoſe that have a care thereof 1636</item>
               <item>77 Biſhop <hi>Pearſons</hi> Expoſition of the Creed — 1659</item>
               <pb n="6" facs="tcp:42676:17"/>
               <item>78 <hi>Goodwins (John)</hi> being filled with the Spirit — 1670</item>
               <item>79 <hi>Gotts</hi> Divine Hiſtory of the <hi>Geneſis</hi> of the World, Explicated and illuſtrated 1670</item>
               <item>80 <hi>Jeanes</hi> Mixture of Scholaſt. Divinity, with Practical, inſev. Tractates compl. in 2 Vol. 1656</item>
               <item>81 <hi>Latimers</hi> Sermons, wanting a Title and latter end</item>
               <item>82 <hi>Miltons</hi> Hiſtory of <hi>England</hi> — 1671</item>
               <item>83 —Paradice loſt, a Poem in 10 Books — 1669</item>
               <item>84 <hi>Lathams</hi> Falconry, teaching how to train up Hawks, and how to cure their Diſeaſes 1633</item>
               <item>85 <hi>Gregory (John)</hi> Works, in 2 parts; the 1 cont. his Notes on the Script. the 2 his <hi>Poſthuma</hi> 1665</item>
               <item>86 <hi>Grangers</hi> divine Logick for the uſe of Divines in the practice of Preaching 1620</item>
               <item>87 <hi>Kings</hi> Lectures on <hi>Jonas</hi> — 1600</item>
               <item>88 <hi>Prynns</hi> profitable Meditations on theſe three leaves of Nature, Rocks, Seas, &amp; Gardens. 1641</item>
               <item>89 <hi>Hicks</hi> Tranſlation of certain ſelect Dialogues of <hi>Lucian</hi> — 1634</item>
               <item>90 <hi>Gales</hi> Court of the Gentiles, ſhewing the Or. of humane Literature 2 1ſt. pts. together. 1672</item>
               <item>91 Certain Sermons appointed by the Q. Maj. to be read by Parſons, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> in Churches. 1595</item>
               <item>92 Dr <hi>Pierces</hi> decad of Caveats to the peop. of <hi>Eng.</hi> with an Appen. againſt Atheiſts &amp; Infidels, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>93 <hi>Sterry</hi> of the Kingdom of God in the Soul of Man. — 1683</item>
               <item>94 Harmony of the Confeſſions of Faith of the Chriſtian and reformed Churches, 1643</item>
               <item>95 <hi>Saviolos</hi> two Books, 1ſt. of Rapier and Dagger, the 2d. of Honour, &amp; honour. Quarrels 1595</item>
               <item>96 Biſhop. <hi>Reynolds</hi> of the paſſions and faculties of the Soul of Man. — 1640</item>
               <item>97 — Meditations on the Sacrament of the Lords laſt-Supper — 1638</item>
               <item>98 — Explication on the 110 Pſalm. — 1632</item>
               <item>99 <hi>Rogers</hi> Faith, Doct. &amp; Relig. profeſſed in this Realm of <hi>Eng.</hi> expreſſed in 39 Articles. 1658</item>
               <item>100 <hi>Whitbys</hi> Romiſh Doctaines not from the beg. being a reply to <hi>Ccreſſy,</hi> aga. Dr. <hi>Pierces</hi> Sermon.</item>
               <item>101 <hi>Mornays</hi> trueneſs of Chriſtian Religion, againſt Atheiſts, Epicures, Jews, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1604</item>
               <item>102 Biſhop <hi>Parkers</hi> divine Authority of the Law of Nature, and Chriſtian Religion. 1681</item>
               <item>103 <hi>Pierſons</hi> excellent encouragements againſt Afflictions, or an expoſ. of 4 ſelect Pſalms. 1647</item>
               <item>104 Dr. <hi>Sclaters</hi> Expoſition on the firſt and ſecond Epiſtles to the <hi>Theſſalonians</hi> — 1627</item>
               <item>105 Dr. <hi>Mantons</hi> Expoſition on the Epiſtle of St. <hi>Jude</hi> — 1658</item>
               <item>106 — Expoſition on the Epiſtle of St. <hi>James,</hi> ſecond Edition — 1653</item>
               <item>107 Dr. <hi>Pierces</hi> Collection of Sermons on ſeveral occaſions — 1671</item>
               <item>108 Dr <hi>Patricks</hi> Parable of the Prodigal Son, written to a Friend — 1667</item>
               <item>109 <hi>Fitzherberts</hi> Treatiſe of Policy and Religion, written for the benefit of a young Stateſt. 1657</item>
               <item>110 <hi>Leſtrange</hi> (Sir <hi>R.</hi>) Memento, directed to all that reverence the memory of K. <hi>Ch.</hi> the Mar. 1662</item>
               <item>111 <hi>Junius</hi> of the Painting of the Antients, ſhewing the begin. and conſummation of that Art. 1638</item>
               <item>112 <hi>Ortelius</hi> his Epitome of the Theatre of the World — 1603</item>
               <item>113 Dr. <hi>Stillingfleets Origines Sacrae,</hi> or a rational account of the divine Authority of Script. 1662</item>
               <item>114 — <hi>Irenieum,</hi> or a weapon Salve for the Ch. Wounds, &amp; an Append. about Excommun. 1662</item>
               <item>115 <hi>Seldens</hi> Hiſt. of Tythes, about the Payment, Laws, Opinions, touching the right of them 1618</item>
               <item>116 <hi>Quarles (Francis)</hi> Fancies, in Epigrams, Meditations and Obſervations — 1641</item>
               <item>117 Biſhop <hi>Prideams</hi> Introduction for the reading of all ſorts of Hiſtories — 1655</item>
               <item>118 <hi>Perkins</hi> Expoſition of the Symbole or Creed of the Apoſtles — 1631</item>
               <item>119 — His whole Treatiſe of the Caſes of Conſcience — 1651</item>
               <item>120 <hi>Leybournes</hi> nine Geometrical Exerciſes for young Seamen — 1669</item>
               <item>121 <hi>Baylies</hi> diſſwaſive from the Errors of the Times — 1646</item>
               <item>122 Biſhop <hi>Halls</hi> Divine Right of Epiſcopacy aſſerted — 1640</item>
               <item>123 Biſhop <hi>Sanderſons</hi> ten Sermons, <hi>ad Clerum, ad Magiſtratum, &amp; Populum</hi> — 1627</item>
               <item>124 Biſhop <hi>Montagns Apello Ceſurem,</hi> a juſt Appeal from two unjuſt Informers — 1625</item>
               <item>125 — Immediate Addreſs unto God alone — 162<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>126 <hi>Greenhills</hi> Expoſition on the five firſt Chapters of <hi>Ezekiel,</hi> Title wanting.</item>
               <item>127 <hi>Hides</hi> Chriſtianity explained under 7 Evangelical and Eccleſiaſtical Heads — 1658</item>
               <pb n="7" facs="tcp:42676:17"/>
               <item>128 <hi>Mede (Joſeph) Diatribae,</hi> Diſcourſes on divers Texts of Scripture, on ſeveral occaſions 1648</item>
               <item>129 <hi>Symmonds</hi> Vindication of King <hi>Charles</hi> the Firſt — 1648</item>
               <item>130 <hi>Swetmans</hi> School of Defence, plainly deſcribing the true knowledge of Weapons 1617</item>
               <item>131 <hi>Haywards</hi> lives of the three <hi>Norman</hi> Kings, wants a title</item>
               <item>132 <hi>Veſteg<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ns</hi> Reſtitution of decayed Intelligences in Antiquity about the <hi>Engliſh</hi> Nation 1634</item>
               <item>133 <hi>Swinnocks</hi> Door of Salvation opened by the Key of Regeneration — 1671</item>
               <item>134 <hi>Eſtwicks</hi> againſt Mr. <hi>Biddles</hi> Confeſſion of Faith, touching the Holy Trinity 1656</item>
               <item>135 <hi>Forreſters</hi> Marrow and Juice of two hundred and ſixty Scriptures — 1611</item>
               <item>136 <hi>Balls</hi> Treatiſe of Faith, ſhewing the Nature and Life of Faith — 1637</item>
               <item>137 Biſhop <hi>Whites</hi> Treatiſe of the Sabbath Day — 1635</item>
               <item>138 Dr. <hi>Woodferds</hi> Paraphraſe on the Pſalms of <hi>David</hi> — 1670</item>
               <item>139 Second and laſt Part of the Works of the faithful Servant of God Mr. <hi>Daniel Dyke</hi> 1633</item>
               <item>140 Hiſtory of Independency the two firſt Parts. — 1648</item>
               <item>141 <hi>Lithgows</hi> Travels through <hi>Europe, Aſia, and Africa</hi> — 1640</item>
               <item>142 <hi>Clavels</hi> Tables for the Forbearance, and Diſcompt of Money — 1683</item>
               <item>143 <hi>Tkorndykes</hi> juſt Weights and Meaſures — 1680</item>
               <item>144 Dr. <hi>Bucks</hi> Treatiſe of Beatitudes, or Chriſts happy Man — 1637</item>
               <item>145 <hi>Morices Diatribe</hi> and Defence of the Sacrament of the Lords Supper — 1657</item>
               <item>146 Dr. <hi>Ridleys</hi> View of the Civil and Eccleſiaſtical Law — 1639</item>
               <item>147 <hi>Kings</hi> Expoſitton on the Lords Prayer — 1628</item>
               <item>148 <hi>Shutes</hi> Judgment and Mercy, delivered in nine Sermons, with the Funeral Sermon 1645</item>
               <item>149 <hi>Pages</hi> Expoſition, with apt and profitable Notes on the Lords Prayer 1631</item>
               <item>150 <hi>Bezas</hi> Sermons on the 3 firſt Chapters of the <hi>Canticles</hi> — 1587</item>
               <item>151 <hi>Beards</hi> retractive from the <hi>Romiſh</hi> Religion — 1616</item>
               <item>152 Inſtructions for the Wars, amply, learnedly, and politiquely diſcourſing that Subject 1589</item>
               <item>153 <hi>Matchiavells</hi> Art of War. Wants a Title</item>
               <item>154 Biſhop <hi>Gardeners</hi> Declar. of ſuch Articles as <hi>George Joy</hi> hath endeavoured to confute 1546</item>
               <item>155 <hi>Pierce</hi> Plowmans Viſion, whereunto is annexed his Creed, never before printed 1561</item>
               <item>156 New Teſtament of an ancient Tranſlation, undivided, <hi>Lat.</hi> &amp; <hi>Eng.</hi> want a leaves at the beg.</item>
               <item>157 Biſhop <hi>Taylor</hi> of the ſacred Order and Offices of Offices of Epiſcopacy — 1642</item>
               <item>158 <hi>Lightfoots</hi> Temple, eſpecially as it ſtood in the days of our Saviour — 1650</item>
               <item>159 <hi>Luthers</hi> Commentary on the fifteen <hi>Pſalms</hi> called <hi>Pſalmi Graduum</hi> — 1577</item>
               <item>160 <hi>Stowes</hi> Annals of <hi>England,</hi> collected out of the moſt authentical Authors — 1592</item>
               <item>161 — Survey of <hi>London,</hi> containing the Original, Antiquity, and Deſcription thereof 1599</item>
               <item>162 <hi>Richardſons</hi> Logicians School-Maſter, or a Comment on <hi>Ramus</hi> Logick — 1629</item>
               <item>163 <hi>Baynes</hi> Commentary on the firſt Chapter of the Epiſtle St. <hi>Paul</hi> to the <hi>Epheſians</hi> 1618</item>
               <item>164 <hi>Lloyd</hi> Tragicomidie of Serpents — 1607</item>
               <item>165 <hi>Godwins</hi> Engliſh Expoſition of the <hi>Roman</hi> and <hi>Jewiſh</hi> Antiquities</item>
               <item>166 <hi>Du Moulins (Peter)</hi> Buckler of the Faith — 1623</item>
               <item>167 <hi>Gores</hi> godly and faithful Sermons preached on ſeveral occaſions — 1646</item>
               <item>168 <hi>Mayers</hi> Expoſition of the Epiſtle of St. <hi>James</hi> — 1629</item>
               <item>169 <hi>Gatakers (Thomas)</hi> Sermons</item>
               <item>170 An Anſwer to the Biſhop of <hi>Condoms</hi> Expoſition of the Catholick Faith — 1686</item>
               <item>171 <hi>Pelagius redivivus,</hi> or <hi>Pelagius</hi> raked out of the Aſhes, of <hi>Arminius</hi> and his Scholars 1626</item>
               <item>172 <hi>Nortons</hi> Orthodox Evangeliſt, wherein many evangelical Truths are diſcuſſed and clear. 1654</item>
               <item>173 <hi>Nova Francia,</hi> or the Deſcr. of that part of <hi>New France</hi> which is one Contin. with <hi>Virginia</hi> 1609</item>
               <item>174 Natures Paradox, or the innocent Impoſtor, a pleaſant <hi>Polonian</hi> Hiſt. orig. entit. <hi>Iphigenes</hi> 1652</item>
               <item>175 Biſhop of <hi>Lincolns Brutum Fulmen,</hi> or the Bull of Pope <hi>Pius</hi> the Fifth. — 1681</item>
               <item>176 <hi>Brerewoods</hi> Enquiries touching the diverſity of Languages and Religions in the World 1622</item>
               <item>177 <hi>Elderfield</hi> of Regeneration and Baptiſm — 1653</item>
               <pb n="8" facs="tcp:42676:18" rendition="simple:additions"/>
               <item>178 Dr. <hi>Muffets</hi> Healths improvement, or a diſcourſe of the Food of the Nation 1655</item>
               <item>179 The Doom, warn. all men to the Judgm. contain. all the ſtrange Prod. hap. in the World 1581</item>
               <item>180 <hi>Partheneia Sacra,</hi> a <hi>Roman</hi> Catholick, Book full of Figures — 1633</item>
               <item>181 <hi>Dalle</hi> on the right uſe of the Fathers — 1675</item>
               <item>182 <hi>Olbia,</hi> or the new Iſland diſcovered, with Religion, and Rites of Worſhip — 1660</item>
               <item>183 <hi>Morgans</hi> perfection of Horſemanſhip, drawn from Nature, Art and Practice 1607</item>
               <item>184 Second part of the Works of St. <hi>Tereſa,</hi> a <hi>Roman</hi> Catholick Book — 1675</item>
               <item>185 Dr. <hi>Donne</hi> of Self Homicide</item>
               <item>186 Dr. <hi>Moores</hi> Supplement and Defence of his Expoſition on <hi>Daniel</hi> and the <hi>Revelations</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>187 King <hi>James</hi> his Apology for the Oath of Allegiance — 1609</item>
               <item>188 Biſhop of <hi>Lincolnes</hi> Anſwer to a Catholic, who wrote againſt King <hi>James</hi>'s Apology 1609</item>
               <item>189 <hi>Sprints Caſſander Anglicus,</hi> ſhewing the neceſſity of Conf. to the Cerem. of the Church 1618</item>
               <item>190 Dr. <hi>Gibbs</hi> 31 Sermons, preached on ſeveral ſubjects and occaſions — 1677</item>
               <item>191 Hiſtory of the Quarrels of Pope <hi>Paul</hi> V. with the State of <hi>Venice</hi> — 1626</item>
               <item>192 <hi>Browning</hi> concerning publick Prayer and the Faſts of the Church — 1636</item>
               <item>193 <hi>Haywoods</hi> Life and Reign of K. <hi>Henry</hi> the Fourth, firſt part — 1599</item>
               <item>194 Dr. <hi>Owens Vindiciae Evangelicae,</hi> or myſtery of the Goſpel vindicated — 1655</item>
               <item>195 Sin diſarmed, ſhewing the loathſomeneſs thereof, by a Reverend and Judicious Div. 1654</item>
               <item>196 <hi>Taylors (Thomas)</hi> Commentary on the Epiſtle of St. <hi>Paul</hi> to <hi>Titus</hi> — 1619</item>
               <item>197 Arraignment of the whole Creature, at the Bar of Religion, Reaſon and Experience 1631</item>
               <item>198 <hi>Kilburnes</hi> Survey of the County of <hi>Kent</hi> — 1659</item>
               <item>199 Spiritual Journey of a young man to the Land of Peace — 1659</item>
               <item>200 <hi>Sclaters</hi> Expoſition, with Notes, on the Epiſtle to the <hi>Romans</hi> — 1629</item>
               <item>201 Certain Reaſons proving the lawfulneſs of the Oath of Allegiance, by <hi>R. S.</hi> 1611</item>
               <item>202 <hi>Sparkes</hi> Anſwer to Mr. <hi>John de Albines</hi> Diſcourſe againſt Hereſies — 1591</item>
               <item>203 <hi>Swadlin</hi> Scriptures vindicated from the unſound concluſions of Card. <hi>Bellarmine</hi> 1643</item>
               <item>204 Dr. <hi>Sibs</hi> Bowels opened, in divers Sermons on the <hi>Canticles</hi> — 1639</item>
               <item>205 Fountain of ancient Fiction, deſc. the Images and Statues of the Gods of the Ancients 1599</item>
               <item>206 <hi>Barclays Argenis,</hi> or the Loves of <hi>Polyarchus</hi> and <hi>Argenis</hi> — 1636</item>
               <item>207 <hi>Jackſon</hi> of the Divine Eſſence and Attributes, ſecond part — 1629</item>
               <item>208 <hi>Harris</hi> Engliſh Concord in anſwer to <hi>Becanes</hi> Engliſh <hi>Jaree</hi> — 1614</item>
               <item>209 <hi>Betts</hi> Regiment of the Curch, as it is agreeable with Scriptures, Antiquities &amp;c. 1606</item>
               <item>210 <hi>Luther</hi> on the <hi>Galathians.</hi> wants a Title</item>
               <item>211 Biſhop <hi>Reynolds</hi> Explication of the 110 <hi>Pſalm</hi> — 1632</item>
               <item>212 A Defence of the Articles of the Proteſtant Religion — 1601</item>
               <item>213 <hi>Squires</hi> Expoſition on the firſt part of the ſecond Chapter of St. <hi>Paul</hi> to the <hi>Theſſal.</hi> 1630</item>
               <item>214 <hi>Godwins (John)</hi> Expoſition on the ninth Chapter of the Epiſtle to the <hi>Romans</hi> 1653</item>
               <item>215 — <hi>Imputatio fidei,</hi> or a Treatiſe of Juſtification — 1642</item>
               <item>216 <hi>Yarrantons Englands</hi> Improvement by Sea and Land, 2 parts — 1677</item>
               <item>217 <hi>Randalls</hi> 29 Lectures of the Church, for the Conſolation of Gods people 1631</item>
               <item>218 <hi>Wottons</hi> Sermons on part of the firſt Chapter of the Goſpel of St. <hi>John</hi> — 1609</item>
               <item>219 Dr. <hi>Tilleſlys</hi> Animadverſions on Mr. <hi>Seldens</hi> Hiſtory of Tythes — 1629</item>
               <item>220 <hi>Jackſons (Tho)</hi> Commentories on the Apoſtles Creed — 1613</item>
               <item>221 <hi>Wiſeman</hi> (Sir <hi>Will.</hi>) Chriſtian Knight, compiled for the Weal of <hi>England, Scotland,</hi> &amp;c. 1619</item>
               <item>222 An Ancidote againſt the peſtiferous writing of all <hi>Engl.</hi> Sectaries. A Catholick Book 1615</item>
               <item>223 <hi>Readings</hi> Guide to the Holy City — 1651</item>
               <item>224 <hi>Scots</hi> Diſcovery of Witchcraft — 1684</item>
               <item>225 Love and Valour. A Romance — 1638</item>
               <item>226 <hi>Whites</hi> Orthodox Faith, and way to the true Church, Explained and Juſtified 1619</item>
               <item>227 B. <hi>Reyn lds</hi> 3 Treatiſes of the Van of the Creature, Life of Chriſt, and ſinfulneſs of Sin 1651</item>
               <pb n="9" facs="tcp:42676:18"/>
               <item>228 Lord <hi>Napiers</hi> plain diſcovery of the whole <hi>Revelation</hi> of St. <hi>John</hi> — 1651</item>
               <item>229 <hi>Platts</hi> Jewel houſe of Art and Nature, containing divers profitable inventions 1594</item>
               <item>230 Dr. <hi>Venners Via Recta ad Vitam Longam</hi> — 1622</item>
               <item>231 <hi>Edwards</hi> 1 and 2 part of <hi>Gangraena,</hi> or diſcov. of Errors, Hereſies, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> of the Sectaries 1646</item>
               <item>232 Examination of Mens Wits — 1616</item>
               <item>233 Dr. <hi>Crakanthorps</hi> Defence of <hi>Conſtantine,</hi> with a Treatiſe of the Popes Monarchy 1621</item>
               <item>234 <hi>Parrs</hi> Expoſition on the 8, 9, 10, 11 Chapters of St. <hi>Paul</hi> to the <hi>Romans</hi> 1618</item>
               <item>235 <hi>Il Paſtor Fido,</hi> the Faithful Shepherd — 1647</item>
               <item>236 Biſhop <hi>Lucys</hi> Obſervations, Cenſures and Confutations of Mr. <hi>Hobbes Leviathan</hi> 1663</item>
               <item>237 <hi>Swediſh</hi> Intelligencer</item>
               <item>238 <hi>Ramſeys</hi> ſummary of Sermons, preached in ſeveral places, and on ſundry occaſions 1659</item>
               <item>239 <hi>Singlars Hydroſtaticks,</hi> or the weight, force, and preſſure of fluid Bodies 1672</item>
               <item>240 Sir <hi>Henry Vanes</hi> Retired mans Meditations, or the myſtery and power of Godlineſs 1655</item>
               <item>241 Dr. <hi>Heylins</hi> Hiſtory of that famous Saint and Souldier of Chriſt, St. <hi>George</hi> of <hi>Cappadocia</hi> 1631</item>
               <item>242 <hi>Owen Harrys</hi> Genealogy of the high and mighty Monarch K. <hi>James,</hi> from <hi>Noah</hi> 1604</item>
               <item>243 <hi>Glanvils Scepſis Scientifica,</hi> or confeſt Ignorance they way to Science — 1665</item>
               <item>244 <hi>Warren Jews</hi> Sabbath antiquated, and the Lords day inſtituted — 1659</item>
               <item>245 Sir <hi>Henry Wottons</hi> Elements of Architecture — 1624</item>
               <item>246 <hi>Randalls</hi> eleven Sermons on the eighth of the <hi>Romans</hi> — 1626</item>
               <item>247 Dr. <hi>Preſton</hi> of the New Covenant, or the Saints portion — 1639</item>
               <item>248 — Saints Qualifications — 1633</item>
               <item>249 — Four Godly and Learned Treatiſes — 1633</item>
               <item>250 Abridgment of the Acts and Monuments of the Church, written by Mr. <hi>John Fox</hi> 1589</item>
               <item>251 <hi>Weemſe</hi> of the 4 degenerate Sons, Atheiſt, Magician, Idolater and Jew 1636</item>
               <item>252 — Chriſtian Synagogue — 1630</item>
               <item>253 — Portraicture of the Image of God in man — 1627</item>
               <item>254 A Deſcription of the Royal Government of the Children of <hi>Iſrael,</hi> from their departure out of <hi>Egypt,</hi> until their laſt and final Captivation and Diſperſion, a Manuſcr. fairly writ.</item>
               <item>255 <hi>Sheldons</hi> Motives for his juſt, voluntary, and free Renouncing the <hi>Rom.</hi> Cath. Religion 1610</item>
               <item>256 <hi>Camdens</hi> Remains, concerning <hi>Great Britain</hi> — 1623</item>
               <item>257 <hi>Wilſons</hi> Art of Rhetorick and Logick, bound up together — 1580</item>
               <item>258 <hi>Brownes</hi> Travels in <hi>Hungaria, Servia, Bulgaria, Macedonia, Theſſaly, Auſtria,</hi> &amp;c. 1673</item>
               <item>259 <hi>Struys</hi> Voyages, through <hi>Italy, Greece, Lifeland,</hi> &amp;c. full of Figures and Maps 1683</item>
               <item>260 The Prophecy of K. <hi>Cadwal.</hi> and of <hi>Merlin, Beid, Berlington, Rymer, Waldhave, Sybilla,</hi> &amp;c. 1620</item>
               <item>261 Dr. <hi>Stillingfleets</hi> Unreaſonableneſs of Separation — 1681</item>
            </list>
         </div>
         <div type="catalogue">
            <head>Divinity, Hiſtory, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> in Octavo.</head>
            <list>
               <item>1 <hi>AGrippas</hi> Vanity of Arts and Sciences — 1679</item>
               <item>2 Antiq. of <hi>Exeter,</hi> giv. an acc. of the Laws and Cuſtomes of the place, by <hi>R. Iſacke</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>3 <hi>France</hi> painted to the Life, by a Learned and Impartial hand — 1657</item>
               <item>4 Dr. <hi>Barrows</hi> Duty and Reward of Bounty — 1671</item>
               <item>5 — Of Contentment, Patience, and reſignation to the Divine Will — 1685</item>
               <item>6 — <hi>Euclids</hi> Elements, the whole 15 Books compendiouſly demonſtrated 1686</item>
               <item>7 Dr. <hi>Aylets</hi> Divine Speculations in metrical numbers upon various ſubjects 1654</item>
               <item>8 <hi>Bromes Horace,</hi> conſiſting of Odes, Satyrs, and Epiſtles — 1680</item>
               <item>9 <hi>Smyths</hi> Rhetorick unveiled — 1665</item>
               <item>10 Monarchy aſſerted to be the beſt, moſt ancient, and legal form of Government 1660</item>
               <item>11 The Lords Day, or a ſuccinct Narration, compiled out of the H. Script. and Anc. Fath. 1672</item>
               <item>12 Art of Gardening, in 3 Books, illuſtrated with Sculptures, repreſ. the form of Gardens 1677</item>
               <pb n="10" facs="tcp:42676:19"/>
               <item>13 <hi>Angels</hi> right government of Thoughts — 1659</item>
               <item>14 <hi>Antoninus</hi> the <hi>Roman</hi> Emperours Meditations concerning himſelf — 1673</item>
               <item>15 <hi>Howels</hi> Familiar Letters, Domeſtick and Foreign, in 4 Books — 1673</item>
               <item>16 <hi>Bromes</hi> Poems and Songs — 1664</item>
               <item>17 Dr. <hi>Barrows</hi> ſeveral Sermons againſt evil ſpeaking — 1678</item>
               <item>18 <hi>Bilſons</hi> difference between Chriſtian Subjection and Antichriſtian-Rebellion 1586</item>
               <item>19 Reply to an Anſwer to Dr. <hi>More</hi>'s Antidote againſt Idolatry — 1672</item>
               <item>20 <hi>Indiculus Univerſalis,</hi> or the Univerſe in Epitome, in <hi>Engliſh, Latine,</hi> and <hi>French</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>21 <hi>Hinchleys</hi> Letters on ſeveral Occaſions — 1680</item>
               <item>22 Journey into <hi>Spain</hi> — 1670</item>
               <item>23 Right of Succeſſion aſſert. againſt the Seditious inſinuations of <hi>R. Dolman</hi> and others 1683</item>
               <item>24 <hi>Du-Veil</hi>'s Expoſition, of the Acts of the Holy Apoſtles — 1685</item>
               <item>25 <hi>Leybornes</hi> Arithmetick, Vulgar, Decimal, Inſtrumental, and Algebraical. 3d. edition</item>
               <item>26 Dr. <hi>Featleys</hi> Hand-maid to private Devotion — 1675</item>
               <item>27 <hi>Boyles</hi> occaſional Reflexions on ſeveral Subjects — 1665</item>
               <item>28 <hi>Cottoni Poſtruma,</hi> divers pieces ab. the right and power of the Lords and Com. in Par. 1679</item>
               <item>29 <hi>Herns</hi> account of the Noble Foundation of the Charter Houſe — 1677</item>
               <item>30 <hi>Hanmers</hi> Exercitation about Confirmation — 1658</item>
               <item>31 Biſhop <hi>Halls</hi> Honour of the married Clergy — 1620</item>
               <item>32 Unfortunate Heroes, or the adventures of 10 Famous men, in 10 Novels 1679</item>
               <item>33 Dr. <hi>Tillotſons</hi> Sermons, preached on ſeveral Occaſions. firſt Volume — 1671</item>
               <item>34 <hi>Wallers</hi> Poems, written on ſeveral Occaſions, and to ſeveral Perſons — 1664</item>
               <item>35 <hi>Charnocks</hi> Diſcourſe of Divine providence — 1685</item>
               <item>36 <hi>Gouges</hi> Chriſtian directions, ſhewing how to walk with God all the day long 1680</item>
               <item>37 Dr. <hi>Pullers</hi> Moderation of the Church of <hi>England</hi> — 1679</item>
               <item>38 <hi>Bacons</hi> Cure of Old Age, and preſervation of Youth, alſo an account of the Tree of Life 1683</item>
               <item>39 <hi>Cokes</hi> Art of Logick, or the entire Body of Logick in <hi>Engliſh</hi> — 1654</item>
               <item>40 <hi>Theopolis,</hi> or the City of God new <hi>Jeruſalem</hi> — 1670</item>
               <item>41 <hi>Brinſlys</hi> true watch, and Rule of Life. A direction for examining our ſpiritual eſtate 1619</item>
               <item>42 <hi>Crookes</hi> Guide to Bleſſedneſs. Brief directions to true happineſs. Turky Leather 1614</item>
               <item>43 <hi>Blagraves</hi> ſupplement to Mr. <hi>Culpepers Engliſh</hi> Phyſician — 1677</item>
               <item>44 Sr. <hi>Roger L'Eſtranges</hi> Tranſlation of 20 Select Colloquies out of <hi>Eraſmus</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>45 <hi>Dykes (Jer.)</hi> Righteous mans Tower — 1641</item>
               <item>46 <hi>Durants</hi> Cluſter of Grapes, or Comfort and Counſel for believing ſouls — 1660</item>
               <item>47 <hi>Capel</hi> of Tentations, their Nature, Danger, and Cure — 1650</item>
               <item>48 Dr. <hi>Fowles</hi> deſign of Chriſtianity — 1676</item>
               <item>49 Biſhop <hi>Parker</hi> diſcourſe of Eccleſiaſtical Polity — 1670</item>
               <item>50 — Defence and continuation of Eccleſiaſtical Polity, with a Letter from Dr. <hi>Patrick</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>51 The tears of the <hi>Indians,</hi> being an acc. of the Maſſacres and ſlaughters by the <hi>Span.</hi> 1656</item>
               <item>52 <hi>Brownes</hi> compleat Treatiſe of preternatural Tumors, both general and particular 1678</item>
               <item>53 <hi>Combers</hi> Companion to the Altar, or an help to the worthy receiving the L.s Supper 1681</item>
               <item>54 Confeſſion of the Miniſters or Paſtors within the United Prov. called Remonſtrants 1676</item>
               <item>55 <hi>Culpepers</hi> School of Phyſick, or the Experimental practice of the whole Art of Phyſick 1678</item>
               <item>56 Dr <hi>Fullers</hi> Triple Reconciler — 1654</item>
               <item>57 <hi>Fenners</hi> Treatiſe of Affections, or the Souls pulſe — 1642</item>
               <item>58 — Wilful impenitency the groſſeſt ſelf-murther — 1650</item>
               <item>59 <hi>Fald's</hi> Quakeriſm no Chriſtianity — 1673</item>
               <item>60 <hi>La Picara,</hi> or the Triumphs of Female ſubtilty — 1665</item>
               <item>61 <hi>Epheſian</hi> and <hi>Cimmerian</hi> Matrons 2 notable Examples of the power of Love and Wit 1668</item>
               <item>62 <hi>Elborows</hi> Reaſonablen. of our Chriſtian Service, as it is contained in the Com. Prayer 1677</item>
               <pb n="11" facs="tcp:42676:19"/>
               <item>63 <hi>Roſes</hi> School of Inſtructions for the Officers of the Mouth, ſhew. the wh. Art of Cookery 1682</item>
               <item>64 The Rehearſal Tranſproſed — 1672</item>
               <item>65 Biſhop <hi>Parpers</hi> Reproof to the Rehearſal Tranſproſed — 1673</item>
               <item>66 <hi>Engliſh</hi> Adventures, by a Perſon of Honour — 1676</item>
               <item>67 Mrs. <hi>Behns</hi> Poems on ſeveral occaſions, with a Voyage to the Iſland of Love 1684</item>
               <item>68 <hi>Reynolds</hi> Flower of Fidelity, being the various Adventures of 3 Foreign Princes 1660</item>
               <item>69 <hi>Fenners</hi> Souls Looking-glaſs, with a Treatiſe of Conſcience — 1643</item>
               <item>70 <hi>Dickſons</hi> Expoſition on the Goſpel according to St. <hi>Matthew</hi> — 1651</item>
               <item>71 A door open. into Chriſtian Relig. or an account of the principal heads of Religion 1662</item>
               <item>72 Dr. <hi>Barrow</hi> on the Lords Prayer and decalogue, to which is ad. the Doct. of the Sacr. 1681</item>
               <item>73 <hi>Herberts</hi> Country Parſon, his Character and Rule of Holy Life — 1679</item>
               <item>74 Sir <hi>Tho. Moores</hi> Commonwealth of <hi>Utopia</hi> — 1639</item>
               <item>75 Biſhop <hi>Wards</hi> Sermon againſt the Antiſcripturiſts, and another againſt Infidelity 1670</item>
               <item>76 Dr. <hi>Hammonds</hi> Practical Catechiſm — 1655</item>
               <item>77 — Aſſertion of the Exiſtence and Duration of Hell Torments — 1665</item>
               <item>78 <hi>Richardſon</hi> of the Torments of Hell — 1657</item>
               <item>79 <hi>Chewney</hi> of Hell, with the everlaſting torments thereof aſſerted — 1660</item>
               <item>80 The Merchants daily Companion — 1684</item>
               <item>81 <hi>Lillys</hi> ſix Court Comedies Acted before Queen <hi>Elizabeth</hi> — 1632</item>
               <item>82 The Country Captain, and the Variety, 2 Comedies, by a Perſon of Honour. — 1649</item>
               <item>83 The Politicks of <hi>France</hi> — 1680</item>
               <item>84 <hi>Britaniae Speculum,</hi> or a ſhort view of the Ancient and Modern State of <hi>Great Britain</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>85 <hi>Clavels</hi> Tables for the forbearance and diſcompt of Money — 1653</item>
               <item>86 <hi>Polidore Virgils</hi> Works, containing the Original of all Arts, Sciences, Myſteries, &amp;c. 1663</item>
               <item>87 Sir <hi>Thomas Overburies</hi> Wife, with the addition of new Characters and Conceits 1638</item>
               <item>88 <hi>Randolphs</hi> Poems — 1652</item>
               <item>89 Dr. <hi>Donnes</hi> Poems, with Elegies on the Authors Death — 1639</item>
               <item>90 London Jilt, or the Politick Whore, in 2 parts compleat — 1683</item>
               <item>91 Sir <hi>Geo. Machenzie</hi> of Moral Gallantry, endeav. to prove that hon. oblig. men to be virtuous</item>
               <item>92 Dr. <hi>Hammond</hi> of Schiſm, being a Defence of the Church of <hi>England</hi> — 1654</item>
               <item>93 Biſhop <hi>Halls</hi> Reſolutions of Caſes of Conſcience, in continual uſe amongſt men 1650</item>
               <item>94 <hi>Jackſons</hi> Pedigree and Perigrination of <hi>Iſrael</hi> — 1649</item>
               <item>95 <hi>Parſons</hi> Treatiſe of the Three Converſions of <hi>England,</hi> from Paganiſm to Chriſtianity 1603</item>
               <item>96 Court of Curioſity, wherein the moſt intricate Queſtions are reſolved — 1681</item>
               <item>97 Sir <hi>Kenelin Digbys</hi> Receipts of Phyſick and Cookery — 1668</item>
               <item>98 — Diſcourſe made in an Aſſembly of Nobles, &amp;c. about the powder of Sympathy 1658</item>
               <item>99 Sir <hi>Tho. Smith</hi> of the Commonwealth of <hi>England</hi> — 1633</item>
               <item>100 B. <hi>Ward</hi> Philoſophical Eſſay, to Evict the Attributes of God, immortality of the Soul <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>101 Dr. <hi>Cowells</hi> Inſtitutes of the Laws of <hi>England</hi> — 1651</item>
               <item>102 <hi>Darys</hi> Intereſt Epitomiz'd, both ſimple and compound — 1677</item>
               <item>103 <hi>Beraults</hi> Noſegay, or Miſcellany of Divine Truths, <hi>Engliſh</hi> and <hi>French</hi> — 1684</item>
               <item>104 <hi>Corbets</hi> Intereſt of <hi>England</hi> in matter of Religion, in 2 parts — 1661</item>
               <item>105 <hi>Ingelo</hi> of the Perfection, Authority, and Credulity, of the Holy Scriptures 1659</item>
               <item>106 Archbiſhop <hi>Lauds</hi> ſeven Sermons — 1651</item>
               <item>107 <hi>Bovets</hi> Pandaemonium, or the Devils cloyſter, being a further blow to modern Sadduciſm</item>
               <item>108 <hi>Madamoiſelle de Scudrys</hi> converſations on ſeveral Subjects — 1683</item>
               <item>109 <hi>Quevedos</hi> Novels, to which is added the marriage of <hi>Belphegor</hi> — 1671</item>
               <item>110 Sir <hi>H. Wottons</hi> Remains, being a collection of Lives, Letters, and Poems, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1651</item>
               <item>111 Biſhop <hi>Halls</hi> Treatiſe of Contentation — 1684</item>
               <item>112 — contemplations on the Hiſtorical part of Old Teſtament. eighth and laſt Volume 1626</item>
               <pb n="12" facs="tcp:42676:20"/>
               <item>113 — Select Thoughts, or choice helps for a Pious Spirit — 1682</item>
               <item>114 — Satans Fiery Darts Quenched, or Temptations Repelled — 1674</item>
               <item>115 — Soliloquies, or Holy ſelf conferences of the Devout Soul — 1651</item>
               <item>116 — Peace-maker, laying down the right way of Peace — 1645</item>
               <item>117 — Devout Soul, or Rules of Heavenly Devotion — 1650</item>
               <item>118 Diſcourſe of the period of Humane Life, with the defence and continuation 1677</item>
               <item>119 Gentele ſinner, or <hi>Englands</hi> brave Gentleman. wants a title</item>
               <item>120 Dr. <hi>Hammond</hi> of Fundamentals in a notion referring to practice — 1654</item>
               <item>121 <hi>Scudders</hi> Key of Heaven, or the Lords Prayer opened — 1633</item>
               <item>122 <hi>Ciceros</hi> three Books touching the nature of the Gods — 1683</item>
               <item>123 <hi>Whites</hi> middle ſtate of Souls from Death to the day of Judgment — 1659</item>
               <item>124 Fort Royal of Holy Scriptures — 1656</item>
               <item>125 <hi>Raymonds</hi> Itinerary, containing a Voyage made through <hi>Italy</hi> — 1648</item>
               <item>126 <hi>Matchiavels</hi> diſcourſes upon the firſt Decade of <hi>T. Livius,</hi> to which is added his Prince 1663</item>
               <item>127 The School of the Heart in forty ſeven Emblemes — 1676</item>
               <item>128 <hi>Quarles (John)</hi> Poems on Gods love and Mans unworthineſs — 1675</item>
               <item>129 <hi>Poor Robins</hi> Jeſts, or the compleat Jeſter — 1670</item>
               <item>130 <hi>Eraſmus's Encomium moriae,</hi> or the praiſe of folly — 1668</item>
               <item>131 Dr. <hi>Patricks</hi> devout Chriſtian inſtructed how to pray and give thanks to God 1686</item>
               <item>132 Two diſcourſes for the furthering Chriſtian Piety and Devotion — 1671</item>
               <item>133 <hi>Hammends</hi> Letter of Reſolution to ſix Queries of preſent uſe in the Church of <hi>England</hi> 1653</item>
               <item>134 A proſpect of Divine Providence, by <hi>T. C.</hi> — 1672</item>
               <item>135 <hi>Gees</hi> divine right and original of the civil Magiſtrate from God — 1658</item>
               <item>136 <hi>Graunts</hi> natural and political Obſervations upon the Bills of Mortality — 1665</item>
               <item>137 The grandeur of the Law, or a coll. of the Nobility, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> whoſe Eſtates have been acq. by Law</item>
               <item>138 <hi>Flavels</hi> two Treatiſes, one of Fear, the other the righteous mans refuge 1682</item>
               <item>139 <hi>Londinum Triumphans,</hi> or an hiſtorical account of the City of <hi>London</hi> — 1682</item>
               <item>140 <hi>Fenners</hi> practical Divinity in ſeveral choice Sermons on divers Texts — 1649</item>
               <item>141 <hi>Faldos</hi> Quakeriſm no Chriſtianity — 1673</item>
               <item>142 <hi>Johnſons</hi> novelty repreſt, in a reply to Mr. <hi>Baxters</hi> anſwer to <hi>W. Johnſon</hi> 1661</item>
               <item>143 Sir <hi>Hugh Plats</hi> Garden of <hi>Eden</hi> — 1675</item>
               <item>144 Love of Heavens Glory and Hells Terror — 1671</item>
               <item>145 <hi>Gaffarels</hi> unheard of curioſities — 1650</item>
               <item>146 The Engliſh Rogue deſcribed in the life of <hi>Meriton Latroon,</hi> the two laſt parts. 1668</item>
               <item>147 <hi>Brittaniae Speculum,</hi> or a ſhort view of the antient and modern State of <hi>Great Brittain</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>148 Dr. <hi>Moors</hi> divine Dialogues conc. the Attributes and Providence of God, comp. 2 Vol. 1668</item>
               <item>149 <hi>Heskeths</hi> exhortation to frequent receiving the Sacrament of the Lords Supper 1684</item>
               <item>150 Dr. <hi>Hammonds Paraeneſis,</hi> ſeaſonable exhortations to all true Sons of the Ch. of <hi>England</hi> 1656</item>
               <item>151 Dr. <hi>Patricks</hi> friendly debate between a Conf. and a Nonconf. in three parts, with an App.</item>
               <item>152 Dr. <hi>Camberlaines</hi> preſent ſtate of <hi>England</hi> — 1627</item>
               <item>153 Remarques on the humors and converſations of the Gallants of the Town 1673</item>
               <item>154 The Pilgrim, a pleaſant piece of gallantry, in two parts. — 1680</item>
               <item>155 Dr. <hi>Heylins</hi> help to Engliſh Hiſtory, containing the ſucceſſion of all the Kings of <hi>England</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>156 An exhortation to all men to take heed of Rebellion, Dedicated to the moſt ex. Q. <hi>Mary</hi> 1554</item>
               <item>157 The Spiritual Exerciſes of the moſt vertuous and religious <hi>D. Gertude More Paris</hi> 1658</item>
               <item>158 Catalogue of the names of the Parliament Men from 1640. to 1661</item>
               <item>159 Memoires of the Family of the <hi>Stuarts,</hi> the remarkable providence of God two. them 1683</item>
               <item>160 Gods love to mankind, by diſproving his abſolute decrees for their damnation 1673</item>
               <item>161 Biſhop <hi>Halls</hi> occaſional Meditations — 1634</item>
               <item>162 —Heaven on Earth: And Art of Divine Meditation, two books bound up together 1606</item>
               <pb n="13" facs="tcp:42676:20" rendition="simple:additions"/>
               <item>163 <hi>Truemans</hi> great propitiation, or Chriſts ſatisfaction — 1672</item>
               <item>164 <hi>Relique ſacrae Carolinae,</hi> or the Works of the glorious Martyr King <hi>Charles</hi> the Firſt 1650</item>
               <item>165 Image of both Churches, diſcuſſing whether Catholicks or Proteſtants are better Subjects.</item>
               <item>166 Biſhop <hi>Sparrows</hi> Rationale on the Book of Common-Prayer of the Church of <hi>England</hi> 1676</item>
               <item>166 The <hi>Calviniſts</hi> Cabinet unlocked — 1659</item>
               <item>167 <hi>Wilſons</hi> Scripture genuine Interpreter aſſerted — 1678</item>
               <item>168 <hi>Webbs</hi> Eſſay to ſhew the probability that the Language of <hi>China</hi> is the Primitive 1669</item>
               <item>169 Sir <hi>Charles Woſleys</hi> unreaſonableneſs of Atheiſm — 1669</item>
               <item>170 <hi>Villiers Vocabularium Anologicum,</hi> Engliſh Man ſpeaking <hi>French,</hi> &amp; French-Man <hi>Engliſh</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>171 The highneſt and chiefeſtwork of a Chriſtian, by <hi>J. W.</hi> — 1668</item>
               <item>172 <hi>Terrys</hi> Voyage to <hi>Eaſt-India,</hi> deſcribing the rich and ſpacious Emp. of the great Mogol 1655</item>
               <item>173 A Conference between a rich Alderman and a poor Country Vicar, about obligat. of Oaths</item>
               <item>174 <hi>Playfords</hi> Intruduction to the skill of Muſick — 1679</item>
               <item>175 <hi>Harmony</hi> of Natural, Moral, and Poſitive Laws — 1682</item>
               <item>176 Dr. <hi>Ingelos</hi> diſcourſe concerning Repentance — 1677</item>
               <item>177 —Of the Perfection, Authority and Credibility of the Holy Scriptures — 1659</item>
               <item>178 <hi>Le Grands</hi> Man without Paſſion, or the wiſe Stoick, according to <hi>Seneca</hi> — 1675</item>
               <item>179 <hi>Samwayes</hi> Devotion digeſted in Meditations on the Lords Prayer — 1652</item>
               <item>180 Doctrine of Devils, an Eſſay to rectifie thoſe undue Notions of Demons and Spirits 1676</item>
               <item>181 <hi>Boyles</hi> Tracts, to which is prefixt an Introduction to the Hiſtory of particular qualities 1671</item>
               <item>182 A Diſcourſe concerning the beauty of Holineſs — 1683</item>
               <item>183 <hi>Brightmans</hi> Expoſition of the Revelation of St. <hi>John</hi> — 1616</item>
               <item>184 <hi>Symmonds</hi> Caſe and Cure of a deſerted Soul — 1641</item>
               <item>185 <hi>Goodwyn (Phil.)</hi> Evangelical Communicant, in the Euchariſtical Sacrament 1649</item>
               <item>186 Dr. <hi>Pierces</hi> ſinner impleaded in his own Court — 1660</item>
               <item>187 Dr. <hi>Waltons</hi> Conſiderator conſidered, or a view of certain conſider. on the <hi>Biblia Polyglotta</hi>
               </item>
               <item>188 <hi>Hoards</hi> Souls miſery and recovery — 1636</item>
               <item>189 Reconciler of the <hi>Bible,</hi> wherein above 2000 ſeeming contradictions are reconciled 1656</item>
               <item>190 Lord <hi>Bacons</hi> Eſſays or Counſels, Civil and Moral — 1663</item>
               <item>191 —Hiſtory Natural, Moral and Experimental of Life and Death — 1638</item>
               <item>192 Artificial Imbelliſhments, or the beſt directions to preſerve Beauty and procure it 1665</item>
               <item>193 Buckler of State and Juſtice againſt the deſign of the univerſal Monarchy — 1673</item>
               <item>194 The Reſolver, or curioſities of Nature</item>
               <item>195 <hi>Wrights</hi> five Sermons, in five ſeveral ſtiles or ways of preaching — 1656</item>
               <item>196 Dr. <hi>Buſhels Coſmo-meros,</hi> or the worldly portion — 1682</item>
               <item>197 <hi>Craſhaws</hi> ſteps to the Temple 1648 <hi>Herberts</hi> Poems 1656. bound together</item>
               <item>198 Delights for the Ingenious, in above fifty ſelect choice Emblems — 1684</item>
               <item>199 <hi>Hierocles</hi> upon the Golden Verſes of <hi>Pythagoras</hi>
               </item>
               <item>200 Catholiciſm: or ſeverl Enq. touching Viſible Church-memberſhip, Ch.-Communion, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>201 The Grand Prerogative of Humane Nature, namely the Souls Immortality 1653</item>
               <item>202 <hi>Pelecanicidium,</hi> or the Chriſtian Adviſer againſt Self-murther — 1653</item>
               <item>203 <hi>Howards</hi> Brittiſh Princes, an Heroick Poem — 1669</item>
               <item>204 Sir <hi>John Haywards</hi> Life and Reign of <hi>Edward</hi> VI. and the beginning of Q. <hi>Elizabeths</hi> reign 1636</item>
               <item>205 <hi>Gearings</hi> Eye and Wheel of Providence — 1662</item>
               <item>206 <hi>Bulwers</hi> natural Language of the Hand, compoſed of the ſpeaking motions 1640</item>
               <item>207 Biſhop <hi>Bramhalls</hi> Replication to the Biſh. of <hi>Chalcedons</hi> Survey of the Vind. of the Ch. of <hi>Engl.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>208 Animadver. on a Book entit. Fanaticiſm fanatically imputed to the Catholick Church. 1674</item>
               <item>209 <hi>Glanvils</hi> vanity of dogmatizing, or confidence in Opinions — 1661</item>
               <item>210 <hi>Aſhwels</hi> diſcourſe, aſſerting the received Authors and Authority of the Apoſtles Creed 1653</item>
               <item>211 <hi>Glanvils</hi> way to happineſs, repreſented in its difficulties and incouragements 1670</item>
               <pb n="14" facs="tcp:42676:21"/>
               <item>212 <hi>Clanſtrum Animae,</hi> the reformed Monaſtery, or the love of Jeſus — 1677</item>
               <item>213 <hi>Engliſh</hi> Military Diſcipline, or the way and method of exerciſing Horſe and Foot 1680</item>
               <item>214 <hi>Brittaniae Speculum,</hi> or a ſhort view of the antient and modern ſtate of <hi>Great Britain</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>215 <hi>Boyles</hi> Enquiry into the vulgarly received notion of Nature — 1686</item>
               <item>216 —Memories for the natural experimental Hiſtory of Mineral Waters — 1685</item>
               <item>217 Sir <hi>Tho. Browns Religio Medici,</hi> with the Annotat. aad Obſervat. of Sir <hi>Kenelm Digby</hi> 1680</item>
               <item>218 —Certain Miſcellany Tracts — 1684</item>
               <item>219 The Famous <hi>Chinois,</hi> or the loves of ſeveral of the French Nobility — 1669</item>
               <item>220 Dr. <hi>Mores</hi> Platonical Songs of the Soul, conſiſting of four ſeveral Poems — 1642</item>
               <item>221 <hi>Petits</hi> Viſions of the Reformation — 1683</item>
               <item>222 —Of Purgatory — 1680</item>
               <item>223 Dr. <hi>Caves</hi> diſſertation concering the Government of the ancient Church 1683</item>
               <item>224 <hi>M.Cs.</hi> Apology for the Church of <hi>England,</hi> with a decl. of the true Religion of the ſame 1564</item>
               <item>225 The Piety of <hi>Paris,</hi> which repr<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>in ſhort the pious practices of the whole Cath. Church 1666</item>
               <item>226 St. <hi>Pauls</hi> late progreſs upon Earth, by <hi>J. H.</hi> — 1644</item>
               <item>227 Dr. <hi>Lindeſays</hi> Reaſons for kneeling at the receiving the Holy Communion. — 1659</item>
               <item>228 <hi>Cottoni Poſthuma,</hi> divers choice pieces of that renowned Antiquary Sir <hi>Robert Cotton</hi> 1679</item>
               <item>229 <hi>Graftons</hi> abridgment of the Chronicles of <hi>England</hi> — 1570</item>
               <item>230 Boulſter Lectures, ſtored with variety of witty Jeſts, merry Tales, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1640</item>
               <item>231 Preſent State of <hi>France,</hi> concerning the orders, dignites and charges of that Kingdom 1671</item>
               <item>232 Biſhop <hi>Andrews</hi> Manual of Private Devotions and Meditations — 1682</item>
               <item>233 <hi>Goodwins (Thom.)</hi> return of Prayers — 1641</item>
               <item>234 Meditations upon the marks of the true Church of Chriſt — <hi>Paris</hi> 1655</item>
               <item>235 <hi>Hickmans</hi> Juſtification of the Fathers and Schoolmen — 1659</item>
               <item>236 <hi>Cornalius Agrippas</hi> Vanity of Arts and Sciences — 1676</item>
               <item>237 The Royal Charter granted unto Kings by God himſelf, written by <hi>T. B.</hi> 1649</item>
               <item>238 An endeavour to rectifie ſome prevailing Opinions cont. to the Doctr. of the Ch. of <hi>Engl.</hi> 1671</item>
               <item>239 Biſhop of <hi>Condoms</hi> Expoſition of Doctrine of the Catholick Church — 1685</item>
               <item>240 <hi>Annands</hi> Myſtery of Godlineſs, wherein the Myſteries of Chriſt and the H. Ghoſt are unfolded</item>
               <item>241 <hi>Drexelius</hi>'s right intention the Rule of all mens actions — 1641</item>
               <item>242 <hi>Markams</hi> Perfect Horſeman, or his fifty years practice — 1684</item>
               <item>243 Dr. <hi>Sibs</hi>'s Glance of Heaven — 1638</item>
               <item>244 <hi>Leigh's</hi> Obſer. of all the Kings of <hi>Engl.</hi> from the <hi>Saxons</hi> to the death of K.C. the firſt 1661</item>
               <item>245 <hi>Capel</hi> of Tentations, their nature, danger, and cure — 1636</item>
               <item>246 <hi>Parſons</hi> Chriſtian Directory, guiding all men to their Salvation — 1685</item>
               <item>247 <hi>L'Eſtrange</hi> (Sir <hi>Roger</hi>) Tranſlat. of <hi>Seneca</hi>'s Morals, in 2 Vol. large pap. gilt and letterd 1679</item>
               <item>248 State of Chriſtianity examined, unfolded and characted — 1655</item>
               <item>249 The <hi>Roman</hi> Martyrology ſet forth by the command of Pope <hi>Gregory</hi> XIII. St. <hi>Omers</hi> 1617</item>
               <item>250 <hi>Herdſons Ars Memonica.</hi> The Art of Memory made plain — 1651</item>
               <item>251 <hi>Willis</hi>'s Art of Memory, or a certain Cure for a weak Memory — 1654</item>
               <item>252 <hi>Pallas Armata.</hi> The Gentlemans Armory, diſplaying the genuine uſe of Rapier &amp; Sword 1639</item>
               <item>253 Touchſtone for Gold and Silver Wares, or a Manual for Gold-ſmiths — 1677</item>
               <item>254 <hi>Brittaniae ſpeculum,</hi> or a ſhort view of the Antient and Modern State of <hi>Great Brittain</hi> 1683</item>
               <item>255 <hi>Leighs</hi> Deſcription of the Counties and Shires in <hi>England</hi> — 1659</item>
               <item>256 <hi>Bromes</hi> five new Playes — 1654</item>
               <item>257 <hi>Hotchkis</hi> of the imputation of Chriſts Righteouſneſs to us and out ſins — 1675</item>
               <item>258 Hiſtory of the Rights of Princes to diſp Eccleſiaſtical Benefices and Ch. Lands, by <hi>G. Burnet</hi> 1682</item>
               <item>259 —of the Reformation of the Church of <hi>England</hi> abridged, by <hi>G. Burnet</hi> — 1683</item>
               <item>260 —of <hi>Brutes,</hi> or a deſcription of living Creatures, by <hi>Wolfangus Francius</hi> — 1672</item>
               <item>261 —of the preſent ſtate of the Jews, containing an account of their Cuſtomes' <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1676</item>
               <pb n="15" facs="tcp:42676:21"/>
               <item>261 —of the <hi>Turks,</hi> containing the Lives and Reigns of their ſeveral Emperours 1683</item>
               <item>262 —of the later times of the <hi>Jews,</hi> with the deſtruction of <hi>Jeruſalem</hi> — 1684</item>
               <item>263 —of <hi>Lazarillo de Tomes,</hi> the Witty <hi>Spaniard</hi>
               </item>
               <item>264 —of ancient Ceremonies, containing an account of their riſe and growth 1669</item>
               <item>265 —of <hi>England,</hi> from the firſt traditional beginning, to the <hi>Norman</hi> Conqueſt 1677</item>
               <item>266 —of Magick, being an Apology for Wiſe men who have been unjuſtly reputed</item>
               <item>267 —of the Holy War, by the Chriſtian Princes of Europe, againſt the <hi>Turks</hi> 1685</item>
               <item>268 —of the Houſe of <hi>Eſte</hi> — 1681</item>
               <item>269 —of <hi>Aegypt,</hi> treating of the <hi>Pyramids</hi> and Inundation of <hi>Nyle</hi> and other prodigies 1672</item>
               <item>270 —of the late Revolutions of the Empire of the great <hi>Magol,</hi> with the continuation 1676</item>
               <item>271 —of the laſt Parliaments held and diſſolved at <hi>Weſtminſter</hi> and <hi>Oxford</hi> 1681</item>
               <item>272 —of <hi>Florence</hi> in 8 Books, by <hi>Nicolas Matchiavel</hi> — 1674</item>
               <item>273 —of Don <hi>Feniſe,</hi> a Romance, written in <hi>Spaniſh,</hi> and <hi>Eng.</hi> by a Perſon of Honour 1651</item>
               <item>274 —of Prince <hi>Eraſtus,</hi> and thoſe Philoſophers called the Wiſe Maſters of <hi>Rome</hi> 1674</item>
               <item>275 —of the moſt Unfortunate Prince <hi>Edward</hi> II. By <hi>H.</hi> Viſcount <hi>Falkland</hi> — 1680</item>
               <item>276 —of the Lives and Reigns of the Monarchs of <hi>England</hi> — 1679</item>
               <item>277 —of the Civil Wars of <hi>England,</hi> from 1640 to 1660. by <hi>T. H.</hi> — 1680</item>
               <item>278 —of the <hi>Romans,</hi> by <hi>Lucius J. Florus,</hi> with the Life of <hi>Romulus</hi> — 1676</item>
               <item>279 —of <hi>Spain,</hi> or a Rel. of the differences between the Court of <hi>Spain</hi> and Card. <hi>Nitard</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>280 —of Man, relate the wonders of his generat. vanities of his degenerat. neceſ. of his regener.</item>
               <item>281 —of the late Revolutions of the Empire of the great <hi>Mogul</hi> — 1671</item>
               <item>282 —of the Infamous Impo<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>tors, or the Lives and Actions of ſev. notor. Counterfeits 1683</item>
               <item>283 Life and Actions of <hi>Ath<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="4 letters">
                        <desc>••••</desc>
                     </gap>,</hi> with the riſe and downfal of the <hi>Arian</hi> Hereſie 1664</item>
               <item>284 —of St. <hi>Auguſtin.</hi> Firſt part — 1660</item>
               <item>285 —of St. <hi>Baſil</hi> the Great, and St. <hi>Chryſeſtom,</hi> drawn by way of parallel — 1681</item>
               <item>286 —of that eminent Lady <hi>Elizabeth Brook</hi> — 1684</item>
               <item>287 —of that eminently Religious and Charitable Lady, <hi>Mary,</hi> Count. Dow. of <hi>Warwick</hi> 1678</item>
               <item>288 —of Dr. <hi>Donne,</hi> Sir <hi>H. Wotton,</hi> Mr. <hi>Hooker,</hi> and Mr. <hi>Herbert,</hi> by <hi>I. Walton</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>289 —of King <hi>Richard</hi> the Second — 1681</item>
               <item>290 —of that Renowned <hi>John Fiſher,</hi> Biſhop of <hi>Recheſter</hi> — 1655</item>
               <item>291 —of the exemplary holy Mr. <hi>John Brewen</hi> — 1641</item>
               <item>292 —of Biſhop <hi>Sanderſon,</hi> with ſeveral things of his Writing — 1678</item>
               <item>293 —of <hi>Henry</hi> the Fourth, ſurnamed the Great, King of <hi>France</hi> and <hi>Navarre</hi> 1663</item>
               <item>294 —of Mr. <hi>Rich. Hooker,</hi> by <hi>J. Wal<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>en,</hi> with <hi>George Cranmers</hi> Letter unto Mr. <hi>Hooker</hi> 1665</item>
               <item>295 —of <hi>Oliver Cromwell</hi> the late Uſurper — 1663</item>
               <item>296 Mr. <hi>Scarrons</hi> Letters to perſons of the greateſt eminency — 1677</item>
               <item>297 <hi>Lucians Pharſalia,</hi> or the Civil Wars of <hi>Rome,</hi> betw. <hi>Pompey</hi> and <hi>Jul. Caeſar,</hi> Eng. by <hi>T. May</hi> 1631</item>
               <item>298 Dr. <hi>Godolphins</hi> View of the Admiral Juriſdiction, to which is added the Laws. of <hi>Oleron</hi> 1661</item>
               <item>299 Common-prayer, Concordance, and doctrine of the Bible, bound up together</item>
               <item>300 <hi>Guild's Moſes</hi> unveiled, or the figures and ſnadows pointing out the Meſſiah, expl. 1658</item>
               <item>301 The <hi>Aethiopian</hi> Hiſtory of <hi>Heliodorus,</hi> in ten Books — 1686</item>
               <item>302 Remarks on the State of the Church of the firſt Centuries, being the lives of the Fathers 1680</item>
               <item>303 Inquiries into the cauſes of the contempt of Proteſtant Religion, and Church of <hi>Engl.</hi> 1675</item>
               <item>304 <hi>Drummonds</hi> elegant and elaborate Poems — 1659</item>
               <item>305 Harmony of Confeſſions of the Faith of the Chriſtian and Reformed Churches 1586</item>
               <item>306 Dr. <hi>Hammond</hi> of Fundamentals, in a Notion refering to Practice — 1654</item>
               <item>307 —Letter to the Reverend Dr. <hi>San lerſon,</hi> concerning Gods Grace and Decrees 1660</item>
               <item>308 Biſhop <hi>Parker</hi> of Platonick Philoſophy, and pre-exiſtence of Souls — 1667</item>
               <item>309 <hi>Roſs</hi> againſt <hi>Brownes</hi> Vulg. Errors, <hi>Bacons</hi> Nat. Hiſt. and Dr. <hi>Harvey de generatione</hi> 1652</item>
               <item>310 <hi>Hernes</hi> account of the Noble Foundation of the <hi>Charter-Houſe</hi> — 1677</item>
               <pb n="16" facs="tcp:42676:22"/>
               <item>311 <hi>Herberts</hi> Country Parſons Character and Rule of Holy Life — 167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>312 <hi>Dugres</hi> Dialogues in <hi>French, Engliſh</hi> and <hi>Latin</hi> — 1660</item>
               <item>313 <hi>Bifields</hi> Marrow of the Oracles of God — 1630</item>
               <item>414 <hi>Epicurus</hi> Moralls — 1670</item>
               <item>315 <hi>Ames</hi> marrow of Sacred Divinity — 164<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>316 Annotation on the Book of <hi>Eccleſiaſtes,</hi> ſuppoſed to be by Biſhop <hi>Reynolds</hi> — 1669</item>
               <item>317 <hi>Smiths</hi> great Aſſize or day of Jubilee — 1680</item>
               <item>318 <hi>Stephens</hi> new Eſſays and Characters — 163<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>319 <hi>Craggs</hi> Royal Prerogative vindicated in the converted Recuſant — 166<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>320 <hi>Caſaubon</hi> (Dr. <hi>Meric</hi>) Treatiſe of the Enthuſiaſm — 165<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>321 Biſhop <hi>Sparrows</hi> Rationale upon the Book of <hi>Common-Prayer</hi> in the Church of <hi>England</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>322 <hi>Sleidens</hi> Key of Hiſtory, or an abridgment of the four chief Monarchies — 162<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>323 The five days debate at <hi>Ciceros</hi> houſe in <hi>Tuſ<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ulum</hi> on ſeveral Subjects — 168<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>324 The Sophy, a Play written by Sir <hi>John Denham</hi> — 167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>325 Gate of Tongues, or a Seed-plot of Tongues and Sciences, <hi>Latin, French,</hi> and <hi>Engliſh</hi> 163<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>326 <hi>Roſſes</hi> view of all Religions in the World, with the lives of Hereticks — 165<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>327 <hi>Seigniors</hi> 8 Sermons of God, the King, and the Church — 167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>328 <hi>Nertherlandiſh Heſperides,</hi> that is the management and ordering of Limon and Orange Tr. 168<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>329 Impoſtor expoſed, in a diſſection of a villanous Libel about the Black Box — 168<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>330 Humane Reaſon, and the Apology for Humane Reaſon. Two Books</item>
               <item>331 Sir <hi>Walter Raleighs</hi> Remaines — 166<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>332 Dr. <hi>Falkners</hi> Chriſtian Loyalty, and concerning Supremacy in cauſes Eccleſiaſtical — 168<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>333 Rebels no Saints, or a collection of Speeches, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> of <hi>Harriſon, Carew, Cook, Peters,</hi> &amp;c. 166<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>334 <hi>Scarrons</hi> City Romance made Engliſh — 167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>335 <hi>Records</hi> Arithmitick, or the grounds of Arts — 164<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>336 The <hi>Lancaſhire</hi> Lovers, or the excellent Hiſtory of <hi>Philocles</hi> and <hi>Doroclea</hi> — 164<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>337 A Manuel of Millions, or accounts ready caſt up to ſhew the value of any Commodit. 165<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>338 <hi>Sandys</hi> Paraphraſe on the <hi>Pſalms</hi> of <hi>David,</hi> ſet to Tunes by <hi>Henry Lawes</hi> — 167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>339 Principles and Practices of certain moderate Divines of the Church of <hi>England</hi> defend. 167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>340 Truth and Innocency vindicated, in a Survey of a Diſcourſe about Eccleſiaſt. Polity 1669</item>
               <item>341 <hi>Mayhews</hi> death of Deaths, in the death of Chriſt — 1679</item>
               <item>342 <hi>Scots</hi> Philomythy, wherein outlandiſh Birds and Fiſhes are taught to ſpeak Engliſh 1610</item>
               <item>343 Unreaſonableneſs of Separation, the Second Part — 168<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>344 <hi>Birds</hi> magazine of Honour, or a Treat. of the ſeveral degrees of Nobility of this Kingd. 164<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>345 Life of God in the Soul of Man, or the nature and excellency of the Chriſtian Religion 167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>346 <hi>Miltons</hi> Poems on ſeveral occaſions, with a Tractate of Education — 167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>347 —Paradiſe regained, a Poem in four Books — 167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>348 The Painters Voyage of <hi>Italy,</hi> giving an account of the Curioſities of that Countrey — 167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>349 A Perſwaſive to Conformity, in a Letter to the diſſenting Brethren — 167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>350 The Nature, Power, and Deceit, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> of indwelling in ſin — 166<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>351 <hi>Medulla Medicinae,</hi> or a Plea for the free Profeſſion of the Art of Phyſick — 166<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>352 A full Anſwer to that Queſtion, What is the Church of <hi>England?</hi> — 168<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>353 St <hi>Chryſoſtom</hi>'s golden Book of the Education of Children — 165<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>354 Dr <hi>Playferes</hi> Sermons — 162<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>355 A Diſcourſe of Auxiliary Beauty, or Artificial Handſomneſs — 165<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>356 An Hiſtorical diſcourſe of the Original and Growth of Heraldry, by <hi>Tho. Philipot</hi> 167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>357 <hi>Waterhouſes</hi> defence of Arms and Armory, ſhew. the riſe of honour and Arms in <hi>Engl.</hi> 16<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>358 <hi>Roberts</hi> way to the Tree of Life, or the natural man directed to Chriſt 167<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>359 <hi>John Foxes</hi> Sermon of Chriſt Crucified — 16<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>360 <hi>Greenhills</hi> Sermons, of Chrſt his laſt diſcovery of Himſelf</item>
               <pb n="21" facs="tcp:42676:22"/>
               <item>361 <hi>Nalſons</hi> common intereſt of K. and people, ſhewing the Original of Monarchy 1678</item>
               <item>362 <hi>Traherns</hi> Chriſtian Ethicks, or Divine Morality — 1675</item>
               <item>363 Dr. <hi>Roberts</hi> Communicant Inſtructed, or directions for receiving the Sacrament 1678</item>
               <item>364 Dr. <hi>Cudworths</hi> Diſcourſe concerning the true notion of the Lords Supper 1670</item>
               <item>365 <hi>Quarles</hi> Emblems — 1684</item>
               <item>366 Dr. <hi>Stillingfleets</hi> and <hi>Burnets</hi> Conference about Relig. with ſome Gent. of the <hi>Romiſh</hi> Church</item>
               <item>367 Biſhop <hi>Wilkins</hi> Sermons on ſeveral occaſions — 1682</item>
               <item>368 — Sermons, with the Beauty of Providence at the end — 1680</item>
               <item>369 <hi>Wadſworths</hi> Remains, being a collection of Meditations on the Sacrament 1680</item>
               <item>370 Biſhop <hi>Jewels</hi> Sermons, preached before the Queen at <hi>Pauls</hi> Croſs — 1583</item>
               <item>371 <hi>Hopkins</hi> Salvation from Sin by Jeſus Chriſt — 1655</item>
               <item>372 <hi>Taylor</hi> (Dr. <hi>Tho.</hi>) principles of Chriſtian Practice — 1635</item>
               <item>373 <hi>Stokes Verus Chriſtianus,</hi> or directions for Private Devotions — 1668</item>
               <item>374 <hi>Shirleys</hi> Poems — 1646</item>
               <item>375 <hi>Boyles</hi> Experiments, about the poroſity of Bodies — 1684</item>
               <item>376 Dr. <hi>Jacombs</hi> Treatiſe of Holy dedication, both perſonal and domeſtick — 1668</item>
               <item>377 <hi>Camfieds</hi> Enquiry in the comprehenſive Rule of Righteouſneſs — 1671</item>
               <item>378 Sir <hi>Walter Raleighs</hi> Judicious and Select Eſſays and Obſervations — 1650</item>
               <item>379 <hi>De Jure Maritimo,</hi> or a Treatiſe of Affairs Maritime — 1677</item>
               <item>380 Dr. <hi>Sherlocks</hi> Diſcourſe of the Knowledge of Jeſus Chriſt — 1674</item>
               <item>381 <hi>Steels</hi> Tradeſmans-calling — 1684</item>
               <item>382 <hi>Bournes</hi> Light from Chriſt, leading unto Chriſt — 1646</item>
               <item>383 <hi>Dringleys</hi> deputation of Angels, or the Angel Guardian — 1654</item>
               <item>384 The whole Duty of Man — 1686</item>
               <item>385 The whole Duty of Man, the ſecond part — 1683</item>
               <item>386 Gentlemans Calling, and Decay of Piety, bound together — 1668</item>
               <item>387 <hi>Hornecks</hi> happy Aſcetick, or beſt Exerciſe — 1686</item>
               <item>388 —Great Law of Conſideration — 1677</item>
               <item>389 —Exerciſe of Prayer, a help to Devotion — 1685</item>
               <item>390 —Firſt Fruits of Reaſon — 1686</item>
               <item>391 <hi>Watſon</hi> on the Beatitudes, or a Diſcourſe on Chriſts Sermon on the Mount 1671</item>
               <item>392 <hi>Tanners</hi> Primordia, or the Riſe and Growth of the firſt Church of God deſcribed 1683</item>
               <item>393 <hi>Temple</hi> (Sir <hi>Will.</hi>) Obſervations on the United Provinces of the <hi>Netherlands</hi> 1673</item>
               <item>394 The Diſcovery of a new World in the Moon — 1638</item>
               <item>395 <hi>Barrows</hi> Compendious demonſtration, of the whole 15 Books of <hi>Euclids</hi> Elements 1686</item>
               <item>396 Biſhop <hi>Wilkins</hi> of the Principles and Duties of Natural Religion — 1683</item>
               <item>397 An Epitome of <hi>Speeds</hi> Deſcrip. and Maps of <hi>England, Scotland,</hi> and <hi>Ireland</hi> — 1660</item>
               <item>398 Men before <hi>Adam</hi> — 1656</item>
               <item>399 <hi>Lux <gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>rientalis,</hi> or an enquiry concerning the pre-exiſtence of Souls — 1662</item>
               <item>400 <hi>M<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>gers French</hi> Grammar — 1686</item>
               <item>401 <hi>L<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ſ<gap reason="illegible" resp="#MURP" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>els</hi> Voyage of <hi>Italy,</hi> with Characters of the People, and deſcrip. of the Towns <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1670</item>
               <item>402 <hi>Larkins</hi> Looking-glaſs of the Fathers, wherein you may ſee them characterized, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1659</item>
               <item>403 Now help to diſcourſe, or Wit and Jollity, mixt with more ſerious matters 1684</item>
               <item>404 <hi>Engliſh</hi> Dictionary, or an Expoſitor of hard <hi>Engliſh</hi> words — 1670</item>
               <item>405 <hi>Effigies Amoris,</hi> or the Picture of Love Unveiled — 1682</item>
               <item>406 <hi>Heywoods</hi> Hiſtory of Women, containing the lives of the moſt Holy and Prophane, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1657</item>
               <item>407 <hi>Walſinghams</hi> Manual of Prudential Maximes for the States-man and Courtier</item>
               <item>408 <hi>Englands</hi> Jeſts Refined and Improved, 1687. and Poor Robins Jeſts</item>
               <item>409 Five Love Letters from a Nun to a Cavalier, and five Letters by a Cavalier to a Nun</item>
               <item>410 <hi>Religio Medici,</hi> with Annotations and Obſervations by Sir <hi>Kenelm Digby</hi> 1659</item>
               <pb n="22" facs="tcp:42676:23"/>
               <item>411 <hi>Ogilbys</hi> tranſlation of <hi>Virgil,</hi> adorned with Sculptures, and illuſtrated with Annotations. 1675</item>
               <item>412 <hi>Roſſes</hi> Muſes Interpreter, explaining the myſteries of the <hi>Greek</hi> and <hi>Latin</hi> Poets 1653</item>
               <item>413 Reduction of <hi>Ireland</hi> to the Crown of <hi>England</hi> — 1675</item>
               <item>414 Vindication of the Primitive Chriſtians in point of Obedience to their Prince — 1683</item>
               <item>415 <hi>Ames</hi> ſubſtance of Chriſtian Religion, wants a title</item>
               <item>416 <hi>Smithies</hi> benefit of early Piety, recommended to the Youth of the City of <hi>London</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>417 <hi>Englands</hi> faithful Reprover and Monitor — 1653</item>
               <item>418 <hi>Agars</hi> Paraphraſe on the <hi>Canticles</hi> or <hi>Song of Solomon</hi> — 1680</item>
               <item>419 <hi>Nalſons</hi> intereſt of tne King and People, ſhewing the Origil, Antiquity, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> of Monarchy 1678</item>
               <item>420 Dr <hi>Sherlocks</hi> diſcourſe concerning the knowledge of Jeſus Chriſt — 1674</item>
               <item>421 Dr. <hi>Patricks</hi> Diſcourſe concerning the Sacrament of the Lords Supper — 1660</item>
               <item>422 <hi>Agiatis</hi> Queen of <hi>Sparta,</hi> or the Civil Wars of the <hi>Lacedemonians</hi> — 1686</item>
               <item>423 The honourable ſtate of Matrimony made comfortable — 1685</item>
               <item>424 Dr. <hi>Burnets</hi> tranſlation and examination of a Letter writ by the Clergy of <hi>Fr.</hi> to the Proteſt.</item>
               <item>425 <hi>Charras</hi> new experiments upon Vipers — 1670</item>
               <item>426 <hi>Spencers</hi> Art of Logick, delivered in the Precepts of <hi>Ariſtotle</hi> and <hi>Ramus</hi> — 1628</item>
               <item>427 <hi>Anderſons</hi> Gauging — 1668</item>
               <item>428 <hi>Proteus Redivivus,</hi> or the Art of Wheedling — 1679</item>
               <item>429 <hi>Sandis</hi> tranſlation of <hi>Ovids Metamorphoſis</hi> — 1678</item>
               <item>430 <hi>Burroughs</hi> gracious Spirit, and <hi>Moſes</hi> Self-denial: bound together — 1640</item>
               <item>431 <hi>Reyners</hi> conſiderations concerning Marriage — 1657</item>
               <item>432 A ſpiritual Duel between a Chriſtian and Satan — 1646</item>
               <item>433 <hi>Blunts</hi> Dictionary, interpreting the hard Words in the <hi>Engliſh</hi> Tongue — 1674</item>
               <item>434 Sir <hi>John Denhams</hi> Poems and Tranſlations, with the <hi>Sophy</hi> — 1684</item>
               <item>435 Sir <hi>Aſtin Cokains</hi> Poems of divers ſorts — 1658</item>
               <item>436 Dr. <hi>Burnets</hi> Vindication of the Ordinations of the Church of <hi>England</hi> — 1677</item>
               <item>437 Dr. <hi>Sherlocks</hi> Diſcourſe of Religious aſſEmblies — 1682</item>
               <item>438 Dr. <hi>Sibbs</hi> Souls conflict with it ſelf — 1651</item>
               <item>439 <hi>Cokes</hi> compleat Copy-holder, with a Suppliment neceſſary for Landlord &amp; Tenant 1663</item>
               <item>440 Sir <hi>Tho Smiths</hi> Commonwealth of <hi>England,</hi> and the manner and Government thereof 1640</item>
               <item>441 The Office and Duty of Executors, directing Teſtators in making their Wills, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> 1641</item>
               <item>442 <hi>Flagellum,</hi> or the Life and Death of <hi>O. Cromwel</hi> the Uſurper — 1665</item>
               <item>443 Dr. <hi>Bauderons</hi> expert Phyſician, learnedly treating of all Agues and Feavers 1657</item>
               <item>444 <hi>Franc<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>s Quarles</hi> divine Poems — 1634</item>
               <item>445 <hi>Martin Luthers</hi> thirty four Sermons — 1652</item>
               <item>446 <hi>Now-Englands</hi> Rarities diſcovered, in Birds, Beaſts, Fiſnes, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1672</item>
               <item>447 Collection of Poems written on ſeveral occaſions by ſeveral perſons — 1672</item>
               <item>448 <hi>Marchs</hi> Actions for ſlander, ſhewing what Words are actionable in Law, and what not 1648</item>
               <item>449 The Souls communion with her Saviour, or the Hiſtory of our Lord Jeſus Chriſt 1685</item>
               <item>450 Dr. <hi>Rolls</hi> Doctrine of Juſtification ſtated according to the Scriptures — 1674</item>
               <item>451 <hi>Leybourns</hi> Platform for Purchaſers, Guide for Builders, Mate for Meaſurers — 1668</item>
               <item>452 The <hi>Indian</hi> Hiſtory of <hi>Anaxander</hi> and <hi>Orazia</hi> — 1657</item>
               <item>453 The Elements or Principles of Geometry — 1684</item>
               <item>454 The Mirrour which factors not, enriched with fair Figures — 1639</item>
               <item>455 <hi>Bartens</hi> Hiſtorical Romarques on the Antient and Preſent State of <hi>London</hi> — 1684</item>
               <item>456 Wits Recreation, wherein are Conceits for the Witty, and Medicines for the Melanch. 1667</item>
               <item>457 The Mirrour of For<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="3 letters">
                     <desc>•••</desc>
                  </gap>, or the true Characters of Fate and Deſtiny, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1676</item>
               <item>458 The <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> of the Creature, by the Author of the whole duty of Man — 1684</item>
               <item>459 <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> Marrow of <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>acred <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ivinity — 1642</item>
               <item>460 <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> Treatis;e of the power of Godline's — 1658</item>
               <pb n="23" facs="tcp:42676:23"/>
               <item>461 Singing Pſalm Book, with the reading Pſalms on the Margent — 1649</item>
               <item>462 Dr. <hi>Brevints Miſſale Romanum,</hi> or the dep<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>h and myſtery of the <hi>Roman</hi> Maſs 1673</item>
               <item>463 <hi>Howels Dodonas</hi> Grove, or the vocal Forreſt — 1645</item>
               <item>464 Wit and Drollery, jovial Poems — 1682</item>
               <item>465 <hi>Ovid de Arte Amandi,</hi> as alſo the loves of <hi>Hero</hi> and <hi>Leander</hi> — 1682</item>
               <item>466 <hi>Marianus,</hi> or Loves Heroick Champions — 1641</item>
               <item>467 Hiſtorical and Political Obſervations on the preſent State of <hi>Turkey</hi> — 1683</item>
               <item>468 <hi>Auguſtus Anglicus,</hi> or the Life and Reign of the immortal &amp; glorious Monarch <hi>Charles</hi> II. 1686</item>
               <item>469 Hiſtory of the Court of the K. of <hi>China.</hi> Hiſtory of the Amours of the <hi>French</hi> Court. 1684</item>
               <item>470 Memoires of the Duke of <hi>Rohan</hi> — 1660</item>
               <item>471 The Image of both Churches, <hi>Jeruſalem</hi> and <hi>Babel,</hi> Unity and Confuſion <hi>Tournay</hi> 1623</item>
               <item>472 A Teſtament and Singing Pſalms, with <hi>Bezas</hi> Notes, wants a Title</item>
               <item>473 <hi>Fenners</hi> wilful Impenitency the groſſeſt Self-murther — 1648</item>
               <item>474 <hi>Cartwrights</hi> Doctrine of Faith, handled in ſundry Sermons — 1650</item>
               <item>475 <hi>Wilsford</hi> of the generation of Meteors and Blazing-Stars — 1665</item>
               <item>476 The illuſtrious Hiſtory of WOMEN — 1686</item>
               <item>477 Wits Cabinet, or a Companion for Young Men and Ladies — 1685</item>
               <item>478 The Loves of <hi>Clitophon</hi> and <hi>Lucippe</hi> — 1638</item>
               <item>479 The Viſions of <hi>Dom Franciſco de Quevedo</hi> — 1678</item>
               <item>480 <hi>Smiths</hi> Inſtructions for the <hi>French, Italian, Spaniſh</hi> and <hi>Engliſh</hi> Tongues — 1674</item>
               <item>481 Trial of K. <hi>Charles</hi> I. with the dying Speeches of ſeveral of the Loyal Nobility 1660</item>
               <item>482 <hi>Perrinchiefs</hi> Life and Death of King <hi>Charles</hi> the Firſt — 1684</item>
               <item>483 Sir <hi>John Sucklings</hi> Works, containing Poems, Playes, Letters, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> — 1676</item>
               <item>484 <hi>Shepards</hi> ſound Believer — 1670</item>
               <item>485 <hi>Bezas</hi> Paraphraſe on the Book of the Pſalms of <hi>David</hi> — 1581</item>
               <item>486 Hiſtory of the latter times of the <hi>Jews,</hi> with the deſtruction of <hi>Jeruſalem</hi> 1684</item>
               <item>487 Mock <hi>Clelia,</hi> being a Comical Hiſt. of <hi>French</hi> Gallantries and Novels — 1678</item>
               <item>488 <hi>England</hi> and <hi>Wales</hi> deſcribed, with every Shire, and the ſmall Towns, in 6 Maps 1644</item>
               <item>489 Preſent State of <hi>Jamaica</hi> 1683 Young Anglers Companion, cont. the whole Art of Angling 1680</item>
               <item>490 <hi>Randolphs</hi> Poems, with the Muſes Look. glaſs, <hi>Amyntas,</hi> Jeal. Lov. <hi>Ariſtippus,</hi> &amp;conc. Pedlar 1664</item>
               <item>491 School of the Heart, in 47 Emblems, in Calves Leather, Gilt back — 1675</item>
               <item>492 <hi>Vennings</hi> things worth thinking on, or helps to Piety, in 412 Meditations — 1665</item>
               <item>493 —Orthodox Paradoxes, theoritical and experimental — 1627</item>
               <item>494 —Myſteries and Revelations — 1647</item>
               <item>495 Diſcourſe of Natural and Moral Impotency — 1671</item>
               <item>496 Dr. <hi>Sibbs</hi> bruiſed Reed and ſmoaking Flax, with the life of the Author fairly written 1630</item>
               <item>497 —The Spiritual Mans aim — 1638</item>
               <item>498 <hi>Ferrarius</hi> his Epiſtles concerning the uſefulneſs and neceſſity of the <hi>Roman</hi> Cath. Faith 1673</item>
               <item>499 Plain-mans way of worſhip and practice — 1678</item>
               <item>400 Biſhop <hi>Taylors</hi> Chriſts Yoke an eaſie Yoke, in 2 excellent Sermons — 1675</item>
               <item>401 <hi>Fullers Andronians,</hi> or the unfortunate Politician — 1646</item>
               <item>402 Plous Politician, or the Remains of the Royal Martyr King <hi>Charlas</hi> the Firſt 1634</item>
               <item>403 Hiſtory of Moderation 1669 <hi>Blunts</hi> Eſſays and Characters — 1628</item>
               <item>404 <hi>Blunts</hi> Dictionary, interpreting the hard words in our <hi>Engliſh</hi> Tongue — 1674</item>
               <item>405 Dr. <hi>F<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="3 letters">
                        <desc>•••</desc>
                     </gap>leys</hi> Fountain of Teares — 1683</item>
               <item>406 Dr. <hi>Wi<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="3 letters">
                        <desc>•••</desc>
                     </gap>er</hi> of Education, eſpecially of Young Gentlemen — 1673</item>
               <item>407 Unfortunate Hero, a Novel, 1679. Men-miracles with other Poems — 1679</item>
               <item>408 <hi>Herberts</hi> Devotion, or a Companion for a Chriſtian — 1657</item>
               <item>409 <hi>O<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="4 letters">
                        <desc>••••</desc>
                     </gap>ne</hi> advice to a Son, in a Volumes — 1656</item>
               <item>410 —Political Reflections on the Government of the <hi>Turks</hi> — 1656</item>
            </list>
         </div>
         <div type="catalogue">
            <pb n="24" facs="tcp:42676:24"/>
            <head>Divinity, Hiſtory, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> in Folio and Quarto, Omitted.</head>
            <list>
               <item>1 <hi>HErberts</hi> Travels into <hi>Africa</hi> and <hi>Aſia</hi> the great, laſt Edition full of Maps and Cuts 1677</item>
               <item>2 <hi>Brown</hi> (Sir <hi>Tho</hi>) Enquiries into Vulgar Errors — 1646</item>
               <item>3 <hi>Bentivolio and Urania,</hi> in ſix Books, by Dr. <hi>Nathaniel Ingelo</hi> — 1669</item>
               <item>4 <hi>Barclay</hi> his <hi>Argenis,</hi> or the loves of <hi>Peliarchus</hi> and <hi>Argenis</hi> — 1625</item>
               <item>5 <hi>Poultons</hi> Collection of Statutes — 1618</item>
               <item>6 Dr. <hi>Stillingfleets</hi> Sermons, with a Diſcourſe about the Sufferings of Chriſt, want a Title</item>
               <item>7 Pſalms and Hymns in ſolemn Muſick, in four parts, by <hi>John Playford</hi> — 1671</item>
               <item>8 <hi>Cowleys</hi> Works of Poetry. — 1681</item>
               <item>9 <hi>Tind<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>l, <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>ith</hi> and <hi>Ra<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>es</hi> Wo<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ks, three worthy Martyrs — 1673</item>
               <item>10 <hi>Clarkes</hi> Martyrologie, giving an account of the perſecutions of the Ch. from the Creation 1660</item>
               <item>11 <hi>Mi<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ſ<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="3 letters">
                        <desc>•••</desc>
                     </gap>s Spaniſh</hi> Dictionary, with fair Manuſcript Additions, wants a title</item>
               <item>12 <hi>Eliana,</hi> a<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ew Roma<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ce, formed by an <hi>Engliſh</hi> hand — 1661</item>
               <item>13 <hi>Biſhop Fo<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>herbys Athcomaſtix,</hi> againſt Atheiſt and Infidels — 1622</item>
               <item>14 Dr. <hi>Ham<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>nonds</hi> Sermons — 1675</item>
               <item>15 —Paraphraſe and Annotations upon the Book of the <hi>Pſalms</hi> — 1659</item>
               <item>16 Hiſtory of the World, commonly called the Natural Hiſtory of <hi>C. Plinius Secundus</hi> 1601</item>
               <item>17 —of the Lives of the Noble <hi>Grecians</hi> and <hi>Romans,</hi> by <hi>Plutarch</hi> — 1657</item>
               <item>18 —of <hi>Venice,</hi> from the firſt foundation of that City, by <hi>W. Shute,</hi> wants a title</item>
               <item>19 —of the <hi>Turks,</hi> from the beg. of that Nat. with the Lives of the <hi>Ottoman</hi> Emp. By <hi>R. Knolls</hi> 1603</item>
               <item>20 —of the Life and Death of the Renowned Prelate <hi>W.</hi> Archb. of <hi>Canterbury,</hi> by <hi>P. Heylin</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>21 —of the World, by Sir <hi>Walter Raleigh</hi> — 1614</item>
               <item>22 —Of excellent Perſonages who ſuffered for their Sovereign K. <hi>Charles</hi> I. by Dr. <hi>Lloyd</hi> 1668</item>
               <item>23 —of <hi>France,</hi> writ in <hi>Italian</hi> by <hi>Gualdo Priorato,</hi> engliſhed by <hi>W. Brent.</hi> — 1676</item>
               <item>24 <hi>Luſhingtons</hi> Commentary upon the Epiſtles to the <hi>Hebrews</hi> — 1646</item>
               <item>25 <hi>Reynolds</hi> Triumphs of Gods Revenge againſt Murther. imperfect — 1640</item>
               <item>26 <hi>Daltons</hi> Country Juſtice, containing the practice of a Juſtice of Peace — 1635</item>
               <item>27 General practice of Phyſick, containing Remedies for all Diſeaſes from head to foot 1654</item>
               <item>28 <hi>Williams</hi> right way to the beſt Religion — 1636</item>
               <item>29 <hi>Ambroſe Prima &amp; Media,</hi> or firſt and middle things, with the redeeming the time 1674</item>
               <item>30 <hi>Caryls</hi> Expoſition with practical obſerv. on the book of <hi>Job,</hi> 2 vol. compleat 1676</item>
               <item>31 Biſhop <hi>Reynolds</hi> Works — 1679</item>
               <item>32 Biſhop <hi>Taylors</hi> 28 Sermons for the Summer half year — 1651</item>
               <item>33 Biſhop <hi>Sanderſons</hi> 20 Sermons. <hi>ad Anlum, ad Magiſtratum, ad Populum</hi> — 1656</item>
               <item>34 The Works of King <hi>Charles</hi> the Martyr, in 2 Volumes, Gilt and Letter'd 1662</item>
               <item>35 Sir <hi>Jonas Moors</hi> Syſtem of the Mathematicks, in 2 Volumes compleat. Gilt-back 1681</item>
               <item>36 <hi>Arthur Jackſons</hi> Annotations on the Bible, as far as the <hi>Pſalms</hi> — 1643</item>
               <item>37 <hi>Burroughs</hi> Goſpel Reconciliation — 1657</item>
               <item>38 <hi>Olbian,</hi> the new Iſland lately diſcovered — 1660</item>
               <item>39 Account of the Trial of the Regicides — 1660</item>
               <item>40 <hi>Phelpes</hi> Commentary on the five firſt Chapters of the <hi>Revelations</hi> — 1678</item>
               <item>41 Dr. <hi>Sibbs</hi> Fountain open'd, or the myſtery of Godlineſs Revealed — 1638</item>
               <item>42 Life of the Thrice Noble, High and Puiſſant Prince, <hi>Will.</hi> Duke of <hi>Newcuſtle</hi> 1975</item>
               <item>43 <hi>Swinburne</hi> of Teſtaments, and Wills, uſeful for all the Subjects of this Realm 1640</item>
               <item>44 Dr. <hi>Godolphins</hi> Orphans Legacy, or Treatiſe of Wills and Teſtaments — 1677</item>
               <item>45 <hi>Cowells</hi> interpreter of ſuch words and termes as are mentioned in Law writers 1637</item>
               <item>46 <hi>Mayers</hi> Expoſition on <hi>Matthew, Mark, Luke, John,</hi> and <hi>Acts</hi> — 1622</item>
               <item>47 <hi>Heylins</hi> little deſcription of the Great World — 1639</item>
               <item>48 <hi>Nicols</hi> Lapidary, or Hiſtory of Precious Stones, with cautions for the dealer in them 1613</item>
               <item>49 A very ancient and fair manuſcript on <hi>Velum,</hi> containing the <hi>P<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ter-<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>ſter,</hi> 
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap>, Creed, Ten Commandments, with their Expoſitions. as alſo Diſcourſes on ſev. <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
            </list>
            <trailer>FINIS.</trailer>
            <pb facs="tcp:42676:24"/>
         </div>
      </body>
   </text>
</TEI>
